Remember the "Personality".
Ladies and gentlemen...
greatest name of all times
of flamenco dance...
Senora Feza.
- Olé.
- Sure, Olé.
Do you think Nevra
was convinced?
Absolutely.
So much for been convinced.
She is following us.
The three man who were killed...
they were on the list
in our website.
You know what this means
don't you?
"Dog Killer" is following
our website.
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
That's why the woman neither
got raped nor she got married.
But we knew she was married.
I decided to follow her to find out...
where she was going
and who was forcing her to lie.
That's when you
came into the scene.
- How did you find out?
- I wanted to see the place.
As you can see, the place
has gone back in time.
Nevra Elmas.
Mrs Nesrin's daughter.
Don't call me on this
number again.
In fact, it is better
if you forget this number.
What do you want?
Now, the honourable D.A...
who has been messing
with my case and why?
This is number one.
And the number two...
who specifically reinstated the
man to the case whom I removed?
Who is running this case?
What's going on?
Nevra!
- Reyhan.
- Who is Reyhan?
[Did you hide your gift?
[Yes. What do you want from me?
[To meet me.
[When and where?
[Soon and nearby.
[How will I recognize you?
[There'll be another gift in my hand.
[What is it?
Deva!
Grandad!
Turn that thing of.
Something really bad happened
to me today, because of you.
Why? What happened?
What's done is done.
None of your business.
Dad?
What's going on? Why are you
shouting at the boy?
He put the car's logbook
in a wrong place.
I wasted my morning
looking for it.
Is that what it was?
I thought something happened.
Did you find it anyway?
Yes, I did.
But it was too late.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Did we find her?
I mean, is this the girl
whom Tayyar raped?
I don't know.
But even if we found her,
it is too late.
Much too late.
Reyhan, wait!
My poor baby, how could you
take your own life?
She was still a baby.
Don't you remember Reyhan, mum?
No darling,
I don't remember her.
Was she your friend?
We were classmates.
But I erased almost every memory
related to Kambura.
I don't remember anything.
But when I saw the photo
I thought "I know this girl."
"This is Reyhan."
She was slightly older than me.
That's right, she was
2 years older than me.
What else do you remember?
I don't know.
It is not very clear.
I don't think Reyhan committing suicide
is linked to Tayyar's death.
She committed suicide in 1996.
Tayyar died in 2008.
There are 12 years in between.
Whoever burned down Tayyar's house,
be it Ufuk or somebody else...
wouldn't have waited 12 years
to take Reyhan's revenge.
Anyway, it is not yet clear
why Reyhan had committed suicide.
She committed suicide
2 years after we left the town.
How old was she at the time?
She was 2 years older than me.
That makes her 14.
Why would she do such a thing?
There are 11 cases of female suicide
in the last 15 years.
The dates are closer to the time
when Tayyar was murdered.
If there is a case of rape
it's got be one of them.
I think we should start
by digging into these files.
I don't know any of these girls.
Excuse me.
Hello?
O, K, let's assume that this case
is directly linked to you.
You must know the victim or the killer,
or whatever you want to call them.
So, it may come to you later,
just like you remembered Reyhan.
Just tell me when and where.
Don't worry, no one will know.
Why don't you try to trust me?
If you ask me, this Reyhan case
is waste of time.
Just one more day.
If I don't get a break
I'll go back to Istanbul.
O.K, whatever you say.
Meanwhile I'll go through the files.
O.K, I've got to go.
How are you doing?
I don't know.
Where are you going to start?
I'll check her house first...
and the place
I remember her from.
The school.
My mum knows our teacher.
He settled here after he got retired.
I'll talk to him.
I don't know.
How about you?
Will you go back to Istanbul?
Actually, now that I am here,
I can ask your mother's permission...
to marry you.
But she'd probably ask
what I do for a living.
And I say to her "I am a foot soldier in
the army of unemployed journalists".
That's why I should go back to Istanbul
and return when I get a job.
- Are you alright dad?
- So so.
Are you still upset about
that logbook thing?
No, no. It doesn't
matter anymore.
- I am sorry.
- Yeah, O.K.
You used to do the same to me
when I was little, remember?
You used to put me through hell
for the smallest thing.
Nothing has changed.
Once I broke the video.
If it wasn't for my mum
he would've kicked me out.
He was so mad.
It was just a video,
a piece of machinery.
I had the right to be mad.
I told you not to mess around with it.
We'd only just bought it.
I wanted to enjoy a good movie
only to find out that it wasn't working.
I'd only just begun
to pay the instalments.
Do you know
how much it cost to get it fixed?
You have such a good memory.
It is scary.
You probably still remember
what the movie was.
Of course I do.
Kramer vs Kramer.
Of course I remember.
How do you remember all this?
I never forget.
Now I remember.
I remember the old.
Now there is even a better movie out.
Beyoğlu vs Beyoğlu.
What do you think? Is it nice?
I am so glad that I broke that video.
Well done to me.
- I am off.
- Where to?
I am going on a vacation
with Miss Nükhet.
Going on a vacation with Nükhet?
What is he going to do
with that woman?
"That woman" loves me.
Does she know you
well enough to love you?
Because it's easy to love someone
whom you don't really know.
I both know and love you.
Let's see if she can
do the same.
What is he going to do with
Nükhet on vacation?
We'll make love all night.
What did he say?
Do you know...
one day, they'll put us in jars
just like these...
and scientists will say "there used be a
species called "human"...
but now it's extinct.
It became obsolete.
We may have nothing left
to be put in jars.
The way we're going, the human
race will wipe itself off the history.
That's correct too.
For once, we are
on the same side.
First of all, thanks
for coming Ateş.
You're welcome. I thought this has
got to be important.
Otherwise, why should superintendent
Tolga call a clown?
- Ateş, look...!
- No, no.
You're right.
I've been a clown for years.
But it is over now.
Well, I am all ears.
Alright...
you know that serial killer thing...
there is someone at the top
interfering with the case.
I can't find out who that is...
neither the reason
why they're doing it.
I know you have connections.
Can you help me find this man?
- I can try.
- Fine, good.
But with one condition...
no breaking news
until this case is solved.
Is that a deal?
O.K.
O.K, it is a deal.
Let me ask you something.
Go ahead.
How come you trust me?
Nevra...
Nevra trusts you.
And I trust Nevra.
One more question.
You have all the
right to be anxious.
I will share another
information with you.
Have I got everything?
Toothbrush, socks.
I should take a book too.
We seized evidence from
Tufan Elibol's body...
whom the killer used
to throw us off the case.
Do you really have any evidence?
What do you think?
It is a hoax story.
Let's call it "bonus to
encourage mistake".
It is better this way.
It means that the killer
shot himself on the foot.
And I can assure you
he will be caught very soon.
I was watching the press conference
about the serial killer.
Were you about to say something?
No, I am going.
Grandad!
Don't you want to see mum
before you leave?
I am in hurry.
You can give her a kiss for me.
Mum! Grandad is going.
At least tell us
where you are going?
I am going to
Tanzania for safari.
What am I going to do now?
I never heard that.
May be, I heard
but never listened.
How can they find evidence?
I washed him thoroughly...
with bleach.
Or did I?
How can they find evidence?
Yes, I washed him.
Did I wash him?
No, I didn't. Yes, I did.
It is not possible.
Because I washed the body.
I didn't wash it.
Why?
It is too late now. It is the
end of the road. They got me.
Nothing you can do.
No, wait. Don't rush.
No cops at the door.
They should've been here by now.
They may be on their way.
It's been so many days.
They would've been here by now.
I was about to go on vacation.
Relax a bit and
read a nice book.
I've already read this.
I've just read it.
O.K.
So, this is the case.
Just let it be.
I'll go and do another one.
This one's already gone.
What is this?
No, this one is in Istanbul.
What else?
Not this one either.
F..ck off to hell.
Yes, this one will do.
Business and pleasure in one.
Kill them all.
I think this one will do.
What do you say? Is it O.K?
This will do.
Are you talking to me?
So, what are we doing?
I thought if we go to a spa,
there'll be herds of old people...
floating in the water
like buoys.
It is boring.
I came up with
something different.
- Where?
- It is a surprise.
O.K, that's fine.
But do you know what the
real surprise was?
When you called me this morning
to tell me that...
we are leaving right away.
That was the real surprise.
You caught me off guard.
Because something
happened yesterday.
And I made a decision.
You should never put anything
on hold in life.
What happened?
My kite got stuck on a tree.
Kite?
Do you mean,
you've been flying kites?
Yes, of course.
You are such an
amazing man Agah.
Without being big headed,
I think I am, a little bit.
What is she doing now?
I don't know. She has been in there
for 10 minutes.
I'll find out what she is up to.
Listen Firuz...
you made a mistake by getting
caught by Nevra.
And what did I do?
I took your mistake and
blew it out of proportion.
And that mistake grew so big,
it became legit.
But it doesn't mean that
same will happen every time.
Luckily we sealed the crack.
I want no more cracks Firuz.
I don't want any more leaks.
Is that clear?
If my house gets flooded,
you'd be the first one to drown.
O.K Mr Cemil.
I've been having this done for years
but I am yet to decide.
I wonder who feels better
at the end of the day.
Me or them?
I think I came into this world
to feed the leeches.
Yes, thank you. Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Not understanding anything
is so nice.
- This is such a nice place.
- Yes, it is.
I've heard Pınarcak was a nice place.
But I never had the chance to visit.
I think there is a waterfall here.
Yes, we'll go there too.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- We'd like two rooms.
- Sure, just a second.
Why not a single room?
Do you have your
marriage certificate with you?
We were married by Imam.
And there are cameras
on hallways.
How about Muta marriage?
I am sorry.
Here.
That's what happens
in small places.
Not small, crowded.
I am afraid so.
If you excuse me, I'd like to
take an hour's rest.
I got up very early this morning
and driving tired me out.
Yeah, sure.
I can check my e-mails.
Let's meet downstairs
in one hour.
- O.K, see you.
- See you.
Of course I remember you.
Mrs Nesrin's daughter,
Nevra Elmas.
So, you came to
see your teacher?
I've heard that you've become a cop.
Well done to you.
So, what have you been up to?
Do you like being a cop?
Don't ask.
It was really bad.
They found Reyhan,
laying on the grass.
You know, on the hill where
they take the herds for grazing.
Reyhan!
Come on!
Reyhan, wait.
I can't keep up.
Thanks.
Thank you very much sweetheart.
Have you met my wife Nevra?
No. Pleased to meet you.
Enjoy it.
I was a lot younger then.
God, what was I talking about?
Oh yes, Reyhan was laying
on the grass.
And there was a bottle of
rat poison beside her.
God knows how she got
hold of it.
Such a clever girl. What made her
do such a thing?
What can I say?
You never know what goes on
in someone's head.
Binnaz, come over here.
Sit with us darling.
No thanks. I'll be inside.
She was really talented.
She used to write
great compositions.
She was a late starter at school.
But she was really smart.
She was very smart.
She was like a diamond.
And talented.
She only had a granny.
She had nobody else.
And she passed away.
Well sir...
as far as you can remember...
do you think something
might've happened to Reyhan...
after we left town?
No, I don't think so.
As far as I remember,
there was no wrong doing.
But she was missing school
as of late.
She was there one day
but not the next.
Her file says cause of death is
suicide due to heavy depression.
Have you noticed anything?
Was she depressed?
As far as I remember, Reyhan was a
cheerful girl with a big smile.
But it is not possible to know
what's been happening deep inside.
Sir, can I use the toilet?
What is this?
Is this how I trained you?
You have to raise your hand
and ask for permission first.
I was joking.
Nevra, my sweetheart.
I was only joking.
Go ahead.
Binnaz will show you the way.
Damn! I'll be late.
Did you know Reyhan?
No.
I am not from
around here anyway.
I've come from the village.
When did you come to Kambura?
After I got married.
I was around 15 years old.
That's how I ended up here.
Fifteen?
How old was Mr Tahsin at the time?
In his fifties.
I see.
Thanks.
Do you have something
to tell me Binnaz?
I don't know that girl, Reyhan, but...!
Binnaz!
Can you pour me some tea?
I was new around here.
May be only a year.
I heard that a girl
took her own life.
God almighty! Can't she hear me?
Binnaz! I asked you
to fill my glass.
Binnaz!
One day, while he was at school
a woman popped-by.
She said she was
Reyhan's granny.
She said she found a notebook
hidden inside her pillow.
She said "she wrote down
everything here".
"This may reveal clues
as to why she killed herself".
Why did she bring
the notebook to you?
Binnaz!
Why did she bring it to you?
She was illiterate.
She said "give this to the teacher,
he'd know what to do with it".
And what did you do?
Binnaz!
I didn't do anything.
I just took a quick glance.
Then?
I gave it back to her and
told her to take it to the police station.
She said she already did.
But the police had sent her away saying
that the case is already closed.
I told her to go to the courthouse.
- What was in the notebook?
- I don't know.
I was illiterate at the time too.
Why did you tell her
to take it to the courthouse...
instead of handing it
over to Mr.Tahsin?
I wasn't about to give the poor girl's
notebook to a man...
who took a child as a wife.
He loves me. We'll get married.
I'll be a bride.
You two have been here for ages.
I have been asking you to
pour me a cup of tea.
You wouldn't have
known if I died.
S... it!
This is Hamza.
I am Nevra, the deputy chief.
I sure recognize you.
How can I not, anyway?
How could you forget
the one who put you away?
What do you want this time?
Has your brother Tayyar
ever mentioned a girl named Reyhan?
A 14 year old from Kambura.
Reyhan.
Can you hear me Hamza?
Yes, I can.
Did you say Reyhan?
Yes, Reyhan.
What's in it for me?
- Do you know the girl?
- I don't.
But let's say, I heard the name.
What can you do for me?
I tell you what I'll do, I'll come over
there, lock you in solitary confinement...
and throw away the key.
How about that?
You have such a quick temper, sis.
Woman with a short fuse.
Look, I don't know much
about this Reyhan girl.
This is the first time
I hear the name after a long time.
But now, I remember.
Tayyar kept repeating
her name when he was stoned.
When we asked about the girl
he used to say things like...
"poor girl, they wasted her".
We used to ask him after he sobered up
but he couldn't remember anything.
Perhaps he remembered
but avoided the subject with us.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
When I've asked you
if Tayyar raped anyone...
why didn't you mention Reyhan?
You are so gullible sis.
Tayyar was an alcoholic.
He was stoned.
He used to say "they wasted her",
not "I wasted her".
I'll tell you what...
a drunken man can do
anything except one thing...
he can't lie.
If he got up to no good
he would've told us.
It means that
somebody else did it.
So, what is it?
The girl has gone and
the case is closed, isn't it?
Keep quiet Tayyar.
Keep quiet for what?
She was wasted
in broad day-light.
Poor Reyhan got wasted.
Shut up!
Do you call yourselves men?
What did you want
from the poor girl?
I am listening.
Sir, this plate is no
longer registered.
What do you mean?
It was dropped from the system in 1998
and the vehicle was scrapped.
I see.
- Here is your coffee.
- Thanks mum.
Mum...
I think really bad things
happened here.
Do you mean the burned house?
No, not that. I mean Reyhan.
I think some people
did very bad things to her.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know.
But whatever happened,
people of Kambura are responsible.
Why are you laughing?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Do you know someone
called Reyhan?
- Who, who did you say?
- Reyhan.
- Nevra's schoolmate.
- Mum!
The girl who committed suicide
when she was 14.
I swear, I don't know her.
How would I know her anyway?
Look, if you're hiding anything...!
Mum, calm down. Come here.
- God almighty.
- Calm down.
Sit down.
Uncle Selim...
you know my friend, Reyhan...
something really bad
happened to her...
here in Kambura.
I am not too sure...
but you know the killer
who picks victims from Kambura...
I think he kills the
ones who did evil to Reyhan.
If you know anything about this
or have an idea...
please tell me. Don't be afraid.
If you know anything but not telling me,
that's when you should be afraid.
Because the killer
will eventually find you too.
I told you, I haven't done anything.
I only threw a small piece of stone.
Look here, you b... stard!
Just spill the beans.
You said he was having
dreams about it...
but thinking it was real because
he was avoiding his medication.
Was it worth it?
Was it worth you
hiding it from me?
What did you think
you were hiding? This?
That you had a husband
who lynched people.
What good did that do?
You don't trust him tiny bit.
So much so that you belive he would do
something to 14 year old girl.
And you even asked him.
Mum!
Why?
Why have you become
the woman you are?
Why have such a life?
I don't know any other life.
All I knew "Stand on your own feet,
be independent, be strong..."
you are an orphan".
"You have a deceased husband".
"And a little girl in your arms".
Don't ever fall.
But how can you not?
You are young, working...
trying to make a living.
But you are not a man.
You are a woman.
Wish you knew how you used to look at
me when I held you in my arms.
I was frightened
of this world Nevra.
You have to hold on to a man.
While trying to find the right one...
I myself became a man.
I turned into a man.
When you asked me...
why I hid it from you...
I was afraid to be left
on my own...
if they took Selim away.
I was scared of being on my own.
I always took cover behind men.
In order to avoid being alone and
being labelled "whore".
But you weren't alone.
You had me.
And you still have.
Why were you so scared?
My little darling...
why do you think Reyhan
took her own life?
F... ck!
- Nükhet, hi.
- Hi.
Did you have a nice sleep?
Having a rest for about an hour
was refreshing.
Let's go and have a nice dinner.
There must be so many
things to see here.
Have you ever been
around this way?
No, never.
Look, such an interesting
name for a town, Kambura.
Why give such a strange name
to the place you live?
Maybe, it was others
who named it.
Very interesting.
I feel sorry for the residents.
Yes, yes.
Finally, I got hold of you.
The meeting has
only just finished.
How is Ankara? Still hot
and dry in the summer?
It certainly is.
What is the situation?
Did you find anything?
I digged into the ministries.
But no avail.
You will have to cough up
some dosh.
No dosh, I told you
it is a favour.
You say favour but asking for the most
precious item in the black market.
I have asked million and one people.
Nobody knows anything.
We have to go in reverse order.
What do you mean?
We'll get in touch with the key people
through our contacts.
Then we'll make them talk.
We are not going to ask
who is messing with your case.
We'll do the opposite.
We'll bait them with
a lot of names...
who supposedly interfering
with the case.
We'll cast the line and wait.
- Wait for what?
- For bureaucratic ego to take over.
Because whoever is pulling the strings
or acting like a middle man...
will get beaten by his ego
and begin to talk.
He will say
"f... ck off, I am the one".
This is a long shot.
These people are not stupid.
They are stupid.
The only thing that sets those
who wear the same style of suit...
apart from one another is to brag
about whose back you are scratching.
You must get
really bored in Ankara.
It's because it's hot and dry here
in the summer.
You haven't eaten anything.
I am not hungry mum.
What are you doing?
Trying to figure out
when everything started and...
in what order it progressed.
Nevra!
Have you ever heard a man
called Cemil Havran?
Yes. I even talked to him
on the phone the other day.
He sent his regards to you.
I never got around to tell you,
thinking they may harm Selim.
Are you still hiding
something mum?
Isn't that enough of secrets?
I am not hiding a secret or anything.
I am telling you now.
Cemil almost owns
whole of Kambura.
Nothing ever takes place
without his knowledge.
I think you'd better talk to him.
Was he the one who
threatened Uncle Selim?
He wouldn't do it himself. He would
get his monkeys do it instead.
You know Vural, the guy
who's been hanging around.
Vural.
Apparently he warned Selim
not to talk about the fire.
I see.
It means we have to turn
Kambura on its head.
Don't worry, I'll talk to him.
Mum...
we came here in 1993, didn't we?
Stayed here for a year.
1994.
I think it was August.
Left in August.
Reyhan had a notebook.
If it is as precious as to be
hidden under a pillow...
it was more likely a diary.
Where is that diary now?
If these notes were taken
by Reyhan...
the killer has the diary.
Let's assume that she wrote this
on my birthday.
March 18th.
Nevra...
has Reyhan given you
a birthday present?
I don't remember.
[It's Nevra's birthday today]
[I got her a present].
- When I set out to write this book...
- Life is Traffic.
I did a lot of research on accidents.
- Here you are sir.
- Good.
Go on, open it.
It may cause a problem.
The guy himself is the problem.
And I am here to solve it.
By the way, he won't know about this.
Am I clear?
Yes sir.
There was an incident.
I never forget it.
Do you remember the TV show...
the contest...
where contestants gather around a car
and place their hands on it.
Yes, I remember it. They used to
spend days in that position.
A man spent 37 hours
with his hand on the car.
He places his hand on the car
and just stands there.
He was the one
who lasted the longest.
So, he wins the car.
He takes the car away...
and on his very first day on the road
he gets involved in a horrific accident.
A truck hits the car
on the driver's side.
That is really bad.
And there is more.
Do you know what happens?
He loses his right hand, the one he used
to touch the car for 37 hours.
Do you think it has a meaning?
And if there is a meaning,
what is it?
Where is that guy now?
They were talking about
having dinner.
There is only one place to eat around
here which is at the end of the road.
O.K, fine. Thanks.
I met a girl today.
Her name is Nevra Elmas.
She is the only one I trust.
Because Nevra understands me.
It's Nevra's birthday today.
I got her a present.
Me and Nevra share a secret.
Did you really kiss?
You promised not to tell anyone.
Of course we kissed.
Swear to God?
You don't believe anything.
I told you so many times.
I told Nevra everything.
But she doesn't believe me.
I don't eat fruit.
Because when the sugar in fruit
gets in reaction with alcohol...
it turns into fat.
Move your hand.
Reyhan.
Who remembers?
Tayyar!
Tayyar remembers you.
He said "they wasted
the poor girl".
If Tayyar remembers
so do the others.
All of them, they all remember.
Whole of Kambura remembers.
They just pretend
that they don't.
Who am I speaking to?
Not to your friend in Ankara.
That's for sure.
I don't think you should
speak to him again either.
Save his a..ss
and save your own.
Stick to what you know.
Write 3rd page articles.
Because as you turn the pages
in a newspaper...
you come to the pages
with political issues...
and that's where
the scenery changes.
You may end up being locked up.
And when it comes to trying
to prove your innocence...
the trial would last
at least a year.
Have mercy on yourself.
O.K?
Don't get yourself mixed up with
complicated businesses.
Because next time that phone rings,
it won't be for a warning.
We can leave if you're ready.
This way.
What is it?
Police. Don't touch anything.
O.K.
We used to drink wine too.
But the cheapest one.
It was called the "dog killer".
Have you heard of it?
Do you know what was
written on the label?
In vino veritas.
We used to wonder what it meant.
What does it mean?
The truth is hidden in the wine.
- Leave me alone.
- Come on.
- B... stards!
Leave me alone.
I can find my own way.
F... cking gypsy!
He's got such a big mouth.
He thinks he can
take over the place.
I know you don't like gypsies.
I f..cking hate them.
My dad says they should
f... ck off somewhere else.
But saying is not enough Ufuk.
Look how he forces
himself on us.
Best thing to do is set his bed alight.
Let the b... stard burn to ashes.
He is a walking alcohol bottle.
Just one spark would be enough
to blow him up.
But we need a hero
to do the deed.
Look around you.
Everybody is sitting all quiet,
tails between their legs.
He might've as well
spat on their faces.
We need someone to sort him out.
I'll do it.
I swear I can do it.
I will burn that gypsy so bad they
will ever dare to return to Kambura.
Now, this is the man talking.
Come on, bottoms up.
Why are you calling me?
What do you want from me
in the middle of the night?
Yes, Deva told me.
O.K, just send the divorce papers.
I will sign them.
What do you mean
you changed your mind?
How can you?
Do you think this is a game?
No, I don't want you
to come to Turkey.
I have nothing to say to you.
The marriage is over.
There is nothing between us.
Don't ever call me again.
Who was it, calling
this time at night?
Deva.
He was looking for something
but couldn't find it.
Called to ask me.
I don't think he found it.
I'll be right back.
- Thank you very much Nükhet.
- What for?
I haven't felt this
peaceful for ages.
And you are the reason.
I feel like I am going
to live forever.
I feel like me and you will be sitting
here, watching the stars forever.
As if it will never end.
It will not end Agah.
We will relive tonight
every time we think about it.
Under the stars.
As long as we remember.
That's what the poet said.
Life is a memory.
You'll die when you forget.
So true. Who said it?
I forgot.
I washed him.
Sure I washed him.
I washed Tufan.
They can't find any evidence.
I remembered. See?
You dirty crooks. I washed him.
Well, now that I am awake...!
It's not here.
How could you forget it?
Wait here. I'll be right back.
- Where have you been?
- I am here aren't I?
Did you tell your dad
that we are going to get married?
No, I didn't have the chance.
But I have something else to tell you.
Remember I told you I have a brother?
Cemil.
Yes, that's the one.
He said "now that Reyhan kissed you,
would she kiss me too".
What are you talking about?
Wait.
He said he will tell everybody,
people will be calling you names...
and we won't be able
to get married.
Hello Reyhan.
How are you?
What's going on here
so early in the morning?
[Do you remember me?