All of you, write down the homework you have to do.
Problem number 32 to 38 on the sheet.
And? - And?
And that's it. - That's it?
Bhaiya we have five days off.
Give us some more. We will do it.
Yes, I know. That's why I am not giving you more.
These five days are for the school's practical.
All of you will focus on that and relax. Okay?
Relax?
Yes. And your reshuffling exams will be held in 15 days of returning.
13 days, sir. 13 days. - Listen. 13 days.
Then you have to study like a lunatic then.
Charge your battery a little.
You won't burn out if you relax a little along with your studies.
But all of you will focus on school.
Uday, what's on your mind? - Sir.
That doesn't mean all of you laze completely. Just sleeping.
Chill a little.
How many of you will be going to school for the first tomorrow?
Put your hands up.
Bravo! This is the cream of our country.
Very good!
Superb handwriting!
The lab report is written in cursive.
Value for money.
They have given 8.2 as the value for g. Shouldn't it be 9.8?
Ignorant chap!
If you get 9.8 as the value of g in the lab.. - Yes.
Then you have certainly cheated, bro.
8.2 seems more realistic.
Even the A1 batch buys lab reports from him.
It cost me 700 rupees to save 8 hours.
No. 300 rupees. 400 rupees was for the scooty rental.
Are you going to charge me just because I used your scooty for 2 days?
No, no. Not mine. The other one that I have rented.
Only 400 rupees for 4 days. Isn't it great deal?
Shivangi says I am not organized.
Wait and watch.
What other one?
And for whom? It cost me 400 rupees?!
You expect the four of us to sit one on top of the other?
I am so sly. I've already filled petrol in the scooty.
What four people? - You, me, Shivangi and Vartika.
Vartika who? - Ratawal.
Ratawal who? - Shivangi's friend.
What are you saying, bro? Quiet. Tell me calmly.
What are you saying?
Should I remain quiet or should I tell you?
Look. We have a 4 day break.
No coaching. No homework.
We will go on an excursion.
I rented a scooty so that the four of us..
..you, me, Shivangi and her friend Vartika Ratawal can sight see Kota.
Isn't that cool?
I am not going anywhere. We have a 4 day break.
Vaibhav and I will revise.
What will you do? - Study.
No, no. Don't do it.
Jeetu Bhaiya said to relax, so you should relax.
Oh, yes.
Do you also pay heed to everything the teachers say?
Is there another possibility?
Your thoughts are so pure. Just like mine.
I can't go, buddy. - Like hell!
I filled 400 rupees worth of petrol in the scooty.
I paid 500 rupees to rent it. Now you're telling me you won't go.
Look, bro. Meena and I want to complete the whole syllabus..
..during these 4 days.
You always do this, buddy.
You ruined the Dussehra fair plans the same way.
One moment.
I wasn't here at the time of the Dussehra fair.
Exactly. You weren't here then and you aren't now either.
Bro. Shivangi has been avoiding me for a long time.
I hope she doesn't break up with me.
She isn't even mean enough to wait for another boy to enter her life..
..before she breaks up with me.
Within four days I want to go everywhere from Troika to Talap..
..seven wonders to C V garden,
from Radha Krishna to standing Ganeshji
..so that we create so many memories here in Kota..
..even the thought of breaking up would torment her heart.
Basic romantic consumerism, buddy.
So, you go, bro.
Why are you making me the third wheel?
Some things can't be done without a third wheel, bro.
She will come if all of us go out. She won't come alone.
But our revision, bro.
Yes, that's what I was saying. ??
Due to some unavoidable circumstances we won't be able to revise. - I am talking.
What? What? What?
We have to complete the whole syllabus in 4 days.
I want to relax. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
Take me with you, Uday.
You won't retract, will you? Promise me.
No.
Meena?
I think even I should go.
Of course. Come along.
Right? Thank you. - Next year.
For the Dussehra fair.
You go. I shall study.
Take this. A Vernier caliper for you.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Exactly what you told me to do. Relax.
Is the coaching going well? - Very good, sir.
It must be.
You don't have time to write your own lab report.
No, sir. - I can tolerate the value of g up to 7.
But I cannot tolerate lies.
You coaching students don't respect school.
You have come to school for the first time, haven't you? - No, sir.
I came. - You're lying again.
No, sir. I came several times.
How much do puffs cost in the canteen?
You think I am an idiot? I can tell by looking at the handwriting..
..the chap at the Xerox center has written it.
This is Gupta's handwriting.
You are from Prodigy, aren't you? - Yes, sir.
You can't be from Maheshwari.
Tell Deepak I wish to see him.
If he doesn't come to see me by tomorrow..
..I will fail all the Prodigy students.
Then you can keep trying for the JEE advance.
You understand? - Yes, sir.
Next.
Vartika Ratawal.
Meena. I will go with Uday.
What about me relaxing? - You relax at home.
Where are they going?
To sightsee all of Kota, inside out.
That is such a nice plan.
Vaibhav, you hop on Uday's vehicle and you come with me.
Excuse me. Hello, friends.
Can I go with all of you to explore Kota?
You are? - Meenal Parekh.
(fake coughs) Nerd Alert (fake coughs) Get rid of her.
Hello. - Hi.
You're most welcome, but we are already four.
How can five of us go? - Six.
Now that everyone is going I shall go too.
Hi. I'm Vaibhav. - Vartika.
Shiv, why don't you all leave? I'll take a rain check.
So we'll buy pads on the way. - No, no. I have some.
No. No. This is not about periods.
I received Maheshwari's sample papers..
..and I couldn't solve any of it.
So, I should stay back and prepare for it.
I made the entire plan for you. - Yes.
You're ditching us? - Sorry.
Oh! With these boring people..
..I will get bored. - She's joking.
We are not boring. - Yes, yes.
We are very intelligent.
These problems will be solved in 30 minutes. - Yes.
Very easy.
By them. - Yes, yes. I'll help her solve it.
No worries, guys.
Shivangi, please. - No. Vartika, this is not done.
Please. - Please, Shivangi. Please.
Okay. Go ahead and study.
Well, alright. Then I won't go either.
Why?
How many times will you change your mind for one plan?
We aren't going to Goa.
I will help her study. It will be a help to her.
In any case you are a group of four.
She will study and get help. Meena will do it.
No, no. I shall go out. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
It is okay, Uday. I shall make the sacrifice this time.
It's fine. - No, no, Vaibhav. You come too.
You will burn out if you don't relax. Come.
We will adjust. Come.
No, no. You go. You guys carry on.
It's okay, buddy.
One spot is available now, right?
Yeah! Thanks.
You're sure you won't come?
You will miss a lot.
Hold this Meena.
Let's go.
Bye, you guys. - Bye.
Don't be tense. We will do the paper.
Just relax.
Thanks.
I'm Vartika. - Ratawal. I know. I know.
Sorry. You introduced yourself earlier.
Okay.
Sorry. Actually I didn't hear your name earlier.
That's why I introduced myself again hoping you would repeat your name.
So, your name? - Vaibhav. Vaibhav Ratawal.
Oh, sorry. How can I be Ratawal? Vaibhav Pandey.
It was a little awkward, wasn't it?
But don't worry.
We will solve the paper. - Okay.
You.. Sorry. Just relax. - No, no. Thank you.
Shall we?
What irony! The cold coffee is the most famous dish at Chai paani.
One cold coffee.
Two.
Shivangi, you are in Medical, aren't you?
I too wanted to be a doctor when I was young but..
But what?
But when I grew up I turned out to be pretty emotional.
My dad said doctors can't be so emotional..
..so, I chose engineering.
You too are emotional? - Yes.
Look at this question. - Yes. Question.
Firstly, you shouldn't see the question.
what?
Jeetu Bhaiya says to check the last line of the question first.
Then one should check the options.
For example, it says here what will the temperature of the vessel be?
Look at the options.
The temperature can't be calculated in joules, moles or calories.
So, D 25 celcius is the correct answer.
This wasn't a thermo question at all.
It was a common sense question.
Oh, yes! Actually I did not pay attention.
By the way, is your brother also in IIT?
No, no. Brother is a Compounder.
What?
Jeetu Bhaiya. Jeetu Bhaiya is in IIT. - I see.
He teaches at Prodigy. - Okay.
Yes.
I too should have joined classes at the beginning.
Everything is in a mess now.
Don't worry.
I'll convert your mess into reasons.
Good reasons.
Okay.
Shall we do the next? - Yes.
Read the last line.
Stay in your limits.
This is such a good family atmosphere, isn't it? - Yes.
Next time I shall bring my parents here. - Yes.
Uday!
You think it is proper to leave the two of them alone?
You're afraid of Meena?
I am afraid for Meena.
You're sure?
The entire year is about to end but I still don't know your whole name.
Meena, what is your surname?
My surname is Meena. My name is Balmukund Meena.
Everybody endearingly calls me Meena.
What are you called endearingly? - Jhamkudi.
Jhamkudi. It's a nice name. - Isn't it?
Yes.
Meenal is so straight and simple.
I bet she doesn't play the knight in chess.
Isn't that true?
Incidentally Meena and Meenal would make a nice pair, wouldn't they?
Meena, Meenal. Meenal, Meena.
Ladies first.
Thanks, Vaibhav. - For?
You helped me solve all three papers. - Yes.
I got through it all in one day.
I would have taken seven days to get through it.
That's right. We got through it all in one day.
Yes, that is true. - Nothing is left for the remaining days.
No, no. I have something left.
I shall revise the whole syllabus.
Good.
Okay. Let me know if you have any problem.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Incidentally, I could help you with your revision. Yes!
I could help you with your revision.
I am very talented. I can help anyone memorize anything.
Shall I remind you of your position?
Uday, bro I can't go out.
I have to study. I have my reshuffling exam. Non sense!
Yes, well. I didn't go out. I was studying.
You weren't studying, scoundrel.
You were clinging.
Onto her.
Listen. You sat up to teach her today, didn't you?
Teach her in a sleeping position tomorrow. - Shut up! Scoundrel!
It is the truth. Isn't that right, Meena?
What's the matter with him?
Has your Deepak lost his mind?
Doesn't he want to run the coaching classes anymore?
I told him to come and see you.
You told him? - Yes.
Well, alright.
What did you tell him my name is?
Vice-Principal Mehta sir.
Modern heart. - I see. That's you.
You go. I will deal with him.
Next!
Vartika Ratawal.
"I said it."
"You said it."
"That's all it is."
"I endured it."
"You endured it."
"But not anymore."
Bye, guys. See you.
I don't feel right about this.
Why? Didn't you enjoy?
I can teach you even better. I can even crack jokes if you like.
What? No, that's not what I meant.
You wanted to go out with them and I kept you here.
Oh! No. No. No.
It's not that.
Even I wanted to do my revision.
Even I have to sit for Maheshwari's exam.
Even you have to sit for it? - Yes, really.
Why would I lie?
When did I say you were lying? - Yes.
Yes, exactly. Exactly.
Crap!
If that's the case, then it's okay. We could study together.
Yes, we can. It's a good idea. It's possible.
By the way, which center did you get?
I haven't got it as yet.
I will get it. I will get it when I fill the form.
You haven't filled the form as yet? - No.
Today is the last date.
What?
Don't take off your jackets.
The uniform should not be visible.
I will place the order. You sit tight.
Don't say a word.
No matter what, never show your I-card.
If anyone asks for your ID, tell them proudly.
I don't have it. - I don't have it.
I don't have it, uncle.
Sir, you have to present an ID to sit here.
Why do I have to present it? - So we know your age.
So, ask me my age.
Seventeen.
Lights were so amazing inside, weren't they? - Reflection.
I told you in the first place. Let's go to Talap..
..but you don't want to pay heed to me.
Baby, they demand IDs even over there.
They must be demanding them from others, not from the staff.
Meena, give me a marker. - Yes.
Back.
Thank you, ma'am. - Never mind that.
Fill the form and return it quickly.
You too are a Virgo? - Yes.
You too? - No. My boyfriend was.
Oh!
You don't have a boyfriend now? - No, we broke up.
Good. Good.
Why did you break up? - He never studies.
That is wrong. That is very wrong.
I study a lot. I love studies.
I mean to say, not all Virgos are the same. Right?
Some Virgos are hard-working. Some are compassionate.
Some are lovers.
Friendly lovers. Friendly lovers.
It's wrong to stereotype. It's wrong to stereotype.
What do you think, sister? - Fill the form and return it quickly.
Your love for the girl made you study and you even taught her.
Now you went and filled Maheshwari's form too?
Love is blind, bro, not insane.
Right, Meena?
Where have you been taking him every day?
I guess I will see you again next year.
No, no. Sir..
..I shall come for the final exam.
You will come? - Certainly.
Certainly? - Certainly
Promise?
Promise.
Go there.
Next.
Vartika.
Vartika Ratawal.
"Like a dream."
"Like heaven."
"This world used to be."
"Look, now it's burning."
"And you ask me."
"Why I am upset?"
Your house is very nice. - Thank you.
Sometimes I feel like shifting here.
Huh? - For studies.
Ladies first.
Hey, boy! - Who is it?
Up. Up.
Greetings, uncle. - Yes, yes. Okay, okay.
You cannot come in.
Why? - This PG is for girls.
I allowed you yesterday.
I thought you must be her brother. - Uncle!
I am not her brother. - That's why I say, out!
Uncle, you are confusing me for her boyfriend, aren't you?
No. Close friend. - Go! Get out of here!
What kind of an uncle is he? He is publicly calling me brother.
Your brother will be offended. - Come on! Get going!
Whoo!
One moment. Don't come inside. Please. Please.
Your aunty won't have a problem here, will she?
No, no. What problem would aunty have?
Uday brings Shivangi here every day.
I have brought a girl with me for the first time. - What?
I mean friend. Friend. - Yes.
You are needlessly worrying. Let me come in.
No! No! No! No! Don't come in. Two minutes. Please.
I have seen dirtier rooms.
You shower every day, right? That will suffice.
Ta-dah!
Please.
Yes. So, we shall study gravitation today.
Gravitation.
Gravitation is such a nice thing.
Gravitation has a beautiful fragrance.
The attraction of two unknown bodies for each other.
Living their lives around each other.
Round and round.
Vaibhav.
Can we ditch gravitation?
Why? - I am very weak with SHM.
So, can we do that first?
Yes, yes. I know it. Why wouldn't I know SHM?
SHM is very easy.
I know it. - But when did I say you don't know SHM?
Exactly. Exactly. You didn't say that. You didn't say that.
SHM.
Oh, crap! Oh, no! It's time for my exercise.
Oh, crap! Crap!
I don't care what you were doing. How could you not answer my call?
Firstly, you don't study. You just wander off anywhere.
Baby, don't yell. Someone will hear you.
Why shouldn't I yell?
Because I will mend my ways. I will change.
I will study too. In fact, I am studying.
Force. Vector. Equilibrium. Irrational. Compound. Complex.
Hello.
Bro, you know I'm out with Shivangi, don't you?
Then why are you calling me now? You spoiled a romantic moment.
I'm sorry, buddy. Vartika has come. - Oh!
Condoms are kept in H.C.Verma, part 2, the semi-conductors.
What are you saying?
I want the login password for Unacademy.
'You won't be able to do it, boy.' - I don't want to do it either.
We are just friends, okay.
Its the password. All small.
He's a true IITian.
Why?
He'll die a virgin.
My dear students, let's have a look at the spring block system today.
This is the block. This is the spring. If I elongate the spring by..
Vaibhav! - Yes, I'm coming. Last two.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
This is very useful at the last minute.
Thank you, bro.
We did it all.
The exam is tomorrow and I am not afraid.
I mean, not that much.
I just have to read the doomsday notes and I'm done.
What notes? - Doomsday.
Hold on.
These. For last minute revision.
It contains the overview of each chapter.
Oh! I too have made this. Wait. I'll show you.
All the topics and time.
You can watch it on the Unacademy app from and to any chapter.
Don't you lose data if you check it all the time? - No.
I download it offline. - Oh, I see.
You've filled up such a big register. Seriously? - Yes.
Why are you so tense for Maheshwari's entrance test?
Because it is tough.
Yes, that it is, but we have covered everything.
What's the matter?
Actually
my brother was in Maheshwari's top batch.
Oh! - So, I felt at least if I make it to Maheshwari..
..I will gain confidence that I can get to IIT..
..but I did not feel I had any chance.
You know I've learned more in these 4 days than I did through the year.
I had starting feeling like an idiot.
Thanks for restoring my confidence.
Why didn't you come to Kota earlier?
We would've become friends earlier.
Yes.
What can I say?
It's okay if you don't tell us, but make sure you tell her.
Once the exam gets over tomorrow, Lord knows when you'll see her again.
The mood is set, bro. Propose to her.
Listen. Tomorrow is an auspicious day, right? Take this.
Go in style.
"Like a dream."
"Like heaven."
"This world used to be."
"Look, now its burning."
"And you ask me."
"Why I am upset?"
"Things won't work your way anymore."
"Say it."
"Now and here."
"Long live love."
Bhaiya, you have yogurt? - Yes, you can have yogurt.
Take it from there.
And...
Sugar? - We have sugar too. There you go, bhaiya.
How much? - Thirty rupees, bhaiya. 30.
Thank you.
What is this?
Today is an auspicious day.
So, this is auspicious. - Oh, okay.
If you eat yogurt your nervousness will disappear.
You eat it too. You too are sitting for the exam.
Yes, oh! I too am sitting for the exam.
What do we do with this now? - I don't know.
Let's apply it on our hair.
It will make the hair lustrous. - Gross!
I'm joking.
Didn't I tell you, I'm not that boring? - Yeah.
Let's finish it. - Yeah.
"Long live love!"
"It is written..
..in red ink."
"My motives are rebellious."
"Look, now it's burning."
"And you ask me."
"Why I am upset?"
"Things won't work your way anymore."
"Say it."
"Now and here."
"Long live love."
"Long live love!"
"My dreams..
..have united with dreams. Know that."
"My motives..
..have united with motives. Know that."
"Long live love!"
Not IIT. I will sit for the SATs. I want to go to US.
Cornell, Yale, Harvard, Columbia. One of these.
What?
My uncle is over there. He told me to come.
Then why are you working so hard over here?
For knowledge. Knowledge doesn't get wasted.
Uday, take me with you.
Nobody in this world stays put in one place.
What's the matter?
I'm already eager for the results. - Yes.
It will take two weeks though. - Yes.
Okay, then. Bye.
Bye.
See you.
Vartika. - Yes.
Yes.
Vartika you... you will go to bed early, won't you?
Peacefully. - Yes.
You too.
Yes. Me too.
Okay, then. Goodnight. - Goodnight.
Stay in touch. - Yes.
Crap!
Vaibhav! - Vartika.
Can we begin the syllabus for the 12th?
Yes, we could do that.
Tomorrow. - Tomorrow.
Cool.
Goodnight. - Goodnight.
Bye.
"I said, hey."
"If she agrees."
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
"I will float into dreams."
"Stop me."
"I said, hey."
"If she agrees to meet ..
and spends a few moments."
"I'll express my feelings."
"Please stop me."
"Oh please stop me."
"But please don't stop us..
..when we are lost in this manner..
..in our small world."
"Why would you stop us?"
Sometimes in our busy lives we find love, love leaves us.
or holds on forever.
This romantic track to touch your hearts.
The seven wonders that are made in Kota are less.
You are the eighth wonder, my love.
Bye.
Love you. Miss you. Take care.
This will last another six months.
Buddy, I should have studied.
A lot of time was wasted because I wanted to relax.
Even studies can be very relaxing, bro.
You just need the right partner.
"Can you imagine..
..when we are lost..
..in the stars."
"How would you find us?"
"I said, hey."
"If she agrees."
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
"I will float into dreams."
"Stop me."