Remember the "Personality".
No murder, O.K?
Let's pray.
- Dad?
- Zuhal?
- Did you know Mr.Tayfun?
- Of Course I did.
All the way from Kambura.
Sorry for your loss.
Be brave son.
You can't escape fate.
What fate?
They blew up the flower man.
As founders of the "Dog Killer" Fan Club
we officially welcome you.
If you don't make an arrest
within a week, it's over.
The girl whom Tayyar raped...
she is talking to me.
Look what she's saying.
Help me Nevra.
Up until now,
I have been her voice.
All these murders are
for her revenge.
If we find her
we find this one too.
We have to go to
Kambura immediately.
Ladies, anyone who was
raped or sexually abused...
please call this number.
What do you mean by
"they gathered the women"?
She is trying to find the girl
who was raped by Tayyar.
O.K, just stand by.
I'll think of something.
They checked out
the burned house.
Find a bulldozer immediately.
And knock it down.
- I don't recognize the number.
- Go on, answer it.
Hello?
Just tell me everything
from the beginning.
It was an ordinary day. I had just
finished my grocery shopping.
As I left the shop
Tayyar appeared out of nowhere.
He grabbed me and...
you know, in the woods.
She remembers everything.
Just call me if
you need anything.
Thank you very much.
You don't need to hang around.
Firuz...
the less you know, the better
you can sleep at night.
Then you won't
have to call me...
or say "leave me alone".
Do you think Nevra
was convinced?
Absolutely.
She was about to start crying,
thanks to my story-telling skill.
By the way, I talked to Cemil.
He said you have the rest of my money.
Yes, that's right.
- S..it!
- What is it?
So much for been convinced.
She is following us.
- Where?
- Don't turn around.
What are we going to do now?
S..it!
What am I going to do now?
What now?
Think. Where is your home?
Think, think, think.
Where is your house?
No, it's not going to work.
Mrs Feza!
Let's go.
Come on, get up. Let's go.
Get up. I don't know where
but we should go.
Here you go.
My bag...
anything else?
O.K, this way Mrs Feza.
Here you go.
Is she still following you?
Keep going Firuz.
Don't get out the car
until I think of something, O.K?
Mrs Feza!
I've read thousands of novels and
I decided to write one myself.
And you two f..cked it up.
Listen to me now.
I am listening Mr.Cemil.
- Can you hear me Yeliz?
- Yes, I can.
I made some calls.
We'll change the story a little.
What I'm about to say,
get it into your heads.
Smallest mistake,
you're done with.
Hello?
Are you serious?
Yeliz met with Firuz?
There must be a mistake.
No mistake.
They are right ahead of me.
It is obvious that they know each other.
He is driving her somewhere.
O.K. Hang on a minute.
Just calm down.
Do you mean Yeliz was
bulls... tting you last night?
And now, she is with Firuz, right?
Yes, that's exactly so.
I have to talk to Firuz to find out
what's been happening.
Just hang up.
Don't call him now Sefer.
I have to see where they are headed.
Listen to me.
No one knows Firuz better than I do.
If there is something iffy going on,
either he won't answer...
or give me a lot of crap.
I have to call Firuz to find out.
- Hang on a minute.
- What?
Are you going to tell him that
I've been following him?
If I know Firuz well enough, he already
figured out that he's being followed.
No, it is not here either.
I made a note of everything.
Even, chucking the TV set out.
But no address.
I am so stupid.
Poor Agah.
Not in the wallet either.
But it should be
on the car's log book.
Yes, it should be
on the log book.
Calm down Agah.
Take a deep breath.
Thank you.
Mrs. Feza, I don't remember
where I live.
I don't remember my home.
What the hell is going on?
Keep doing whatever
you've been doing.
Excuse me?
Keep following me.
I called Sefa. He is on his way.
We have to sit down and talk.
Everything should be here.
I make a note of everything
in this black book.
It says here "Combination for the
Flat No 8 is 1682".
But what is Flat No:8?
Where the hell is it?
How the hell do I know?
Why didn't I write down
the address instead of the combination?
Such an idiot!
Unfortunately, this is the situation
we are in right now.
I don't remember.
There must be a reason
why I forgot.
I'll take you to seaside.
I can play flamenco for you.
- Ol茅!
- Yes, sure, Ol茅.
Remember when you asked me
how the idea came up?
When you said why should others
decide who is to be killed?
Do you know why?
Because they've always been
the ones to decide.
Come over here.
Gerome painted this in 1872.
What are those people doing?
That's what the painting is called.
"Pollice Verso".
It means "thumbs down".
And who is it for?
For the gladiator.
Why? So he can kill this man.
Actually, it is not clear which one means
"death" in ancient Rome.
This, or this.
But Gerome thought
this was the fitting one.
If you do this,
the gladiator will kill.
And there would be
death in the Arena.
If you do this
you save the man's life.
But one is not enough.
The decision has to be unanimous.
What I mean is, who will die or live
has to be decided unanimously.
Unanimous decisions are always
deemed legitimate.
It will take the
guilty conscience away.
At the end of the day,
you are inciting to a murder.
It is a crime.
But this way, everybody can point
the finger at each other.
And the crime disappears.
What this painting tells us that...
if you want to commit a crime
and not get blamed...
all you have to do is to
build a crowd around you.
It is no longer a crime, if you commit it
with a large enough crowd.
And...
do these remind you anything?
Well...
you upload a video on YouTube.
What happens is that it is judged by
people you don't even know.
Like...
and dislike.
Life...
or death.
As you can see, nothing has changed
in 2 thousand years S眉veyda.
Only difference is that
you can't do this anymore.
You have to click on the icons.
I thought of it
when I saw the painting.
We have the gladiator, so let the
crowd decide who'll die.
- Did you hear it?
- What?
The three man who were killed?
The ones with the word "personal"
carved on their forehead?
They were on the list
in our website.
- Are you serious?
- Why don't you check it out?
Switch on the computer S眉veyda.
I found out at school.
They just told me.
One of them was running
a food kiosk or something.
He says "they are extorting money from
me. I hope the "Dog Killer" kill them all".
They issued the names too.
Only a day before the murders.
And people went wild.
Everybody is loading names on the list.
You know what this means
don't you?
"Dog Killer" is following
our website.
Alright then. What were you doing
there? How do you know this woman?
No rush. There is a time for everything.
Wait till Sefa gets here.
Here he is.
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
Put it this way, I have to do
the s... itty work...
because you have been
so f..cking useless.
- What are you talking about?
- Murders are piling up every day.
And your brains are messed up
with Kambura.
We are not getting anywhere.
They are going mad in Ankara.
And I have to take all the s... it.
Remember coming to the hospital
yesterday?
They called me straight after
you left.
- Who are "they"?
- Ones at the top in Ankara.
They said "there is something iffy
going on over there. Dig into it".
I said "you want me to investigate
my partners"?
They said "exactly".
Yes sir.
- Does boss know about it?
- They probably told him.
I'll go and talk to him anyway.
I have been a superintendent for years.
I am not going to spy on my team.
They told Chief Tolga,
gave him a week.
If he can't solve it
they'll show him the door.
Yes sir, I understand sir.
Yes, you've told me sir.
But I think it is unnecessary.
No.
Because I trust my team sir.
O.K.
I understand.
So, what is it?
Do they suspect us?
Thanks.
Don't pretend that
you don't already know Sefa.
They are just pulling
the wool over eyes.
They will want to justify their action
when the case blows bigger...
in couple of days.
They'll say
"we investigated the cops."
Everybody is trying to
save their own a..ss.
It is all about saving your skin.
That's what it is.
Nothing beats the seaside.
Nothing can beat it.
It must've been 50 years
since I last flew a kite.
50 years at least.
I have to run to fly it.
But how can I run?
I'll be back in a minute.
Wait here.
Let me ask you something?
How did you figure it out?
I mean, how did you figure out that
I was going to meet the woman?
I didn't figure out that
you were going to meet.
I only figured out that
she was lying.
But everything she told me
made sense.
That's right, it all made sense.
Except one thing.
No man in Kambura
would marry a non-virgin.
It doesn't matter
how much he loves her.
It is against Kambura's customs.
That's why, the woman in question
either never got raped nor she is married.
But since we knew she was married,
I decided to follow her...
to find out where she was going and
who was forcing her to lie.
That's when you
came into the scene.
You're doing good.
May be not so good.
But you'll do it.
- I can't do it.
- You can do it.
I'll tell you what,
let's try 10 more times and...
we'll quit if it doesn't
work out.
Go on. This is the first.
We start with the first one.
Mrs. Feza.
Come on.
It's O.K.
Let's go for the second.
Come on son.
Well done.
No, this way.
Faster.
Three.
For the forth time.
Lie? Why should I lie to you?
If you don't believe me
ask my husband.
Ask him if I was virgin
when we got married.
It's O.K Nevra.
That's enough. We'll drop you off
wherever you want to go.
What sort of a woman are you,
making me talk about such things?
How can you do this to your own kind?
Have you got no feelings?
What did your mum used to
say to you Yeliz?
What do you mean? What's that
got to do with anything?
What did your mum used to
say to you when you were little?
How was she threatening you?
Wasn't she saying "do you want to
become a whore"?
"You'll end up becoming
a whore".
Isn't that what she was saying?
What's that got to do
with anything?
That's what she used say,
wasn't it?
Do you know why? Because your mum
knew exactly what Kambura was like.
You know too.
If you are looking for a wrong doing,
it is the Kambura itself.
Look mister, it is flying.
It may even be so that...
you're telling the truth Yeliz.
You really have been raped.
Yes, why not?
Yesterday you were talking about
everything in detail.
But you avoided the subject of rape.
Why?
Because you couldn't do it.
You had the guts to lie to us.
But you never had the courage to tell
what happened to you.
You really have been raped Yeliz.
Mrs Feza, it is flying.
We finally did it. It's flying.
Mrs Feza!
It's flying.
And then, you married
the man who raped you.
Why? Because the place called Kambura
never left you with another choice.
That's what happened, isn't it?
Come on, say it.
Isn't that what happened?
That's enough Nevra.
Leave the girl alone.
Because you've got
nothing to say.
It means that it's not
Tayyar who did this to you.
He might've done it to somebody else,
but not to you.
But why are you lying,
blaming him?
Is that what you
want to believe?
Who do you think you're fooling?
Yourself or us?
Do you think your husband will get away
with it if you point the finger at Tayyar?
I'll tell you what, you can blame all
the men in the world...
but it doesn't clear off
your husband.
I am off to Kambura.
Are you coming?
Sure I am.
You can tag along too,
since your job is to spy on us.
Don't bother, we'll meet
you there.
It got stuck.
The kite got stuck.
Mrs Feza...
the kite...
Mrs Feza!
The kite got stuck.
Poor Agah.
That's exactly what you'll become.
Never mind.
- Hello Ate艧.
- Nevra, where are you?
I am off to Kambura.
I was about to ask you
to come to Kambura.
Is that where you are?
I discovered this place
when I first came to Istanbul.
When I was a student.
I became a regular customer.
Do you like it? Nice isn't it?
Yes, it is nice but...
how about the guys?
They are on duty.
I don't like going around
in herds either.
But I am being stalked
by a psychopath. You saw it.
You even saw him better than me.
What am I supposed to do?
Change your routine
until they arrest the man.
I had a routine until that man began
messing with my life.
If you ask me
what paradise is like...
I'd say "it is a place where
every day is the same".
Where nothing changes,
including me...
a place where everything
runs smooth.
As a matter of fact, I built such a place
and lived there.
Now, there is a devil
in my paradise.
Do you want me to close down my
paradise because of him?
And now, there is an
angel there too.
In this case...
Mr Cemil...
is it coincidence that the devil and the
angel made their way into your...
paradise simultaneously?
Or was it fate?
I don't know that much
but I must've left the door open...
allowing both the devil
and the angel in.
This is not the place.
Why did I come here?
This is the place...
where an old friend used to live.
His name is Nazif.
Now he calls himself "Naz".
It's O.K I suppose.
No harm in it.
I once did something here.
They say the killer always
returns to the scene of murder.
So did I.
I was supposed to forget about it.
Wait a minute, your daughter
is not here, is she?
We can go to your place.
There are no cameras there.
The house is empty.
I can play flamenco for you.
Ol茅!
Yes, sure. Ol茅.
- How did you find out?
- I wanted to see the place.
A man hung himself,
causing havoc in the town.
I came to check it out.
And this is the situation.
As you can see, the place
has gone back in time.
There is nothing left. They covered it
with earth, buried it completely.
I wonder who did it?
I found out that too.
Havran Holding.
They bought the land from a farmer
two years ago.
Havran Holding.
They have foundations,
granting scholarship to children.
Cemil Havran is the CEO.
And he is from Kambura.
Cemil.
Yes, we will build a hospital there.
What is your name please?
Nevra Elmas.
Mrs Nesrin's daughter.
Of course I know her.
Where from? Kambura of course.
Do you have any more
questions Miss Nevra?
Yes, I have.
What made you knock this building
down after all these years?
Especially right after...
Yes. Right after a sad incident.
And I knew Ufuk very well.
Sad.
May he rest in peace.
Look Miss Nevra, you can be called a
native of Kambura.
Kambura is a significant
place for me.
A life has vanished there.
We decided to do something that would
pave way for other lives to flourish.
Do you understand?
That's why we decided
to build a hospital.
I tell you what we can do...
make an appointment with me...
we sit down and a have nice chat
over a nice cup of coffee.
By the way, this is
my private number.
You're with the police force.
Therefore you had no problem of
obtaining my number.
But, don't call me on this
number again.
In fact, it is better
if you forget this number.
It is best if you delete it
from your contacts list.
But if it's too much trouble for you,
I get in touch with your bosses...
and they can do it for you.
Is it O.K?
Give my regards to your mother.
Stupid girl.
She's gone into all that trouble
to find your number...
to talk about this.
Let's not say "stupid"...
let's say "enthusiastic".
Young.
Never ran into a wall.
They broke it again.
They broke the lock Mrs Feza.
It is O.K now.
The locksmith had said that
they follow your moves.
They broke in when they realized that
the house was empty.
Isn't that right?
I checked the place. Not much damage.
I don't think they took anything.
The bedroom is a little messy.
But apart from that...!
There is supposed to be a fish there.
I wonder if it's still alive.
Did it have a name?
Did the fish have a name Mrs Feza?
What did you name it?
What would I name it
if it was me?
Agah?
Yes?
You killed Mehmet.
They say Mrs Feza was kidnapped.
I reported it to the police.
They are looking for her.
I told them what happened
to her husband.
They say it probably
has nothing to do with it.
They know nothing.
Cops are useless.
Finally! I have been trying to get
hold of you since morning.
I know dad. I am sorry.
It's been such a hectic day.
I am still busy. But you can talk to me
if it's emergency.
Do you remember the judge,
Mehmet Yurtgil?
His wife Feza was staying here.
They kidnapped her.
Kidnapped? Who? When?
This morning, during the
stroll in the park.
They say she got lost.
But I am sure she was kidnapped...
by her husband's killer.
They reported it to the police.
But the police is not doing anything.
Why would they kidnap her?
She was very ill.
I think they kidnap her to
stop her telling the story.
She may reveal
what she witnessed to.
You can't trust human brain.
You can never know how it works.
Would you take the risk
if you were the murderer?
Moreover, Mrs Feza had begun
to talk recently.
What was she saying?
She was reading poems?
I see.
To the space?
I've got it, dad.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry,
What's going on?
Who kidnapped who?
Feza Yurtgil,
Mehmet Yurtgil's wife.
She suffers from
Alzheimer's Disease.
She's gone missing in the park.
By the way, Naz谋m Hikmet travelled to
space but police didn't know about it.
Let's go.
Unfortunately, we are closed
to the press.
He will find out anyway.
The anonymous tipper among us
will tell him everything.
Now or later,
what is the difference?
You are not the ones
who should be ashamed.
The ones who see you as an item
to be bought and sold...
they are the ones
who should be ashamed.
What did they teach us?
Complete the opposite.
You've got raped
because you've wagged your tail.
You got harassed on the street because
you revealed your body too much.
So many young girls walking
bent-over in Kambura...
to hide their breasts from men.
Are you aware of it?
The hump on children's back...
is our fault.
Mebrule used to hold the cardigan
against my back to measure it.
I am taking over
from she left off.
I wish she was here so I could
knit something for her.
But it is too dark to see in here.
I am sorry Mrs Feza.
We are left in the dark.
But we had to do it to stop others
seeing what's going on inside.
The door can't be locked.
You can't even shut it properly,
let alone locking it.
Mr M眉nir used to hate
the doors too.
Mr M眉nir, my cat.
He hated closed doors.
He used to tap it with his paw,
asking me to open it.
But he was so exhausted
in his final days.
He was unable get up.
He was unable to get up
to even ask for water.
And I never realized.
So intriguing.
This...
look.
Guide to Documentation Sorting.
I have this book too.
This man.
His name is Tayyar Kaymak.
He raped a girl in Kambura sometime
between 10 and 15 years ago.
We don't know how old
she was at the time.
But she is an adult woman now.
Ladies, I am looking
for this woman.
Please come forward if you know
anything about this woman...
about this incident
or about Tayyar Kaymak.
Believe me, the smallest of information
you provide will save a life.
Please, come forward
if you know anything.
Don't hide it.
Don't hide it, so the woman
wouldn't have to hide anymore.
The book has it all.
How to sort documentation.
There are many ways.
One of them is...
by numbering each letter.
For example 1 for A, 2 for B,
3 for C and so on.
And then...
yes, I always sort my documents
this way.
I never forgot.
When you see the number...
1682.
Mrs Feza, 1682.
1 is A.
No, it said "1682 is the combination
for the Flat No:8".
If there is No:8, 1682 refers
to something else.
So, it is not 1, It is 16.
If it's 16...
A, B, C, 脟, D, E...
M.
Mebrule.
You can call me
on this number anytime.
All I want is
to find that woman.
If someone did that to me,
ruining my dignity...
I would commit suicide.
What did you say?
Yes, you.
I said nothing.
Yes, you did. You said if it
happened to you...
I said I would commit suicide.
Wouldn't you?
A man rapes you
and you carry on living?
Who can bear it?
How can you face
your loved ones?
How can you go back home,
to your family?
Mebrule Blocks.
I've got it Mrs Feza.
Flat no: 8.
But what is the "2" at the end?
Mebrule Blocks, flat no: 8.
16, 8, 2, B.
Beyo臒lu.
Agah, Beyo臒lu.
Mebrule Blocks, flat 8, Beyo臒lu.
I've got it.
Mrs Feza, I found the house.
I found the address. Get up.
Get up, we are going home.
Mrs Feza, I've got it. Come on.
Let's go back to the station.
We'll check the archives.
To look for what?
Suicides committed
in the last 15 years...
and we'll go back 20 years
if necessary.
Because the girl
committed suicide.
The girl whom Tayyar
raped committed suicide.
That's why we can't find her.
Because she is no longer alive.
We've got the address.
How could I not remember it?
Just a minute, let me put the book
back in its place.
Yes.
Mrs Feza.
Flamenco?
- Ol茅.
- Sure, Ol茅.
Well, well, well...
the honourable D.A,
I can see you're having a good time.
I am sorry to interrupt
but we have to talk.
How did you know I was here?
How did I know?
I have as many informants
as officers in my team.
They tell me everything.
Where you go, what time
you finish work.
They tell me everything.
What do you want?
Now, the honourable D.A...
who has been messing
with my case and why?
This is number one.
And the number two...
who specifically reinstated the
man to the case...
whom I removed.
Who is running this case?
What's going on?
Look, a little advice from me...
do you know the secret
to move up in the ladder?
Not to ask questions.
F... ck the ladder.
I don't want to move up anywhere.
How about that?
Not moving up means
you are stuck where you are.
And that's where you'll be buried.
Are you threatening me?
No, just talking about a
simple rule of management.
Rule of management. I like that.
For a moment, I thought
you were threatening me.
Because I am allergic to it.
It gives me the itch.
When someone threatens me
I threaten them back.
Now, talking about threats...
does your beautiful and respected wife
know what you are up to here?
You are a good man Tolga.
You wouldn't do such a thing.
You haven't got the evil in you.
That's right.
I haven't got the evil.
But when I walk out that door
anything can happen.
You never know what a man
is capable of doing.
Mankind is an
unpredictable species.
I don't know
who gave the orders.
They called both from Ministry of
Internal Affairs and Ministry of Justice.
They told me what to do
and I agreed.
I swear, I don't know who is
pulling the strings.
You won't say anything
to anyone, will you?
Everybody has a soft belly.
Being lured by temptations
depends on the one's personality.
And that's your problem.
It has nothing to do with me.
Have fun.
You are great Mrs Feza.
You really are.
You were great.
Come on, let's not keep
the children waiting.
Shall we go now?
O.K, one more.
This is the last one.
Just a minute.
Let's do it properly.
Ladies and gentlemen...
greatest name of all times
of flamenco dance.
A unique talent...
Senora Feza.
Cause of Death: Suicide.
Mrs Feza?
What happened?
What happened? Are you alright?
Can you hear me?
Mrs Feza?
Please, don't do this.
This can't be happening.
Please.
Can you hear me Mrs Feza?
Please, don't. Don't do this.
Please, no.
I was going to take you home.
I was going to cook for you.
I was going to
knit a jumper for you.
I was going to look after you.
I was unable to look after Mebrule.
But I was going to look after you.
I wasn't going to be like Mr Mehmet.
I was never going to moan.
I was going to look after you.
I thought of everything.
I was going to introduce you
to my daughter.
to my grandchild.
I was going to say
"Look, this is Mrs Feza."
"She is a dear old friend of mine".
"She is not well".
"She is staying in a nursing home".
"But she is lonely and unhappy there".
"From now on, she'll be staying with us."
"She'll be forever staying with us".
Please, don't do this.
This can't be happening.
Ol茅, Ol茅, Ol茅.
Hi Deva, I am the "Dog Killer".
F... ck off!
You don't believe me.
But this little gift may convince you.
- Are you going out?
- I'll be right back.
Nevra!
Wait!
Are you alright?
Reyhan.
What?
Reyhan committed suicide.
Who is Reyhan?
Don't tell anybody, O.K?
You promised Nevra.
Don't forget.
O.K, I won't forget.