Scoundrel!
You should have atleast told us.
Told you what?
Best wishes on your birthday, Vaibhav.
I will never forget the first time we met.
You were standing there hungry and thirsty in the corridor and I..
It's not.. - Let me complete.
At first sight I felt I'd found my companion..
..on the journey to IT Bombay Computer science.
Meena, it is not my birthday.
Do you rich people eat cake whenever you want?
I went to Maheshwari to check on Vartika's results.
I came across a bakery on the way so, I bought a cake.
She would be happy when I'd tell her the good news.
She would give me credit. I will feel like a hero.
And you will get to kiss her.
Right, bro? You were right. Then?
What then? I saw the results.
Vartika didn't make it. I did.
Did you check the results thoroughly?
Eight times. From up to down.
You taught her so much, bro, and yet she didn't make it?
She's a very dumb girl..
..but good choice for girlfriend.
No. Many students sat for the exam. Somesh. Shubham.
Alok. Utsav. All their names were on the list.
Our Shubham? - Yes.
Maheshwari has batches of 80 students.
If they had batches of 200 students then Vartika would have made it.
Which batch did you get? - A3.
Great! When the teacher didn't make it to the first batch..
..how can he expect his student to get selected?
You are just like Batla.
Hey! Even Abhigyan made it in A3. - Oh!
The A3 students in over there have 80 percent probability..
..of getting selected to JEE.
I didn't mean to sit for the exam.
What is the problem?
It's a good thing she did not make it.
How is it good?
How is it good? She must be very sad, sitting in room.
It will make me feel very bad to see her sad.
Never mind the hero moment, I don't have the nerve to go see her.
You have made it to A1 but you have the same old A10 mentality.
Be a little foresighted. Don't think about the present.
Think about the future.
Look, if she had made it, she would have gone to Vigyan Nagar.
You would be stuck in Talwandi.
How would you meet on a daily basis?
It's been four months since you came to Kota, right?
How many times have you been to Vidyanagar?
We could meet midway somewhere.
Sure, you would go. She wouldn't come time and again.
You were lucky.
Look, now you can practice chemistry..
..in the streets of Talwandi at leisure through the year.
Win her heart.
Then if you wish you can do what Uday said as well.
Crap!
Meena, you have become very smart.
Of course. I'm not in A1 without reason.
Wonderful!
What do you say, brothers?
Shall we have cake? - Yes, yes. Of course.
It has been seven years since I had cake. - Eat.
It's a call from the coaching class.
We still have time to pay the fees. Why are they calling now?
Hello.
What? - What?
I thought you'd be mourning. - No. I'm okay.
Yes, I could tell when I saw the bread and jam.
But so chill?
You are relaxed because your hero made it, right?
Listen. I'm happy for him that he made it but he's no hero.
I've never understood you girls till date.
If you like the boy, then go and propose to him.
No. First we will romance secretly. Then we wait for him to propose.
Following which we shall think whether to say yes or no.
Just a minute. Why should I propose?
You like the boy? - You're back to that again.
Go and give this lecture to Vaibhav.
Those times are gone, madam The kind of guy you like..
..in your case you will have to propose and initiate the first kiss as well.
Like you proposed to Uday? - I would. I see no problem in it..
..but I didn't need to. He isn't that pussy.
Alright. If he is such a pussy then let it be.
You are in doubt? Don't remain doubtful.
He will say yes. He's highly interested.
Uday told you?
Madam, why do you think Shivangi Renawat is so popular in 'Paschim Vihar"?
Because she can sniff romance.
And Uday told me as well.
Look, you take my advice if you wish but there is no compulsion.
Listen. What did Uday say to you?
Sir, we didn't have any particular reason to sit for the exams.
Six hours. Paper one. Paper two. 240 questions.
All of you sat for them for no particular reason?
Bravo!
Yes, sir. Even I had no particular reason for it.
We will be competing in JEE with the same students who sit for Maheshwari's test.
Sir, one should know who one is competing with.
That's why I sat for it. - Yes, that is the correct reason.
I mean to say that is my reason too, sir.
Even I sat for it without reason, sir.
You too?
Sir, he was deliberate. He reached there 30 minutes early.
And he did not go alone. He even got his sister to sit for the exam.
She is not my sister.
What were you thinking, Vaibhav Pandey?
Our top students will go to sit for Maheshwari's entrance test..
..and we wouldn't know?
What is your problem anyway?
You don't talk to me.
All of you are the real prodigies .
All of us are here for you.
I've said this earlier as well. A1 students are my rankers.
The rest are my bankers.
I don't care about them.
Tell me, Shubham. What problem do you have here?
Alok?
Vaibhav?
What is so wrong at Prodigy classes?
Do you guys have any suggestions?
You have no problem?
Alright. Tell me what's good over there.
What is better over there?
Look. You will be selected either here or there.
But here you will be toppers.
You will receive a prize.
We even pay the IIT fees of the top ten rankers here.
We do far more marketing than them.
Look at him.
Rijul Jain.
His All India Rank was 19.
We plastered his face all over the city.
We gave him a BMW.
We made him a star.
Star.
He received four proposals at the age of 18.
Is that a small feat?
Will they print such big photos?
They will print a tiny one.
Look, boys. If you shift there now, your routine will suffer.
Plus they will focus on their toppers..
..who have been with them since the 11th grade.
Over here I know that Somesh is weak with S block.
Vaibhav's Equilibrium is haywire.
So I'll take extra classes.
I'll give them practice question papers.
I will solve their doubts.
Are you going to receive such personal care over there? Tell me.
Will you? - Yes, sir.
I understand. I won't go.
Ask me now if you have any doubts?
Tell me.
Is everyone sure? - Yes, sir!
I mean, me too, sir. Me neither, sir. Not going, sir.
Did you pay the fees for 12th grade?
No, sir. I have to. - Sir, dad will do so.
It will be paid, sir.
We'll pay it, sir.
If haven't paid, it is okay and if you have paid it, don't worry.
We will refund it.
20 percent extra scholarships for the A1 batch.
If you go there you will have to pay higher fees..
..whereas we are giving you scholarships over here.
Okay?
Fine. Give them the booklets.
Give all of them my number too.
My personal number.
Okay?
Well, alright. Dismiss.
Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
Sorry, sir.
You have a list of all their names, don't you?
Call their parents.
We help them get through NTSE, KVPY and Olympiad..
..and the scoundrels will give their ranks to Maheshwari.
You are tense without reason, sir.
I've spoken to them. They won't go anywhere.
Mr. Batla, in the coaching business it's all about one year only.
If they don't get a rank this year we won't get admissions next year.
How long will we print his photo anyway?
He looks so ugly.
Yes, sir. That is true.
But, sir, when a respected man talks to the children..
..theydefinitely pay heed to him. -Correct.
Call Jeetu sir to talk to them. They will pay heed to him.
He took your name? - Not just my name.
He gave me this card with his personal number.
He even gave me scholarship. - Show me.
Work hard. You don't get it otherwise.
I bet Deepak must have been sweating bullets seeing the toppers run.
Yes. He talked to us so politely...
My dad never spoke to me so politely.
And Batla was so sentimental ..
He will surely get a promotion.
He said now that you are in A1 now it will be smooth sailing.
We have misunderstood Batla.
He even knows that I am weak at equilibrium.
He said I shall give you extra classes.
Students who leave Maheshwari and remain with Prodigy gain respect.
I too left Maheshwari last year but I didn't gain any.
Shall I reappear for the exams? When is the next exam?
What good will it do now, buddy?
The toppers already sat for the exam.
That's right. Their batches are going to begin anyway.
You can appear for it next year.
But nobody is going to go.
Why? - All of them sat for the exam only to check out the competition.
We worked so hard to get to A1. Why would they go now?
Yes, that is correct.
Hey, Somesh.
Shubham, we have been studying together for the past one year.
You never told me you are a Bihari.
No, I am Oriya. From Kalahandi. - I see.
Do you mean you don't talk like "we are doing this" or "we are saying that?"
No.
Then why the fuck were you using those words over there?
That's what we decided we would say.
You swine! You were supposed to say you aren't going.
If you say "We", won't he know we have formed a group?
Lord knows what kind of idiots make it to Maheshwari.
Give me dessert.
Next time anyone asks you say you aren't going.
If he asks about the others, you say you don't know.
I haven't spoken to anyone about it.
Else all of them will hound us.
I felt what Batla said made sense.
Don't listen to him. He was talking nonsense!
You are weak at S block because he didn't teach it well.
Batla is jealous of us. He wants to go to Maheshwari himself..
..but Maheshwari does not employ non-IITian teachers.
We have made it to A1 somehow, haven't we?
We will deal with it. - Any idiot can make it to A1 over here.
Try getting into the A1 batch at Maheshwari.
It is not known as the best institute without reason.
These people cannot handle JEE.
Their students are cracking one Olympiad after another.
In future too they will lay it on thick with their emotional crap.
Don't pay heed. You know why?
Because they have several things at Maheshwari that are missing here..
..but they don't have anything over here that is missing at Maheshwari.
Jeetu Bhaiya?
I am not going, Bhaiya.
I have already started electrostatics.
Then why did you sit for the exam.
No reason.
I wanted to see where I stand.
Did you see? Did you make it to A1?
I made it to A3. But I am not going, Bhaiya.
Shubham, is your friend going or not?
Bhaiya, I am not going. I don't know about him..
..because we haven't discussed it. I can only tell you of my plans.
You haven't discussed it? - No.
You are friends. Friends should discuss things.
We aren't friends, Bhaiya. He doesn't even know I am Oriya.
From Kalahandi, right? - Yes. But I am not going.
That's right, Bhaiya. Even we are not going.
Well, alright. There's no point then.
All of you go. Chill.
Bhaiya.
I heard both Shubham and Alok talking in the mess.
Both of them are going to Maheshwari.
I'd give you that in writing. - I know. It happens every year.
I also know that you aren't going, when in fact you should go.
Every year we even have someone like you over here.
Please stop ragging me, Bhaiya.
I only sat for the exam because Vartika..
I'll tell you later. But I don't want to go.
You did a good thing by sitting for it.
Now that you have been selected you should go.
Look, you can manage physics.
You have a problem with chemistry and Math.
Now that you are giving up inorganic..
..you have to strengthen organic and physical, right?
It is taught well over there.
But I am settled over here now, Bhaiya.
Everything is going well.
Why would I leave now?
How will you grow if you don't go? Tell me.
You know the saying, if you're the smartest person in the class..
..you're in the wrong class.
With whom will you compete over here?
All your competition will leave.
Your batches, Shubham and Alok. All of them will leave.
Rather than getting complacent in A1 over here..
..you'll be better off struggling in A3 over there.
Make your way to A1 over there.
But you are over here, Bhaiya.
How many people are you going to fall in love with at one time?
You don't understand.
You must continue to move if you wish to grow.
If you want my lecture I give them on Unacademy plus every week.
Watch the live lecture on it.
One has to give up on some things.
There's no reason to be remorseful.
I see.
Won't you be hurt if one of your students leaves..
..to go to another Institute?
I will be hurt more if he doesn't go and he's not selected.
We fixed some of your weaknesses and they will fix some.
Right. You told me I am not alone. I should not be nervous.
We will crack IIT.
We will fight together right up to the last minute.
I am fighting.
Your selection is important.
Where you are selected from was never important.
What's the matter?
Bhaiya, from the first day that I arrived here..
..it had been my wish to have my photo put up over here.
So, they will put up your photo. - Not over there.
Over here... The place where you are at.
Look, Arjun learned from Indra. He learned from Shiva too.
Still he was known as Dronacharya's student, wasn't he?
Don't I put ex-Agarwalite in front of my name?
If I were in your shoes I would go.
Because we don't have anything here that they don't have over there.
Have you spoken to Vaibhav?
No. I called him but I didn't get through.
He must be at the Institute, I guess. He will call.
I spoke to Uday.
Vaibhav's admin had summoned him..
..along with the other kids who are going to Maheshwari.
He is going? - No.
I see. That's why you asked me if I'd spoken to him.
To cross check?
Listen. He won't go if you tell him not to go.
Why should I tell him? Wouldn't I go if I were in his shoes?
Wasn't that the reason we took the exam?
For which you were not at all prepared and neither was he.
He didn't even want to sit for the exam.
Yet all week long he set everything aside..
..to help you prepare for the exam, right?
He could've gone home, couldn't he? He did not go.
Because he likes you, Vartika.
He likes you.
Do you want me to talk to him if you can't talk?
Oh, no.
Look, won't it be good for him if he goes to Maheshwari?
They have everything over there. - You aren't.
Look, I'm not saying this for the sake of your lovey-dovey romance.
I couldn't give two hoots about that.
You two had set a goal that you were following.
By himself he would never study as much as he studies with you.
You completed the entire syllabus of the 11th grade in one week..
..and you even started studying for 12th grade.
Did you ever get ahead of the class syllabus before? No.
You aren't the only one who will benefit by being together..
..he will also benefit.
He knows this. The only problem is that he won't tell you.
So, you tell him.
You help him. Don't leave him hanging.
He will come to help you if you ever have a problem, won't he?
Jeetu bhaiya is wrong. Tell me.
You tell me. What do they have over there?
80 percent of the A3 batch from Maheshwariis selected, right?
20 percent does not get selected. Jeetu Bhaiya didn't tell you that.
You don't wake up on time for classes. I wake you up.
How will you prepare on your own over there?
Jeetu Bhaiya didn't tell you that. Did you discuss this?
He was only discussing with me.
Besides, we will stay in touch, Meena.
Why are you saying such things?
Really? Do you meet Piyush?
He was your school friend, wasn't he?
Tell me how many times you went to see him in all these months.
Once you go there you won't have the time.
Also, you owe me seven puffs.
You can't leave until you give it to me.
That is final. That is final.
I am still pondering over it.
I don't know as yet.
Deepak is saying something. Bhaiya is saying something else.
I don't know what I should do. - You see?
You see? You see?
I am the one who explains everything to you.
Without me you cannot make sense of things.
You talk to him, Uday. I'll talk to him too.
You are not going. Okay?
You tell him, Uday.
What can I say? - Tell him not to go.
What you or I say shouldn't matter to him.
He came here to prepare for IIT.
Didn't you?
So, do that.
I guess right now we feel we have come to Kota, we are having fun..
..we are going out, studying,
memories are being created..
..and forming friendships..
..but if we don't get the desired result at the end of all this..
..then we won't feel like turning around and remembering these times.
Then it stays with us as a bad memory.
If we aren't selected then all our mischief will haunt us as mistakes.
We are at such an age.
We are unable to foresee the future.
You are in doubt, aren't you?
Talk to your dad. - As though you pay heed to your dad.
I am unable to follow his instructions.
It does not mean that I don't pay heed to him.
I can't do it.
I am unable to concentrate. I cannot sit up 6 hours like you guys.
What should I do?
You tell me, Meena. What should I do?
Tell me. Shall I leap to death, hang or run away?
I can't even return.
People will ask me what happened.
You wanted to join IIT. You didn't get selected into IIT?
I feel ashamed of myself when I look at you, Meena.
I feel ashamed of your achievements despite your background.
I have everything.
Despite having everything I failed to achieve anything.
I am unable to do anything.
My father is an IRS Officer.
How do I tell him I am worthless?
I won't be able to crack the IIT exams.
Please pardon me!
How do I tell him, Meena?
Talk to your dad.
Do what he tells you to do.
Your parents' decision could be wrong..
..but their intent is never wrong.
We have to take this object from location A to location B.
Correct?
It won't go there just by blowing.
It needs to be pushed.
This object needs a push like every person needs a push.
So we shall apply force toit.
We only apply enough force to push it to the neutral point.
Its own potential will take it the rest of the way.
Correct? I've told you a lot about this problem.
You solve the rest of it and bring it back to the next class.
When will we be meeting next?
When will we meet? On Thursday. So, you have two days.
Until then, solve the problem.
Sit. Sit. What is the matter?
Have you decided?
This is for you.
For me?
Thank you for everything.
Oh big spender!
If you are spending so much on me, what is the name of the exam girl?
You must have really splurged on the Vernali.
Vartika. - You are hitting on two girls simultaneously?
Just drop it, Bhaiya.
Come. I'll show you something.
Come. Come.
Over here.
You will take off your shoes..? leave it just come in.
Do you see these?
This is Armani.
This is Gucci.
I think this one isn't even available in India.
You see those shoes?
All of them are LV.
These watches. Rado. Rolex.
Shahrukh does the ad for this one.
I wonder what's written here in French.
Why are you showing off, Bhaiya?
I have to. These are gifts from my students.
This is my true earning.
I don't wear them but I look best in them.
Shubham from IIT Bombay. Then MIT.
This is from Akash. IIT Kanpur. CS dropout.
Then Microsoft.
He has a startup now. Lord knows what he's going to do.
That's from Chirag.
This is from Jhanvi.
Like you, all of them had brought gifts for me.
I didn't accept.
Nothing against gifts. I do accept gifts..
..as long as they're bought with your earning..
..not with your father's earning.
Work hard. Complete your studies.
And after you become successful..
..if you still remember anyone called Jeetu Bhaiya or Jeetu sir..
..then you bring me a gift. Then I shall accept it.
And I don't accept such cheap stuff.
Keep it.
Take care of it. Make good use of it..
..and go to Maheshwari.
Okay?
Yes or no. Say something, bro.
Go.
Didn't Vartika come?
Did you call and ask her to come?
Man.
I couldn't get myself to call her.
Will you do something for me? Will you please give her these notes?
Why?
Can't you give them to her?
Lord knows when I'll see her. - Not my problem.
Give them to her yourself.
Any more bags? - No.
Well, take care.
Stay in touch.
I put the extension cord in your bag.
He is demanding 150 rupees. Don't give him more than 100.
Meena.
Seven onion puffs.
I owed you, didn't I?
I am clearing the score before leaving.
Take it. - No, no. You keep it.
The mess won't be open when you get there. Eat this.
You are refusing onion puffs?
I am not letting you off the hook.
Meet me at IIT.
Repay me there.
This won't be available over there, so, you'll have to pay heavy interest.
You'll have to pay with croissants. - I see.
When I solve your doubts in IIT..
..you will have to pay me with double the number of croissants.
Get it? - You will solve my doubts?
We shall see. - We shall see.
You wanna bet on it? - It's a bet.
We shall stay in touch. - No, no.
You study. Don't think about it.
In any case, there's a difference between meeting sometimes..
..and living together.
Anyway friendship is not revision that must be done.
Focus on your studies.
Bye.
See you, bro.
Please say bye to Vartika for me.
Double croissants.
Vaibhav!
Stop for a minute, brother.
What's the matter? Is everything okay?
Yes, I ran over.
That's why.. - Oh.
I thought you were leaving tomorrow morning.
Yes. Actually the new PG told me to shift today, so..
Oh.
Sorry.
I should have called you.
I didn't think you would leave.
We clicked well.
With our studies. - Yes.
I mean..
Actually even I did not think I would go..
..but I have to go.
Yes.
This is for you.
It will be useful to you.
Thank you.
Are you cold?
No. Why? What happened?
You are shivering. That's why I asked.
Yes.
I don't know. Maybe.
I guess it is happening because I am a little nervous.
Oh!
Wait a minute. Hold this.
What's the matter? - Hold it.
Have this.
Thanks.
What will you do with the rest of the yogurt?
Don't worry. I'll apply it on my hair.
Gross! Yuck!
Best of luck for IIT.
For IIT.
See you.
You will.
'This is Vaibhav.'
'Yes.'
'This is my Kota number. Save it.'
'No, not in Maheshwari. Prodigy.'
'I am Meena. Prodigy. A5.'
'Why didn't you come to Kota earlier?'
'We would have become friends earlier.'
'Hi. Vaibhav. You're from Itarsi. You have come to Prodigy.'
'You are like a son to aunty, right?'
'What is the reason a fragile and helpless boy like you..
..left his home, school and all else mid semester to come to Kota?'
'You are lagging behind because you are late..
..but you aren't alone.'
'We will fight right up to the last minute and crack IIT.'
'Yes!'
Do you have a match box?
No. Not to light a cigarette.
I want to light a mosquito coil.
There are many mosquitoes here.
Yes, I might have one. Let me see.
May I come in?
I am Sushrut. Maheshwari classes. A7.
I stay in the room upstairs. I moved in yesterday.
You?
Vaibhav. Maheshwari. A3.
So, is this your first year or did you attend coaching before?
I was in Prodigy in the 11th grade.
Talwandi. - Oh.
Then you must be quite a bookworm.
No. The usual five to six hours types.
I have only just come.
Seeing everyone has shaken me up.
I wish I had come for the 11th grade.
I think 12th grade is a little late.
I have my boards too this year.
I wonder how I will manage.
Don't be tense.
Only 21 days.
You just have to slog for 21 days.
After that you will blend in.
You want some puffs?