Remember the "Personality".
I met a girl today.
Her name is Nevra Elmas.
Do you have something
to tell me Binnaz?
She is the only one I trust.
Because Nevra understands me.
It's Nevra's birthday today.
I got her a present.
Has your brother Tayyar
ever mentioned a girl named Reyhan?
He used to say "they wasted her",
not "I wasted her".
I told you, I haven't done anything.
I only threw a small piece of stone.
Me and Nevra share a secret.
Cemil almost owns
whole of Kambura.
Nothing ever takes place
without his knowledge.
If it is as precious as to be
hidden under a pillow...
it was more likely a diary.
I told Nevra everything.
But she doesn't believe me.
You are not speaking
to your friend in Ankara.
I don't think you should ever
speak to him again anyway.
Save his a..ss
and save your own.
We need someone to sort him out.
I will burn that gypsy so bad they
will ever dare to return to Kambura.
Tayyar remembers you.
He said "they wasted
the poor girl".
Hello Reyhan.
If Tayyar remembers,
so do the others.
All of them, they all remember.
Whole of Kambura remembers.
They just pretend
that they don't.
Don't pull the trigger.
Because I won't.
The scene will be catastrophic,
God forbid if one of these glasses break.
So intriguing.
Once I saved a fish's live.
Now they are saving my life.
I don't think you've come here
to kill me anyway.
I tell you what's best...
we both put the guns down...
and start from scratch.
Right from the beginning.
Nevra, where are you?
I am at the station in Kambura.
The girl we're looking for
is definitely Reyhan.
I'll tell you when I come back
but I have to stay here another day.
Nevra...
chief Tolga is suspended.
Are you serious? Why?
We don't know.
Nobody knows. Firuz will
take his place temporarily.
The chief is packing up today. I think you
should be here to say your farewells.
O.K.
He tells me to organize a fancy dress
party where all the guests are...
dressed in " Dog Killer" costumes.
He says "bring the gun too.
I'll be there to finish somebody off".
What shall I do? Set up a party?
You're right. But let's say we don't
cooperate. The guy killed 11 people.
Do you think
he'd leave me alone?
- Hi guys.
- Hi mum.
Deva...
can I talk to you in private?
O.K
See you later S眉veyda.
What is so important?
Your dad called.
What did he say?
He says me misses us.
So?
So...
he wants us back.
He says he'll book
and pay for our flight.
"Otherwise I'll come and
get you myself" he says.
So, he is planning to kidnap us.
Not exactly. But you know your dad.
He can be very impatient.
But he doesn't care
about what we want.
And what did you tell him?
"Deva started school and I found a job.
We have a new life now."
Didn't you tell him that?
Of course I did.
But he says "don't worry, school is not a
big issue, we'll figure something out".
Mum...
that's exactly why my dad
wanted to get divorced.
He had enough of you going
along with everything he said.
As if he was your only
connection with life.
He was suffocating because
you made him feel like...
the world revolved around him.
And now he is upset
because we are not there.
That's normal, because
he's got no one to boss around.
The person you call "that man"
is your father. He looked after me.
Your mum is ill, son.
I know.
Your mum is an alcoholic.
I'll still be an alcoholic
even if I quit drinking.
That's how it will always be.
And your father put up with me.
He looked after me. Understand?
Your illness has got nothing
to do with being alcoholic.
Your problem is something else.
You become the slave of whoever
looks after you. That's your illness.
You are addicted to people,
not alcohol.
Girls!
What are you doing?
You've said it was impossible.
How did it happen?
I have been looking
at the wrong floor.
I should've been looking
further up.
- How much further up?
- Very much.
That's why I am telling you the pack it in.
Because it's too dangerous.
Do you remember when
we were at the university?
Remember the dreams we had?
Sure I do. We were planning
to change the world.
But what happened?
We changed our world.
I can't breathe here. Not enough oxygen.
I want to go back to school days.
It's up to you.
What are you going to do now?
I'll arrest him. What else?
Just tell me, is it really him?
99 percent. But you won't
go in alone, will you?
At least let chief Tolga know.
From now on, I am the one
to be reported to.
Tolga is suspended.
I am replacing him.
- Are you serious?
- It was inevitable.
Look at me, I am working
like a donkey.
All Tolga was doing
laying on his back.
You are a dodgy man.
You've got it in for Nevra.
Didn't you say you'll catch the man
before she does?
- See this?
- What?
The mark left by Nevra's slap.
I see it every morning
when I look at the mirror.
It is Zuhal.
Strange.
Hello? Hi Zuhal.
Yes, he is here.
Hang on.
O.K darling.
Zuhal, how are you sweetheart?
Pardon?
What do you mean?
So sudden?
Dear oh dear!
Why?
O.K, I see.
We'll talk later.
O.K, I've got to go.
My silly daughter.
What is it?
Something bad happened?
They are going back.
- Where?
- Australia.
Immediately.
Such a shame.
You only just got back together.
She said "urgent".
Did something bad happened?
- She made up with her husband.
- That's nice.
That's good news.
It is so sudden.
I've just gotten used to them.
Is it alright if we leave tonight?
I want to see them.
That's fine.
I'll go and pack my suitcase.
Agah...
don't be upset.
It was nice to have somebody around,
a voice in the house.
Now, I'll go back to being alone.
I am ready. We can go.
We can leave right away.
No rush. Let's eat first.
Then we can leave.
Boss...
you can take it to the
administrative court...
even all the way
to council of state.
There'll be no use.
What are you going to do?
First, I have to remove the sand bag.
But it's not going to be easy.
Then I'll go and
see may children.
I'll say to them "daddy is back,
I'll be home from now on".
"The never-ending shift has finally
ended. Your dad is here now".
That's what I'll say to them.
Then I'll go to sleep.
This is the plan for time being.
Do you want to know how I feel?
There are things in life that you rely on
when you are in trouble.
For example, 155.
Police emergency.
Or if there is a fire, you know that
fire brigade will attend.
If you're stuck in an elevator
you push the emergency button...
and talk to someone.
There are panic buttons.
You push them and talk to police
or whoever.
All of these give you
a piece of mind.
Just imagine that
none of these works.
You dial 155 but no answer.
There is a fire. You call the fire
brigade but no one shows up.
You are stuck in an elevator. You push
the button to talk to someone.
Panic button for example.
You push it and shout
"is there anybody there".
But no answer.
You start to think there is
something wrong.
You snap it off the wall,
take a look and...!
What the f... cuk!
The wires are not connected.
There are no wires. Just a thing
that was mounted on the wall.
You've spent your life by trusting it.
But they put it there to deceive you.
Just trust it. Don't ask questions. Just do
your job. That's what it is there for.
But you've been fool enough
to trust it.
There was nothing to trust.
That's how I feel now.
I believed in things for nothing.
And that's what really bugs me.
I don't know what to do now.
All right lads...
you know, I always say to you...
our job...
I mean your job...
is saving lives.
That's why, there is no resting for you
until the last killer is caught.
It means that you'll never rest.
Because there will
always be a killer on the loose.
You knowingly choose a difficult life, so
that people you don't even know...
can sleep peacefully
in their beds.
You swore to sacrifice your lives for
people you don't know...
so justice in this sh... tty world
can prevail.
It was an honour to work
with you guys.
And you should be proud
of yourselves.
Because...
dedicating a life to justice
is not a personal matter.
It is the matter of personality.
Take care.
S... t!
What do you want?
Another fairy-tale?
Is that why you're calling?
You hung Reyhan's photo everywhere.
It says on it "do you remember".
What has it got to do with you?
Find Sungur Demirci. He is the one
who best remembers.
He was pimping Reyhan.
Pimping?
How do you know?
My husband told me.
You were right Nevra.
I married the man who raped me.
Sefa...
is there a Sungur Demirci among men
whom you investigate in Kambura?
Sungur.
Let's see.
Sungur Demirci.
We already took a
statement from him.
- What does he do?
- He said "marketing".
We are going to Kambura.
Go on, pass.
Go on.
Isn't he the...?
Yes, that's him.
Agah, can you slow down please?
- We are already slow.
- Make it slower please.
You know I don't like speed.
Agah!
I feel very uncomfortable.
Please slow down.
There is a truck right ahead.
What are you doing?
I want to get off.
Are you alright Agah?
Can you pull over? I want to get off.
I feel very uncomfortable.
Agah, please. I want to get off.
What are you doing? Slow down.
You're going to kill us.
What are you doing?
Agah!
I apologize.
You've made me relive the most horrific
moment of my life.
- How could you?
- I apologize.
You are not what you appear to be.
Who are you?
I don't want to know anyway.
Just leave it at that.
There is a saying...
don't complain about the traffic.
Because you are the traffic.
You were not the only guilty party.
I was guilty too.
I wished that tango we had
that night would last forever.
Let's dance forever.
Let's tango forever.
But the music had stopped long ago
and I never knew it.
I apologize.
What is this? What's going on?
Get out.
I've been following you for hours
and you knew it.
Don't pretend that
you are surprized.
Shut the door.
Easy.
What do you want, money?
Amazing...
eleven murders.
What murder?
I must admit,
you don't fit in the type.
I don't know you.
You know rookie
deputy superintendent Nevra.
You keep texting her.
But you don't know Firuz, the fastest
slinger in the whole homicide.
Of course you know me.
You know me like f... ck.
Well done to you. I mean it.
This is how a serial killer
should be.
He should know the cops
who are after him...
so he can run.
Can I see your badge?
Who are you kidding?
Me or yourself?
Or both of us?
Can I see your badge?
Is it O.K?
Are you arresting me?
Are we going down the station?
We are going straight
to the court.
- What do you mean by court?
- I mean you'll talk.
You'll confess. You'll tell.
You used to work in the courthouse.
You know how it goes.
You'll talk and I'll listen.
I am not telling you anything.
You either take me down to the station
or this is a kidnap.
Do you know the minimum?
I don't think we can see
eye to eye.
I am telling you, it is over.
You are caught. Understand?
I have 40 evidence that says
Agah Beyo臒lu killed all those people.
Now, it is about time you tell me why
you are so interested in Kambura.
I am not telling you anything.
You can take me down to the station
and provide me with a lawyer.
Well, well, well.
I think you've been watching
too many movies.
I can provide you with somebody else
instead of a lawyer.
How about...
your daughter?
Zuhal.
How do you know Zuhal?
I have DNA analysis. And you are
asking me how I know your daughter.
I know her from a different place.
But it is a different subject.
What do you mean
by different subject?
How do you know Zuhal?
Shall we go and ask her in person?
She can sit right beside you...
instead of a lawyer.
She can sit very close to you.
Then I shoot her in the head.
Her blood splashes on your face.
Perhaps you confess while your
daughter's blood is running down...
your face.
What do you think?
Where do you think Zuhal is now?
Home or work?
What do you want from me?
Why are you doing this?
I've a little debt to pay off.
Who knows? I may even
become a payee after all.
If you do anything to Zuhal...
cause her any harm...
I'll make you suffer so much
before I kill you...
you'd wish you were never born.
Do you understand me son?
Yeah, sure.
I am doing my deed...
giving you a little warning.
You are not going anywhere.
What do you mean you're leaving?
You're going nowhere.
I won't let you.
Look...
you did me good.
I won't let you go.
Cemil, think sensibly.
O.K, we have a thing going.
But Deva has a future there.
I have a house there.
I'll bring that house down Zuhal.
What?
O.K, that's good.
Where are you now?
I'll be there right away.
First, we have to sort out
our own issues.
Then I'll deliver the goods.
- What do you want?
- We'll talk about it.
Who is this man?
What's his problem?
I don't know.
But we'll find out.
I'll let you know
if we come to a deal.
B... stard!
What is it, something bad?
Yes, it is.
He does exactly the same.
Who is he? What's going on?
You're all the same.
First, you make me believe things.
Then you betray me.
What did I do to you?
Nothing but favours.
Shame on you.
You are nothing
like your father.
I hope whoever is behind this
slander rots in hell.
I know nothing about pimping.
What are you talking about?
Now Mr Sungur, if you're going
to be all tensed up...
we can take you down the station
where you can relax a bit.
Look, officers...
I have nothing to do
with pimping or anything.
Tell me, how did you manage to
disguise yourself all these years?
You have no criminal record.
I wonder if you happen to
know a judge or something.
For instance, Mehmet Yurtgil.
- Do you know him?
- No, I don't.
I don't know any judge.
Nevra...
can you excuse us for a minute?
Look, I swear I know nothing.
I don't know Reyhan or any other girl.
You can ask anybody.
I am not involved
in anything like that.
We did ask.
They said you are a pimp.
F... cking b..stards.
Yes, you're right. Unfortunately
you can never trust people.
I myself was a victim of a slander once.
That's how I know.
Once, we detained a man who later
claimed that we tortured him.
I said no way.
Son of a b... tch even got
a report from a hospital...
claiming that we broke
his bones.
I said he probably did it himself.
Banging his arms and legs to a wall.
He was planning
to take us to court.
Luckily internal affairs ruled out
investigation and the case closed.
Appropriate outcome.
Yeah, otherwise.
We would've been in deep shit.
That's why I understand you.
Being falsely accused is a bad thing.
Because I had not
broken any bones.
I had stuck a truncheon up his a..s
instead.
I think he was too ashamed
to tell the doctors.
I wouldn't be so upset
if he told the truth.
But he was lying.
He was saying I broke his arm.
So, your wife has passed away.
Yes, she's gone.
May she rest in peace.
What do you do about cooking?
There is a girl.
She comes around and does it for me.
Do you like pastry,
like, pies and things?
- Yeah, I do.
- Good.
So, you must have a rolling pin.
O.K Mr Agah, spill the beans.
What's your problem with Kambura?
It was 1995.
I was transferred to
Kambura Court House.
In the beginning
everything was good.
People were pleasant
and hospitable.
And Kambura was a nice place.
I said to my late wife that
we came to a nice place...
that we are out of the
hustle-bustle of Istanbul.
In 1996...
a 14 year old girl
committed suicide.
She used to live with her granny.
Poor girl was an orphan.
Her name was Reyhan.
I received the file.
The police report said
"heavy depression".
And the case was closed.
One day, her granny turned up,
holding a notebook.
She said it belonged to her grandchild
but couldn't read it as she was illiterate.
She said her grandchild wouldn't
take her life in her own accord.
She said something
must've happened to her.
She said it may be in this notebook.
I want you to take a look.
And so I did.
It was her diary.
She'd written down everything.
Every single name in Kambura
was in the diary.
Even from outside.
For example, a judge.
He used to visit Kambura
every now and then.
So, he knew too.
Judges, teachers...
crooks, cops...
poor and the rich...
the educated, the ignorant...
She was only 12 years old
at the time.
Only 12.
- Reyhan stop.
- Stay away.
Reyhan!
- Don't.
- Away!
Reyhan, stop.
Away!
Let me go.
For 2 years...
all these men
raped the poor girl.
53 of them in total.
The poor girl couldn't take it anymore
and she took her own life.
She'd become anybody's item.
I don't know who but apparently a
boy gives her a false hope of marriage.
He makes a move on her.
She doesn't decline, thinking that they
were going to get married anyway.
Then he begins to threaten her,
forcing her to be with others too.
She gets frightened.
She thinks it will be
just a one-time thing.
But the men keep coming,
one after the other.
Like flies around honey.
Then they brought her to me.
I thought I could
make some cash.
We have a barn just over there.
She worked for couple of months.
Then she killed herself.
You s..n of a b... tc!
I am going to ruin
your f... cking life.
S..n of a b... tch!
What did you do
after reading the diary?
What can I do?
I had an 11-year-old daughter.
I thought I should move her away.
So, I sent her to a boarding school.
She had to get out of Kambura.
Because these men were everywhere.
What did you do about Reyhan?
Didn't you hand the diary over to D.A?
No trial was set?
I was going to hand it to the D.A.
But his name was in the diary too.
My hand was tied. I was scared.
There were so many of them.
And I was just a simple civil servant.
I thought they can
walk all over me.
The girl was gone anyway. What's the
use of taking the case to the court?
It was not going
to bring her back.
F..cking sh... t!
After a while, I got transferred
to Istanbul.
But I never forgot about Reyhan.
I left Kambura. But I was never
able to leave Reyhan.
10 years ago, I bought a gun.
I wanted to kill someone.
I tried but failed.
I tried again...
but failed again.
What made you
start killing them all?
I was diagnosed with
Alzheimer's Disease.
I thought to myself
"you are running out of time".
It will come a day
you'll forget about Reyhan.
You'll forget about Reyhan who has
been in your mind for 22 years.
Was Cemil Havran in the diary too?
Is that why you went to him?
Whole of Kambura
took care of him.
Business owners, civil servants.
I even paid for son of a b... tch's
private lessons.
It turned out that he was pimping
the girl to return the favours.
Most names in the diary belonged
to those who helped Cemil.
Just give me a f... cking break.
Hello?
I am listening doctor.
O.K, we'll be on our way.
I am bringing him.
Are we going?
Come on.
- You are staying here.
- What?
Why are you not taking me?
Take me to the station.
Why are you leaving me here?
Firuz!
Why did you leave me here?
I told Nevra everything.
But she doesn't believe me.
Wish they all die.
They are, Reyhan.
Don't you worry about it.
All dying.
Hello?
I want to ask you something.
In Naz 脟枚rt眉k's case, there was a
drop of blood on the floor...
but away from the victim.
As if it belonged
to somebody else.
It may belong to the killer.
Has anything come out of it?
Drop of blood?
There was no such a thing
in the report.
It is not in your report.
But I can see it in the photo.
I told you I was there
before the cops arrived.
It keeps boggling my mind.
I thought I'd ask you.
- Where are you anyway?
- Kambura.
I'll drop by tomorrow and take the photo
from you before I go the station.
O.K.
- Nevra?
- What?
I love you.
Nevra?
I think I am standing outside the house
we once lived years ago.
Can I call you later Ate艧?
O.K.
Did you check your room Nevra?
Make sure you got everything.
I got everything mum.
I'll return the key to the landlord.
Then we can get going.
I am going to meet Reyhan.
I want to see her for the last time.
Go on. But don't be late.
O.K.
We've got a long way to go.
I want to get there before the evening.
Nevra?
Come with me.
We are leaving.
Mum told me not to be late.
We'll make it quick.
Where are we going?
I am going to meet him in the woods.
I want you to meet him.
But you can't tell anybody, O.K?
O.K, promise. Come on.
Firuz!
Who is there?
Anybody there?
Firuz...
son...
why are you keeping me here?
Take me to the station, arrest me
and let's get on with it.
Shut up!
Don't talk.
The last one...
for the last time.
What?
You will kill for the last time.
Who?
Cemil.
Son, are you alright?
And I'll never hear
your name again.
Or I'll come to your house...
and rip your heart out.
Do you understand?
If you get caught,
I don't know you.
If you don't get caught...
I'll forget about you,
and you'll forget about me.
I killed so many people.
It was all over the papers.
Police will never
stop chasing me.
You...
do you think you are the only one
with Alzheimer's Disease?
Everybody is sick.
They're all sick.
Come an international match,
everybody will forget about everything.
This nation forgot so many things.
You won't be an exception.
Who do you think you are anyway?
You are just a killer,
a murder case in the news.
Why are you doing this?
Cemil...
he owns a hospital.
My son is being treated there
since he was born.
It doesn't cost me a penny.
Cemil wouldn't do
anything for nothing.
True.
He got me in return.
I made a promise to myself.
I said, if something happens
to my son...
Cemil will die.
My son...
my son died today.
He was unable to leave
the operating table alive.
Now...
I'll call Cemil.
I'll tell him that you escaped.
I won't reveal your I.D.
Now, go and kill him.
And then, disappear.
- I will have another gift in my hand.
- What is it?
Then I'll ask your granddad.
Good morning.
I was trying to call you.
I have to leave.
I'll meet ex-chief Tolga.
Chief Tolga?
Are you in touch with him?
I'll tell you all about it.
Shall we meet at the
same caf茅 tomorrow?
The one near you.
Alright.
Fine.
Ate艧!
The photo?
Sorry.
I made coffee for you.
There is food too.
Eat before you go.
I can help myself. Thanks.
See you.
Ate艧!
I found something Nevra.
Something very big.
But I have to tell Tolga first.
Is that O.K?
Ate艧!
I love you too.
Oh, yeah!
Nevra!
Life is good.
1 Week Later.
Where?
What's going on?
Is this earthquake? What is it?
It is night already.
I went to bed in the afternoon.
The time...
half past two.
I must've been sleeping for ages.
Bloody music is still going.
They are bouncing up and down
like donkeys.
I've had enough of this s... it.
Nevra Elmas, the only female detective
in homicide...
handed her resignation today.
She was one of the most mediatic faces
of the police force.
The reason behind her decision
is not known yet.
I said everything will be turned off
by 2 a.m.
What is this, a nightclub?
What is this?
- I got it for you today.
- Why?
We are leaving dad.
You'll be here all alone.
It will be a company for you.
I can't believe all that happened
while I was asleep.
Everybody must've been
waiting for this.
You have been asleep for ages.
I didn't want to wake you up.
It must've been an exhausting vacation
with Miss N眉khet.
Do you think it is the medication
that is making you sleepy?
They say it can make
you feel sleepy.
Where are you going dad?
There was a photo of me and your mum
over there. Where did you put it?
It is still here.
I moved it back
to its old place.
Where are you going?
Downstairs. To find out
what the hell is going on.
Deva and his friends are
having a farewell party.
They are enjoying themselves.
Leave them.
They can enjoy themselves
somewhere else.
Do I go to their house
and bounce up and down?
Bloody hell! What a waste of a
generation.
She got me a TV.
As if I am not capable of
getting one myself.
I don't want it. Simple as that.
Look at that. They shut the door
supposedly keep the noise in.
It is f... cking full blast. It's going
to bring the whole building down.
Open it.
What's going on here?
Why are you dressed like this?
Deva!
Is Deva here?
Let me through.
How dare you call me bitch?
You are the bitch.
I am not a bitch.
Af艧in!
Are you alright?
Af艧in, are you alright?
Don't just stand there.
Call an ambulance. Come on.
It is terrible.
How could she do
something like this?
She was a such a sweet girl.
- How is the boy?
- A minor wound.
The paramedic said
it is not life threatening.
In this case, she may as well
shoot him again.
How come such a young girl
can get hold of a gun?
Who gave it to her?
Apparently, it was her dad's.
She should've shot her dad then.
Like that boy did once.
Nothing.
I think my blood pressure shot up.
I am going.
- Are you alright dad?
- I am O.K. I just don't feel too well.
I just need a little rest.
Come on.
I said I am O.K.
Me and Deva share a secret.
We have a secret.
Don't ever forget me Deva.
Don't ever forget me.
There you go.
Have a nice journey.
No crying.
Take really good care of yourself dad.
Don't forget to take your medication.
No, I won't. Don't worry.
Deva!
Son!
Have a nice journey.
I am sorry grandad.
Don't worry about it.
It happens, doesn't it?
It wasn't your fault.
What do you mean it wasn't my fault?
I was the reason for it all.
You weren't the
reason for anything.
You didn't do anything.
You didn't give her the gun.
The girl is sick, very sick.
But no one had noticed.
Even her own family.
How would you have known?
Apparently, she has been asking
for help for years.
By not talking to anyone, she was trying
to say "I have a problem".
But no one noticed.
Whatever.
Have a safe journey.
I apologize.
No crying.
You'll make me cry too.
Come on, get in the car.
Dad.
I thank you ever so much.
Why? What happened?
If it wasn't for you, there was no way
I could've got rid of Cemil.
We sat down, had a conversation
and sorted it all out. That's it.
Simple as that.
Mistakes are part of our lives.
Everybody makes mistakes.
Now, go on home. Take the
nice memories with you.
And tell your husband, if he gives you
hard time again, I am here.
- But I can't make it next time.
- Next time, I'll come over there.
O.K, off you go.
Have a safe journey.
O.K, we can go.
Staying away from
your daughter for years...
sending her to a boarding school so
that she wouldn't get mixed up...
with the likes of Cemil.
And what happens? In a big jungle like
Istanbul, she somehow ends up with him.
This is the price you pay
for keeping quiet years ago.
1 Week Later.
Nevra.
There is a delivery for you.
Come on darling, get up.
I made you something to eat.
I am not hungry.
Come on.
You'll make yourself ill.
Uskumru Street, Mebrure Blocks
Flat No:8 Beyo臒lu.
Door Lock Combination:1682.
Be there tomorrow morning.
I met a girl today.
He name is Nevra Elmas.
Today, 18th March.
It is Nevra's birthday.
I got her a present.
Me and Nevra share a secret.
Last night, I saw a shooting-star.
And I made a wish.
I wish they all die.
Save me Nevra.
Naimhan came around again today.
Salih beat me up.
Today, Nevra left Kambura.
I wanted her to meet Vural
before she moved away.
I wanted my best friend to see
the person whom I'll marry.
I am going to meet him in the woods.
I want you to meet him.
So, we went to the woods.
But once there,
Vural said something really bad.
He said "now that Reyhan kissed you,
would she kiss me too".
Her only objective is to be a
good cop and a good human being.
Then Cemil came.
Will you not talk to me Reyhan?
I think she swallowed
her tongue.
Oh, look who is here.
Is she your friend?
What's your name?
She is cute too.
Come on, let's leave
the lovebirds alone.
Let's take a walk.
Nevra!
Come on.
Let's sit somewhere.
I've never seen you around.
Where are you from?
Then Cemil appeared.
And I never saw Nevra again.
I hope Cemil hadn't done
anything bad to Nevra.
Cemil.
Kill.
Where have you been?
You left the door open too.
You look such a mess.
Where do you play, in woods?
Nevra?
Darling?
Has something happened?
Nevra?
Darling?
Answer me darling.
Has something happened?
No mum. Nothing happened.
Darling?
Cemil Havran will be available
to be killed tonight at 9 o'clock.
Hello Nevra.
I am Agah Beyo臒lu.
It looks good on you.
You can take the head off.
There are no cameras here.
They are not fitted yet.
It can get too hot in there.
I know it too well.
I remembered.
I remembered everything.
I am elated.
Because I had begun to forget.
I have a little health problem.
I'll tell you later.
I thought, this girl's not doing anything.
May be, she doesn't remember.
Despite me sending her messages.
I thought, may be Cemil didn't do
anything to her.
I mean, I prayed to God
that he didn't.
But when I read about
what he did to Reyhan...
I thought, almost certainly that
he must've hurt Nevra too.
But Nevra doesn't remember.
She erased the memory.
And for the right reasons too.
You must've been so frightened.
I think we'd go insane if we remembered
everything that we've been through.
But sometimes, remembering is the
best way to keep one's sanity.
Whatever.
Now that you remember...
it means that I can forget
with peace of mind.
Why is there nobody here?
Why is the place empty?
It is not completed.
It requires a little more work.
That's what Cemil said.
He is the financier.
He said "the place is empty at night.
I'll take you there, show you the fish".
I said "O.K, take me there,
let's see the fish.".
It's amazing, isn't it?
Kids will love it.
Very nice.
So, you had no problem getting in,
did you?
You used the entrance that I told you.
I had left the door open for you.
Yes, that's right.
Do you know what happened?
I said to myself...
stay out of it.
She can do it alone.
Than I thought, it'd be like
trying to learn to swim.
Like jumping off from a jetty.
I thought I should be with her
when she makes her debut.
I think it was a wise decision.
Don't you think?
You almost got lost,
heading in wrong direction.
- Have you ever met Reyhan?
- No.
Never met her.
But I read that diary
so many times...
I think I know Reyhan
better than I know myself.
Cemil's bodyguards are outside.
You must've seen them.
And there is the
security as well.
Before they begin to barge in,
I think we should make our move.
Come on.
This way.
Come.
Nevra...
come.
This way.
Cemil is here.
Come on.
How could you...
how could you do it?
What's up?
I can't do it.
I thought I could, but...
I can't kill another
human being.
But he is not human.
He is a monster.
No.
This is wrong.
I was in the police force.
This man should be arrested...
should be tried.
No, no. I think
you are confused.
He should be locked up.
You have to differentiate
law and justice.
They are two different things.
What you've just said is how it should be
done in accordance with the law.
Of course, providing that
there is law.
But justice is something different.
This is the justice.
What is justice anyway?
Self-defence?
Revenge?
Or belated self-defence?
This man ruined your life.
For example, think...
if you had a gun that day...
you would've shot Cemil to defend
yourself, wouldn't you?
Yes, you would. That's right.
Then or now.
What is the difference?
Then, you didn't have gun.
But now, you have one.
That's not why I became a cop.
That's exactly why
you became a cop.
You were neither able to save Reyhan,
nor yourself.
That's why you decided to become a
cop. It is so obvious.
I just...
I just wanted to be
a good person.
That's what I want too,
my dear child.
I want to be a good person, too.
This is a matter of
life and death.
He will die...
and we will live.
This is no justice.
It is a murder.
In this case, I'll help you
make a decision.
Put the gun down.
You have to make a choice.
You have to
kill either me or him.
Or I'll kill him right now.
Are you going to kill someone who
committed tens of murders...
or the man who hurt you
in most horrible way?
This man ruined your life.
These people ruined
Reyhan's life.
Reyhan is dead.
But they are still alive.
So, we might as well die and
let them live, what do you think?
This is a matter of
life and death.
Now...
I'll count to three...
then I'll shoot Cemil.
But who knows, you may pull the
trigger before I do.
I begin to count.
One.
Two.
1 Year Later.
Hi dad.
Hello darling.
How is the little one?
Give him to me, will you?
He only just fell asleep.
Where is your mum?
She is home.
She is exhausted,
trying to look after Ate艧.
I told her not to come.
Fine. Say hello.
I will.
- She said hello too.
- Bless her.
How is he?
What do you think?
Same.
Hi Uncle Agah.
Look what I got.
We'll put Miss Mebrure's
photo in it.
Why didn't you put the TV on?
It broke down again.
It keeps breaking down.
We're waiting for the repairman.
I am pregnant.
What if I have a baby girl?
I'd rather die than
having a daughter.
Don't be afraid baby.
You're not going to be born.
I will die.