LAWS OF REPUBLIC OF TURKEY
Poor Agah.
Munir?
Where are you, my boy?
Come on boy, it's time for breakfast.
Where are you?
Munir!
Where are you, sir?
Munir?
Have you gone to
a vacation or something?
No.
- So Munir has never been alone?
- No.
You haven't delayed his treatment?
No, I was giving him the cat food
you gave me for his...
- Acute kidney failure.
- Yes.
Did he die because of that?
Because of acute kidney failure.
Not just that.
The cat has also been dehydrated.
How?
MUNIR - MY LOVELY CAT
Man, what are we going to do with her?
She's been here for six months
and they are still talking about Nevra.
You are bothered because
you couldn't sleep with her.
Fuck off. What the fuck
are you talking about?
How many of my classmates is crazy
about coming here, do you know?
She literally came
here out of nowhere.
Do you know why?
Because she is a woman.
They called it positive discrimination.
What part of this is positive?
There are many strong men out there.
But for them it's necessary to put
Nevra into the spotlight.
Nevra, Nevra.
Fuck that thing
called 'human resources'.
What does it have to do with that?
Let's say you're out there with Nevra.
Would you trust Nevra?
Could you trust her?
I would trust more
if it was a man holding the gun.
- At least it would be clear what he'd do.
- See.
She can get the fuck out of here.
But she shouldn't go without a fuck.
Definitely.
Nurten, could you schedule
an appointment for next week, please?
Agah Beyoglu.
Thanks.
Now...
First thing we should do
is to inform your family.
They have to know about this first.
Your wife had passed away.
Yes.
It's been 10 years.
You have a daughter.
Yes, but she's not here,
she's living abroad.
Doesn't matter, you should inform her.
She may even call me,
I would like to talk to her.
Are we clear?
Yes.
Bon appetit.
I was thinking if we should redo the test,
in case the results are wrong.
I knew a guy named Necmi.
- They said he had cancer but then...
- I know.
I know.
It's hard to accept.
But the results are clear.
So are the symptoms.
For me, there is no doubt
in this diagnosis, Agah.
You have early stage Alzheimer's.
Yes, Dad?
Honey.
Dad, I can't do it.
I can't bear this anymore.
What happened?
I'll call the Chief Inspector.
Dad, I'm not a kid.
I don't want you to call anyone.
Then why did you call me?
Daughter?
Dau...
But doctor, I remember everything.
People forget things
when they have Alzheimer's.
I worked at the courthouse for 27 years.
If I went there now
I'd remember where every file is.
You are in the early stages.
Ask me then, anything.
My anniversary, friends' phone numbers...
I know them by heart.
My friends used to call me
I was like a phone book.
Back then we couldn't save the
numbers so I memorized them.
Agah.
You forgot to give water to your cat.
You forgot to feed him.
He starved to death.
How could I do that? How?
Poor Munir.
Look, this is an early diagnosis.
This will be of tremendous help
for the treatment.
We have patients
that lived 20 years after the diagnosis.
So rest assured.
Lived 20 years but
do they remember what they lived?
Alzheimer's directly affects memory.
It's one of the main reasons
for dementia.
But we will do all we can to stall this
and to keep your mind alive.
But sooner or later,
I will forget things, right?
Don't think about this now.
All my memories, experiences
will be erased, they will go away.
What will happen to me?
I mean...
Phone numbers aren't that important.
But what will happen to my personality?
Wouldn't it be erased too?
I will forget what kind of man I am.
You are alive but you don't exist.
How can someone endure this?
You may put this in your pocket.
I'll check the sound,
say something, please.
- What should I say? Hi.
- You can count the days of the week.
Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
Monday.
Tuesday, Wednesday.
Thursday, Friday.
That should do.
Let's get started.
I'll start with a basic question.
How does it feel
to be the only woman
working in an homicide bureau
with 140 staff members?
How does it feel?
Of course it's amazing.
I feel very privileged.
First of all, all of us here
are part of the homicide bureau.
It's impossible to see anything like
gender discrimination
or any other sexist approaches
in this institution.
Instead of any problems,
my friends are supporting me so much.
Which also means
another responsibility for me.
I am trying to do my best
to be worthy of their support.
- You studied public administration, right?
- Yes.
You even worked as a manager
in private sector
but then you decided to enroll
at the police academy.
Yes.
Why did you decide to
become a police officer?
I always thought about it because...
The greatest man I know
was a policeman... My father.
Who is currently retired.
You start to understand things
as you grow.
We barely saw our father.
Maybe at the weekends, just for a day.
I used to resent him.
I used to tell him that
he cares about other people more.
It seems that my father's job
is to care about other people.
And he ingrained
this concept in me so much
that I don't know
how to live any other way.
I actually repeat this
in every interview
but being a police officer
is not a job for me, never has been.
There is a concept called goodness.
For me, being a police officer means
being a part of that goodness.
That's my purpose...
To become a good person...
Deva!
Deva, answer me!
Where were you last night?
- Yes?
- Zuhal, hello my dear.
Wait a minute.
Tell me where were you last night.
Look at me!
Where are you going?
Come with me then.
You're not going!
Deva, I'll fuck you up!
Deva!
Yes?
My dear, is this a bad time? Did I
wake you up? What time is it there?
No, we are awake.
It's morning here. Is something wrong?
Do I need a reason to call my daughter?
I don't remember
the last time you called.
I'm the one who always calls.
- How is Deva?
- Deva is making me crazy!
Deva doesn't listen to me,
we can't even talk...
Dad, did you take
the vitamins I sent you?
I did, thank you.
But don't take them in high doses,
they may cause diabetes.
You take one.
And keep taking for three months...
Take them for three months
then stop taking for a month.
Then you take them for another
three months. Don't ignore it.
You didn't listen either.
What?
You didn't listen to us
when you were young either.
Is that so?
How would you know?
Deva is 16 years old.
When I was 16,
it was my fifth year on boarding school.
Remember that you sent me away?
Were you with me?
Was my mother there?
How would you know
if I had listened someone or not?
Did you know what I was doing?
Do you know
what I'm doing right now? No!
What can I do, my dear. You ran away to
the other side of the world, to Australia.
Dad, I'm getting a divorce.
Do you have any idea about this?
Dad, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to. I am very upset.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
Were you going to say something?
Were you...
I propose a toast for Nevra.
Different interviews, every week.
Finally, one of us is famous.
- Don't be silly, I'm not famous.
- Oh, wait, what was it?
To Nevra...
Who reassures friends
and awes foes.
To Nevra the po-po!
- What do you mean by po-po?
- She said po-po.
They say that in the movies all the time.
I've always wanted to say po-po.
Nice, are you finished? May I drink now?
All jokes aside, Nevra,
why did you become a police officer?
What do you mean 'why'?
It's a simple question.
Why did you become a fascist?
What are you saying?
Are you a troll?
Are you drunk?
Hang on, I am curious.
We meet very rarely
and you say these things.
You are actually asking me this...
Why didn't I get into
an insurance company?
Why I am not
in the ministry of finance?
Why I am not a banker?
Why I didn't act like a revolutionist
in college and then marry a rich guy
and sit on my ass
all day without working, like you?
Here is my answer...
I didn't want to.
I wanted to do...
I wanted to do something...
Something real.
What is that?
It's a simple question.
Why did you become a fascist?
I'm just kidding.
She's offended.
She was like that in college too.
Come on.
To reuniting after all these years.
To this beautiful night.
Mumtaz!
Agah, I'm here...
- Come, Agah. Come here.
- Excuse me.
That's why I don't come here.
The crowd, the drunks, the noise...
Bums in my apartment
are enough for me
and you brought me here.
You are used to this Agah.
I'm not. I couldn't get used to them.
How long have you lived here?
If you don't want to live here,
sell your apartments
and move away.
I won't go!
My last name is Beyoglu, they'll go.
- You will.
- I won't.
- You will brother!
- I won't go away.
I won't.
It's been so long since I saw you, Agah.
If I hadn't called you,
we were never going to meet.
What's wrong man?
Is there someone in your life?
Are you dating someone?
Are you ignoring us?
I'm not ignoring,
I just don't have time.
Fuck off. In our age,
time is all we have.
You are a joke.
Don't become introverted.
I can come and take you
to Bosphorus in mornings.
Come here.
- Yes, sir.
- Taste this.
- Does it taste bad?
- Just taste it.
I can tell the cook to prepare
another for you.
Why?
You didn't like it.
I didn't say that.
I said 'taste this'.
Why are you bothering him?
He's offering a new one.
That's not the point.
People don't listen to each other.
Maybe it tastes good and I don't get it.
Just go back to work. Come on.
- Go.
- No!
You surprised me.
Our peaceful, sweet Agah
scolding the waiter. I can't believe it.
That's not the point.
People don't listen
to each other properly.
Automatic answers without waiting.
Everything is automated now,
and they say we can't get along.
Don't get mad, okay.
Let's eat and go,
we'll go somewhere else.
I shouldn't come, it's late.
That's the automatic answer.
It's not late, it's 8:30 pm.
Muazzez also asked to see you.
She told me to bring you with me.
Our friends organized an event
that we should...
Where did that event come out from?
For god's sake! We're going.
That's it. My prostate destroyed me.
Destroyed me, made me miserable.
What am I doing here?
Just hang on,
I'll introduce you to someone.
So is that why you brought me here?
Did you set a trap for me?
That's Nukhet. And this is my friend
I told you about, Agah.
Nukhet.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Hello.
Nukhet has been taking tango lessons
and I told her that
there is a tango master here.
Come on...
You wouldn't mind
teaching Nukhet a thing or two, right?
It would be my pleasure.
So... They're doing
a great job, aren't they?
Yeah but, what's with us?
You are confused again,
why don't you drink something?
No, I don't want to.
I don't want to be like them.
They will be drunk soon.
They will embarrass themselves.
And they will regret everything
when they wake up.
Why would they regret?
They'll just get drunk.
They won't remember
anything in the morning.
How nice.
Since I won't remember,
I can do anything I want, is that so?
Exactly.
How nice.
I won't remember, so I can do anything.
Won't they wake up in the morning?
You're obsessed with this again, Agah.
Mumtaz!
Eat one's heart out...
Interesting sentence.
That's conscience.
It can eat your heart out, literally.
Forgetting forever.
Forgetting that you are forgetting.
Yes, that's it.
I will forget everything.
I won't remember anything.
To Agah.
I'm not forgetting.
One more please.
Agah!
Are you leaving?
I had an emergency.
You can call me whenever you want.
I am very glad to meet you.
So am I.
Have a good night.
ARDICHAN COURTHOUSE
PROPERTY AND EVIDENCE UNIT
There was no rape.
I accept the murder
but there was no rape.
INTERROGATION CAMERA
She is not the only fish in the sea.
- All the girls love me.
- Is that so?
- They melt with my one look.
- Really?
For example, that woman.
Which woman?
That police woman.
- She was running after me...
- Is that so?
Told me to stop.
She pulled her gun and I stopped.
Then I turned and looked at her.
- Do you know what happened?
- What?
- She looked like she literally melted.
- Really?
So, guys...
TOLGA YAZGAN CHIEF INSPECTOR
This incident stays in this room.
- Is that clear?
- It is clear, Chief.
Firuz?
What?
Yeah, it is Chief.
Guys...
Do you think I don't know about
your messing with Nevra?
No one will mess with Nevra
from now on!
Is that clear?
And you will be working on
documentation in administration.
No more field duties.
Guys, we are done.
Why are you still here?
Go.
CERTIFICATE
"Not Responsible" by Tom Jones.
CRIMINAL RECORDS
Your daughter hasn't called yet.
She's very busy, but I told her.
What did she say?
- She'll come here soon.
- Nice.
Are you taking your medicines?
- Yes.
- Nice.
Okay.
Recently...
Last week...
Have you gotten angry for no reason?
Something like a tantrum.
- Not really.
- Nice.
I'm asking this because
this tantrum may occur any time.
You may feel insecure.
You may be sensitive about something
that you haven't cared about before.
These things may happen.
If something like this happens,
take a note.
Have you started
doing your homework?
Have you started taking notes?
MY NAMES IS AGAH BEYOGLU.
I THREW MY TV INTO THE STREET.
- I'm taking notes, yes.
- Very good.
Okay, what about physical activities?
You were going to walk.
You should make an effort,
I said simple sports may also do.
Yes, I am doing those things.
- I'm very active nowadays.
- Very good.
Okay, let's talk about mental activities.
We should activate your brain neurons
that have never worked until now.
How will we do that?
For example...
One of my patients was familiar
with Latin languages.
And she started learning Japanese.
And she benefited a lot from it.
You want me to learn Japanese?
No.
Everyone has a different interest.
There must be something that
you always wanted to do but you couldn't.
There are many things I want to do.
That's it, very good.
Look, whatever it is,
however it is done...
You will start doing it
with utmost planning.
Look, planning is the key word here.
You should have daily,
weekly, monthly plans.
You should check if you are
following those plans accordingly.
You won't cut corners.
You'll make it complicated.
You'll detail it.
Let's assume that you'll water a plant.
You'll spray every leaf of that plant,
one by one, patiently.
You should enjoy what you're doing.
Agah, you'll do that
in such an impeccable way
that the plant won't be able to tell
if it's raining or you're watering it.
Are we clear?
- We are clear.
- Nice.
Very nice.
Okay, now tell me...
How have you been feeling lately?
I've never felt so good.
SECURITY CLEARANCE
IDENTIFICATION CARD COPY
Damn it.
- What?
- You are a mechanic, so you should know.
Why are mechanics always late?
What?
Our elevator mechanic for instance,
we waited for so long but he didn't come.
Then he came, but he was late.
Who are you,
what are you saying?
Are we going to wait for mechanics
our whole lives?
- Go away, it's so late...
- No, I was going to say that...
You... Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you going in?
Just a sec...
You are going to write
these down on computer.
Good morning to you too.
TO THE MINISTRY OF INTERIOR AFFAIRS
Come in!
What's this?
My resignation, sir.
Really, I didn't get it...
I can see that. I am asking why.
I have to do that...
It's because of personal reasons.
You'll put it in process.
I haven't had my coffee yet.
I'm not awake yet.
Do you know what I'll do?
I'll take your resignation
and put it in my drawer.
And I'll give you five days off.
Go home, get some rest,
think this through,
and if you still want to resign
after five days, I'll accept it.
I'll put your paper in process. Okay?
- But, Chief...
- Nevra!
Did you know that it was me
who wanted you here at the bureau?
I chose you from 50 girls.
It wasn't because your father was a cop.
Do you know why?
Because among those 50,
it was only you determined to be
a cop although
you had a bright future in your job.
I told myself that she was crazy
and I needed someone crazy here.
Go home and think.
Yes?
Turn it down!
She's driving me crazy.
She got crazy
now she's making me crazy.
How can I help you?
I'm Agah, Agah Beyoglu,
from the courthouse.
- From the secretary.
- Yes.
It has been years...
I was thinking
that you somehow look familiar.
I never forget a face that I saw.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Come, come in.
We were just having dinner.
- Are you hungry? I can prepare for...
- No, thank you.
I'm sorry, it's a bit messy.
There was a girl cleaning the house
but she ran away because of her.
Everyone runs away.
Who would tolerate this?
Why don't you take your coat off?
No thanks, I caught a cold.
- Get well soon.
- Thanks.
It's been 20 years, right?
I guess so.
Do you remember Agah?
When I was working on archives.
Celal from assize court
recommended Agah, God bless him.
- He died too...
- Really, may he rest in peace.
He went there every weekend.
- Was it Kambura?
- Yes, it was Kambura.
Agah was working at the secretariat
at Kambura Courthouse.
You opened many files for me right?
We went there with you once.
We ate trout near the river,
remember?
- She's been like this for four years.
- What's wrong with her?
It's bad, Agah, bad.
She has Alzheimer's.
Get well soon.
She won't get well.
Look at her. She wasn't someone
to be like this.
She's ruined.
She ruined us too.
Our daughter is living in Madrid.
We went to visit her.
We watched a flamenco show there.
All these things are from there.
How do they say...
Feza's only connection to life is these.
I don't know why,
her memory only kept these.
Otherwise she neither
knows me nor our girl.
Come on.
I take care of everything.
I even clean her bottom.
Like I can take care after myself.
So, Agah.
- Are you retired?
- Yes.
What was your wife's name?
Mebrure.
She passed away too.
May she rest in peace.
Thank you.
So Agah, why did you come here?
How did you find this place?
We thought weather is better on this side.
It's also far away from the crowds.
May I use the bathroom
if you don't mind?
I've come a long way.
Yes, sure.
I have the same problem.
My bladder and all are sagged...
Look, it's over there.
Come on, drink.
Drink it woman!
- Drink it, come on!
- Excuse me.
Do you have farsighted glasses?
Yes, over there.
- It's on the shelf.
- Thanks, I forgot mine.
I'm running out of patience,
just take one sip!
Come on, at least take one sip.
So Agah,
what are you doing around here?
I had work to do.
If there is something we can do,
just say it. Don't be shy.
Yes, of course. I will.
I was nine years old.
The year was 1961.
My mom had baked a cake
for my birthday.
That was the first time.
I made a wish blowing out candles.
My wish was this...
Back then,
Yuri Gagarin was going to be
the first man going to space.
And I wished he would take me with him.
I believed so much
that my wish will come true,
I prepared a bag and started waiting.
I thought they will come from
The Soviet Embassy to get me.
But I was hearing that
they were communists.
People were saying
"Careful, they are communists."
I said then I'll be one too.
During that time
college students were staying
on the first floor.
My mom was calling them
communists too
and I knew they had
hidden books in our cellar.
I went there and stole one.
Poems of Nazim Hikmet.
I found the shortest one
and memorized it.
I thought if the Russians came,
I'd read this poem to them
and they'd think
I was one of them and take me.
Chief?
Anyways...
The date was April 12th.
The space shuttle
was going to be launched.
Vostok-1.
But no one had come for me.
I thought they forgot about me.
The shuttle was launched.
Everyone was praying for
the shuttle to go through the atmosphere.
Only I was praying for it
to return half way around to take me.
And maybe the Americans
were praying for Vostok
to not go into the space.
Whatever.
All day long,
near the radio,
I read that poem silently.
My head is a foamy cloud.
My inside and outside is a sea.
I'm a walnut tree in Gulhane Park.
An old walnut tree.
With long branches and pieces.
Neither you are aware of this
nor is the police.
I MET A GIRL YESTERDAY.
HER NAME WAS NEVRA ELMAS.
Whenever I read this poem
I feel like I go to space.
I am 65 years old now.
I made a wish again, just like a child.
An impossible wish, of course.
Do you know what I wished for?
To become a good person.
Dad, I guess you are sleeping.
It's over, I can't tolerate this man no
more. We are moving back to Istanbul.
We are coming together with Deva.
I'll call you later.
Good night.
FIRST FEMALE POLICE OFFICER
OF HOMICIDE BUREAU
HER ONLY GOAL IS TO BE A GOOD
POLICEMAN AND A GOOD PERSON