You've told me about your start-up idea over a 100 times now.
Why don't you do something about it?
How will I get the funding, Bhati?
Everyone's luck isn't as good as your's.
What are you?
What do you mean
You are a beer.
I will resign right now.
My B-Plan is going to get selected?
You should... -never quit
Guys!!!
I quit!!!
Now let's just begin with the start-up
We've only been talking about it since 3rd year. -Naveen we've already discussed this.
That by the time you come back from Brazil, after a
year and a half, Yogi will make some contacts here.
Guys try to understand, I can't leave my job right now.
People are realizing my potential.
I’m a valuable employee to the company.
Listen to me.
A new Silicon Valley is being upstaged at Hiranandani here!
And you're still writing codes on Python.
Whenever graduates of this country, get bored by their 9 to 5 jobs...
So, to get out, they come up with only three options for themselves.
MBA
IAS
or Start-Up.
Beijing.
We're beginning our expansion there, 6 months ahead of schedule.
Apointment within a week.
We need someone smart over there...
Like you.
Now is the real choice.
One in hand is obviously better than one not-so-sure in the bush.
He's the one who requested me to come here.
He...
... had to leave urgently.
Let me explain it to you, with beer today.
It won't burn, even if it spills.
You're back!!!
I knew it, you'd come!
Akhil gave us the wrong information!
Our name's not on the winner's list!
But wait...
What about my salary now?
MOM! I don't want to get married!!!
I'm only 27. Not even old enough to get married!
Don't "Shona beta" me!
Mummy... Mummy, don't lie to me, OK?
You don't have any Thyroid cancer!
OK wait... I'm getting another call.
Yeah... Wait! Wait!
Yeah Aarti?
Actually no. I'm still in a client meeting.
Where are you?
Oh, you've already reached?
Where?
OK. OK.
You've just reached, then?
No, no, no...
My client meeting... can be cancelled!
Yeah, I'm on my way!
Let's go.
We've to go around and then come back here!
Come on!
Come on already!
Hi!
Sorry, I got a little late.
Hope I didn't keep you waiting for long!
No!
Nice ambience!
Did you order anything?
Akhilesh, 2 cappuccinos!
No... I don't want to have anything!
No, no. Both are for me.
I'll drink one now, and the other one later, once it gets cold.
These guys charge 100 bucks extra for cold coffee!
By the way...
You look...
Quite different from your pictures!
I know!
I'm not photogenic!
I mean...
I look good in real life!
But my pictures, don't come out that great!
You've met guys before... like this?
Yes!
2-3 times
Me too!
6 times!!!
You know...
Since I've completed my P.G. from IIM Indore?
Mom's had girls lined up for me to meet!
I told her, "Mom...
...I can't marry right now!...
...I want to explore the world...
...Travel with friends...
...Scuba dive...
...Sky dive"
I'm telling you... You too should stop with this marraige shabang!
Marriage doesn't even make sense
Youngsters like us should have fun!
It's a good thing actually, that my mom forcefully made me a profie.
Or else, we wouldn't have been on this date!
Wait a minute!
Your mom... made your...
Tinder profile?
Tinder?
No, no. Shaadi.com
You're..
Hi.
Nikita?
Nikita.
Oh...
Oh shit... shit!
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I got confused!
It's a good thing he showed up early!
We were about to get...
WE were about to get married!
Saurabh Mandal!
I'm a marketing head in Technity.
And what do you do?
Today's Thursday?
Yes.
On Thursdays I...
...do legs!
Gym!!!
Nice... Nice
Please have a seat! Enjoy!
Enjoy!
And have fun also.
Mr. Saurabh?
Aarti?
Actually, Aarti. I wanted to clear something first, before we start.
Mr. Saurabh, I know what you want to say.
That you've had girlfriends before this, isn't it?
I know.
No, not really. That's not it.
How did you know that I like cappuccino?
Aarti, look...
I didn't want to come here in the first place
It's just that my mom wanted me to be here.
You know how parents pressurize you
Your...
Your moustache is just like Anil Kapoor's!
No look, Aarti...
Actually, I can't go ahead with this marriage!
Mr. Saurabh, I understand your reluctance!
How much sugar?
One.
Just like me!
Look, if I were to tell you the truth...
I too, had two boyfriends before this
And I got intimate with them, as well!
But we didn't do anything "dirty".
That I will do...
...only with my husband.
After all, I'm an Indian!
How can I forget my roots and culture
Aarti. No doubt, you're a very nice girl...
Panditji too, says the same
No, no. Now...
Now, I...
Mr. Saurabh, it's a yes for me.
Just...
Like the last guy...
Don't hide anything from me!
Why... What did the last one hide?
My marriage with him had been confirmed.
But just a few days before the engagement...
...dad got to know that...
...he was quitting a stable job to begin a start-up!
And the marriage got canned, then and there.
That's when I saw your profile and...
So what, if he was going to begin a start-up?
Why would any girl marry a "start-up guy"?
Now... If the company doesn't do well...
Will I have to leave my household chores and go do a job?
Tell me Mr. Saurabh?
Actually, Aarti...
This is exactly, what I wanted to tell you about...
No laundry from tomorrow!
No maid from tomorrow!
No milk from tomorrow!
Even, no newspaper from tomorrow!
Gym membership will be cancelled!
Metros will be used instead of the car!
Electricity will be saved!
Internet speed will be reduced from 8mbps to 1mbps!
No. No. No. No dude.
Atleast let the net speed stay!
Do you not want Jeetu, then?
If we don't save enough, how will we ensure his salary?
Alright then. Let's reduce the speed from 8mbps to 4mbps.
Table top-ups will be stopped!
Ordering food from restaurants will be stopped!
Will be absolutely stopped!
Infact, all kinds of luxury expenditures will be absolutely stopped!
What's the total?
Three thousand
Seven hundred
Twenty-five.
And adding my share to it...
Seven thousand
Four hundred
Fifty.
And how much is Jeetu's salary?
One lac
Thirty seven thousand
Five hundred.
Superb plan!
We'll save for a year and a half...
...and shell out one month's salary!
"Alright!"
Madal, what are you doing dude?
What?
What are you doing?
Music!
Loud music!
Can't hear a thing!
You carrry on!
"Alright!"
What I'm saying is...
Let's add another 50 bucks to this...
And hire some intern to do the coding.
Yogi, an intern will replace Jeetu, now?
We need people with some work experience in our compnay!
People who've worked at some senior level!
Someone who can build a team in the future...
Someone who can strategize!
Naveen...
Did you find that t-shirt of mine?
What t-shirt?
The 'InfoCom' one.
Where I'd an experience of 4 years?
As a Senior Consultant!
Since I'd BUILT a team there...
They'd gifted that t-shirt to me.
I don't know dude. We're busy right now!
Shit!
Now, I'll have to strategize what to wear!
What do we do then?
Dude, I think we're getting a little impatient here!
I was thinking, what if...
Jeetu manages to convince Soumya!
Naveen...
She's his wife!
She gives him sex!
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
Trust me.
This is all coming from experience!
Look Yogi...
Without Jeetu, we have no company.
Naveen...
We've no jobs.
We have to start a company, with or without Jeetu.
Yogi...
What are you doing?
Did you think about it?
I'd asked you something, yesterday?
What'd you asked?
That thing...
Can I be part of your start-up?
WHAT?
WHY?
What do you mean by "Why?"?
You all are engineers!
You need an MBA!
How will you'll run a company without business expertise?
Mandal, I'll let you know!
Give me some time.
It's a very important professional decision!
I'll let you know, alright? -OK
So will you send me a mail, or you'll communicate verbally?
Should I expect a call by Friday?
I'll...
Why Friday? He's a sweet kid!
Let's do your G.D. and P.I. today itself!
And the results tomorrow.
Personal interview, today?
Iit's already 10. When will I prepare...
Fuck, it's 10 already?
I'm going to get killed!
What if it's 10?
'Jhalak' comes up only at 10 in the night!
No Yogi! I've to meet Shreya. If I get late, she'll screw me!
Haven't you told her already, about our start-up?
Where have I met her, since so many days?
MANDAL!
Where's my face-wash dude?
The 'Kurule' medical therapy one?
Don't use that!
I used it and 4 of my pimples combined into a boil!
No dude. My face-wash!
Will you get it, or should we disqualify you before the interview round, itself?
I was just about to go!
Dude, look...
There's this coder...
He's in the third year.
He's the son of the paternal uncle of a mutual friend!
He's almost family!
Let's get him onboard. I assure you, he'll rock!
Look, Yogi!
A comapny's all about the people in it.
You think, any college guy can replace Jeetu...
If that's how randomly we want to hire people, why don't we hire Mandal as well?
Sorry to disturb your important meeting!
But I hope you take the right decision!
I also love Jeetu!
Though 3 years late, I've passed by cheating from his answer sheet.
We definitely want him onboard.
But till the time we do not ensure his salary, we need a coder.
I'm telling you...
Let's go meet this guy...
And let's get the fucking thing started!
OK, alright.
Let me meet Shreya for now.
After that, let's go meet this guy, in the afternoon. OK?
How do I look?
Fair!
OK. You make a move, I'll go meet Shreya and then catch you!
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Hello?
Naveen!!! - Hey Shreya!
You still haven't upgraded your internet, have you?
How are you?
You've always been and always will be a miser!
Can you see me?
Wait a second.
You can see me?
I can see you now.
Oh God, what is that shirt you're wearing?
Have you borrowed it from the gardenkeeper?
Actually, his and mine shirt size is the same. So it fit me!
By the way, his wife wears XL. Looks like that too, will fit you!
If only you had something XL, no?
Baby, I have my heart.
My heart is so big.
OK, you should know, that I haven't been looking for
wi-fi all over Bhutan, to listen to all these ridicules.
Yeah, as if I asked to go to Bhutan!
Meditation is being learnt, with Consultancy Project only as an excuse.
If it's meditation that you wanted to learn, you could've done that
just by waking up in the mornings to watch 'Ramdev baba' on the T.V.
Yeah, because I just love old, hairy men sweating at 6 in the morning!
Why do you think I sleep with you, baby?
Baby, I thought you sleep with me, because not
a lot of men, believe in doing charity, no?
Oh, you want me to start counting down on the charity cases?
Should we start listing your dating history, now? -No, no, no, no...
When is my true love, by tearing through clouds...
Landing on the grounds of this country, we call India!
Four O'clock!
Sharp!
You're coming to get me, right?
Ok, I've a meeting at 8 and I've something very important to tell you.
Oh! Even I've something very important to tell you.
OK, I'll go first. Please. Please. Let me go first!
OK, go. As if I have a choice.
Blurt out!
Actually...
Naveen, I'm pregnant.
Very nice!
Who's child is it?
I don't know...
It could be anyone's.
It could be yours.
It could be Raghav's. It could be Vaibhav's.
Oh, it could even be the monastery monk's.
Do you have anything important to say or are you just eating into my internet pack?
No. No. No. I do have something important to say.
But I'd thought, that I'd keep it a surprise.
Should I tell you?
What? You bought handcuffs?
Yeah, but apart from that...
So!
There's this guy, who's leaving his girlfriend and moving to Brazil.
This girl, decides to start looking for a job.
In Brazil.
And, guess what?
She finds herself in the final shortlist.
Shreya! Wait!
...last telephonic interview is left, but after that...
Shreya, wait.
...going to live with you in Rio, bitch! - Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait Shreya...
This is exactly what I wanted to give you news about.
Tell me.
Uh...
What are you doing...
I was just about to wash them up
How much will you work, after all!
Anyway, the machine isn't workiing and the maid hasn't come...
It hardly takes time...
I washed them...
What's the deal? Suddenly today...
It isn't really "suddenly"!
I'd cooked chicken, day before!
And last night, I'd chopped the vegetables.
In a household, if 2 people work in unison, it becomes easy.
These days, these machines have come up...
Otherwise...
Our dads used to do it all, by hands.
Why don't you go...
Go do your prayers. I'll come, make tea, once I'm done here.
Do you have something, to tell me?
No!
Why would you think so?
Give me.
Naveen... had called...
Yogi and Naveen have quit their jobs...
They're going to begin their own start-up...
They were asking me... as well
You go on downstairs. I'll get done here.
So what were you saying?
What was I saying...
No...
Naveen and the guys were asking me as well...
To quit my job and join them as the C.T.O.
But now...
This... When did you buy this?
This is an old one!
Had gotten it from my parents'.
No... I was saying... These colors suit you... They come out very well!
So what did you say?
I said, I'll think about it... Now things like...
...these can't just be decided in the moment.
So I wanted to talk to you as well, about this.
Will you be benefited, in your career?
If the start-up goes big, then there's a benefit...
Otherwise, it's just a risk!
Well, the work will be a lot of fun...
It'll be interesting but the salary...
I think you should do it.
What?
You're not doing it right...
Give it to me!
No...
What were you saying?
I think, you should do it.
No...
You don't have any problem?
I was trying to say, that once...
...I quit my job, our plan to buy a house will be delayed.
So, what's the hurry in buying a house?
Anyway, this is such a nice house.
There's such a big terrace!
And then the chances of your growth, are also so much more.
I won't even get an L.T.A.
We'll have to drop our Mauritius trip, as well.
We'll go to Mahabaleshwar, instead.
Shalini's husband owns a resort there.
But the salary issue will still persist.
Our savings are good enough.
Anyway, it's been 5 months since I've come to Mumbai.
I'm thinking...
...of getting a good job for myself.
How do you hang these? By clips?
I thought, you wouldn't agree to this.
I even had my flowcharts ready, so that I could convince you!
I've only been thinking about this, since Monday.
All the effort, went waste!
Don't worry.
None of your effort will go waste.
Anyway...
You'll have to talk to your dad about this...
You wouldn't quit your job, without asking him, would you?
I was asking you to do it properly!
Now I'll have to wash, all the clothes again!
Even the maid's not come today!
...got down all the lectures, and uploaded youporn videos, instead.
Our guy's won the IBM code competition, twice over...
...in a row.
Legend says that he got a congratulatory mail from Eric Schmidt, himself.
But he doesn't have random expectations, does he?
He knows, he won't get anything more than the basic stipend, right?
Dude, relax! He's our kid!
We'll offer him a couple of treats at Barbeque Nation and he'll say yes!
I told him, it's an Environment Science lecture motherf**ker...
If not proxy, should I whoop your arse?
Is Rohan Negi's room this way?
Is he expecting you?
Yes.
Follow me!
You go to hell!
I don't want to see your face again!
You aren't satisfied only with foreplay, are you?
You have to have this afterplay of melodrama!
She got mad because it was strawberry.
It isn't ice-cream that you'd get almond and pistachio flavours!
Does the uncle party, have matchsticks?
Go run to the canteen. It's time!
Uncle, give him a 100 bucks.
Give it.
Follow me!
I can't go beyond this point.
Deposit your mobiles, pendrives, hard-disks and any other storage devices.
There's a door ahead...
Knock it.
Twice!
And then wait.
Do you smoke?
No.
Kids!
Yes?
Tell chintu, that 'Yogi bhaiyaa' is here, to give him an internship.
Come in.
Sit.
He's in the middle of something...
Give him 75.
Minutes?
Headshots!
Despite being the class monitor, my performance from class 6 to class 12 steadily increased...
From 72.3% to 87.8%
This goes to show...
I'm responsible...
...persistent...
...dedicated, motivated, over...
Under-rated dude!
Responsible, persistent, motivated, dedicated, under...
Hi Shreya!
Hi Mandal!
Hi...
Sorry, I didn't mean to disturb your paranormal powerpoint fantasy.
I'll just sneak into Naveen's room and lock the door, so you can't come in!
No. No. No.
Actually, I was waiting for you!
Naveen'd told me that you're going to come.
In that blazer and towel?
You aren't a serial killer Mandal, are you?
Only, if looks could kill!
Please have a seat!
Actually, if I get tensed, I need to have a bath!
Better?
Congratulations Mandal.
You've reached a new level of creepy!
Soo...
Naveen's quit his job to...
Yeah, I know. He's told me everything.
And I too, want to...
Everything!
Soo...
So?
Shreya. We're friends, aren't we?
Facebook-wise or in real life?
Joke!
Do you remember?
Last month, early morning...
You wanted a Xerox of your PAN card.
Naveen was sleeping.
So you asked me for help.
I was getting late for work...
I didn't have any change on me...
I still went and got the Xerox done.
Look, I've this one philosophy...
Friends should always help each other!
No. No. No. No. No.
One second.
You want me to convince Naveen to hire you?
No.
Sorry.
Not gonna happen.
Anyway, I can't convince him. Instead, he'll end up convincing me!
Shreya... Trust me!
He can never convince you!
A man can never convince a woman, who gives him...
...Love!
And if...
He doesn't budge...
You know...
Use your methods!
What methods?
Intercourse
What?
Mandal, have you gone nuts?
Just for a 1 buck Xerox...
It's actually 2 bucks. One for each side!
I'm worth much more than that!
OK? I'm sorry.
I would've helped you with anything else, but with this, I can't! Sorry.
Naveen needs my help!
Yogi keeps winding him up against me!
I really want to be a part of this!
I know, I'm gonna regret this.
OK.
Alright.
Tell me one thing.
When do...
You call for a plumber?
That wasn't me...
Naveen thinks that I broke his jet spray and then...
No. I mean hypothetically.
I mean...
When would anyone, call for a plumber?
One calls for the plumber when a tap's broken.
Right. And what if a tap isn't broken?
Then why call the plumber?
Exactly!
Look.
In this situation...
You're the plumber and Naveen's start-up doesn't have any broken tap.
Irrespective of, however great, the work you're doing in life is...
Unless, your inclusion doesn't solve any of their problems...
They don't need you!
See... You need to figure out what they need.
You also need a bigger towel, dude!
No. No.
Don't shy away!
I'm wearing my underwear!
Sorry.
Not wearing any!
F**K!
Yogi!
And...
You must be Naveen.
How are you 'chintu'? I saw you at the threading ceremony, last.
Not 'chintu'.
Dungeon Master.
There's an underscore between Dungeon and Master.
So...
You guys want me to work for your company.
You tell him.
We were interested in discussing the possibilities...
I looked into your idea.
It's... quite interesting actually.
Looked into?
But, I haven't sent you any mail, as yet!
But you'd mailed NASSCOM, hadn't you?
You see...
Privacy on mail is a myth my friend!
So... If I join you guys...
How do I benefit?
What do I get?
Opportunity!
Of course, there'll also be a stipend initially.
About... 7K.
8... 8K. Yeah.
And as we grow, your monetory compensation will obviously increase...
Do you know what's the prize money for the Internation Counter Strike competition?
How much?
475,000...
Dollars.
4... 4 times 6 is 24...
And you won that?
Twice!
4... 4 times 2 is 8... 8 times 6 is 48...
So theoritically... I can hire you guys.
But not the other way round.
I want 30% equity...
And... veto on product design.
Dungeon_master@hotmail.com
Don't forget the underscore.
Mail me by Monday.
Or just save it in your drafts.
I'll read it.
I think we need Jeetu.
Do you think we need Jeetu?
We need Jeetu.
We'll have to first change the passwords for all our accounts.
What's up, start-up founder?
Your battery looks dead after listeninig to the deal.
What's up, entrepreneur uncle?
Pass on some stake to us as well!
Listen up Jeetu. There's no other way out. You have to join in.
I can't join in.
Sorry.
I told you!
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
Noo!
Suamya has agreed.
SO?
Ohh!
What?
Did you try talking to him?
That's all I've been able to do since I was 1.5 years old. TRY to talk!
With whom?
Haven't you watched 'Udaan'?
Ohhhh!
Your dad?
He's alcoholic?
He's not alcoholic...
Why are you scared of your dad? Are you still a kid?
Naveen. Even my passbook is with him.
If my salary doesn't get credited on the 1st of the next month...
My life will get debited.
You guys, atleast, start.
I'll see. I'll try putting in a couple of hours of work, everyday after my job.
"You guys start", "I'll see". Are you mad?
This way, even the Beta version won't be ready in 6 months.
There's so much to do.
Excuse me!
Aren't you the guys launching the coolest company of Indian history?
Hey! The start-up wags are here. -Hey!
The gold-diggers are here even before the money.
Listen, you need to get a better CEO, though!
Don't know about the coolest, but could be most short-lived for sure!
Don't say such bad things on a good day like this, Jeetu.
This is for you'll.
So what's up, Jeetu?
What are you doing here?
I've come here for the interview!
Mandal, that was only a joke. There's no interview happening.
I know. I know.
I know jokes.
I've taken improv. comedy classes for a month.
Is this taken? -Yes.
OK!
Don't you get it, motherf**ker?
Anyway our battery's down...
This is our shit, Madal!
We don't need you.
Trust me.
You need me!
Infact without me...
You don't have a company!
OK, go get a chair.
We'll interview you right away!
Just hear him out na, once.
Tell me.
Why should we hire you?
You know, as an MBA...
I've always had a clarity about my R&Rs.
One of my KRA has been problem...
We don't need a marketing manager. We need a coder...
Thanks for applying. You interview's over.
No. No. No. One second.
I can solve your problem.
I can give you something, which you need.
I can give you Jeetu!
How?
Till the time, you'll don't get an investment...
I'll pay for Jeetu's salary.
A part of it through my salary and a part through my savings.
But I'll ensure that, Jeetu keeps getting as much as he gets from his company.
Mandal. Why would you do these things for us?
Not for you guys...
I'll do it for myself!
You guys are the best friends I've ever had.
I know, apart from Naveen...
We've not interacted as much...
But I've always thought, that the four of us are a very good team.
You know when I'd seen 'Zindagi Milegi Na Dobara'
I'd decided that...
The four of us too, just like them...
Would go on a trip.
But ZNMD had only 3 guys.
OK. Then... like 'Dil Chahta Hai'.
Again, only 3 guys, Mandal.
'Rock On' definitely had 4 guys.
The 4th one, gets cancer and dies. Only 3 remain.
The point is, if I join your start-up...
Then Jeetu can work full-time with us.
All MBAs... are not that bad.
Soo...
Is somebody going to say something, or are we sitting just like this for the next hour?
Don't worry, guys.
It won't be that bad.
Backstreet Boys... Alright!
Cheers!
And then there were four!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Finally, he's made himself useful!
So, Jeetu's back!
Important point - This news doesn't get out of here!
If dad gets to know... - Stop going "Dad. Dad."
Once we're a million dollar company, even your dad will chill out!
And also, I've done some research and thought of a few names for our compnay.
I think, our compnay name should have 'le' in it!
Like Google had 'gle', Apple has 'ple', Oracle has 'cle'
What non-sense are you talking? You've started with your stupid marketing logics again!
Please don't throw fries on me. I'm the marketing manager!
Oops! Sorry.
Careful! Why are you throwing it on me?
So, this is your million dollar team?
Congrats