Remember...
The date was April 12th.
The space shuttle
is about to be launched. Vostok 1.
He used to launch shuttles,
but still no one comes around.
A STAR FELL FROM THE SKY
I MADE A WISH
I WISHED THEY ALL DIED
Mom, I need to ask you something.
Why did you lie that day?
You and Selim, when I asked you
how that house burned down?
Why would I lie?
You're going to make a decision.
Will I see your face again?
It's Firuz! Don't shoot!
I'm coming out!
I was on night duty when a man came by.
I remember everything he said to me.
"You will forget about this.
Or you will disappear," he said.
- Tell me you're letting me go.
- Let's say I let you go.
Will everything you've done
all these years also let you go?
I asked you if you're mafia, son!
Yeah. We are. So what?
Good. Here's your mafia.
PERSONAL
Bro...
This is an incredible idea, Deva.
- You see it, right?
- Yeah. I see it.
How many people have written in?
It's as if they've waited
their whole lives for this moment.
Waiting for someone
to ask them their opinion.
There are some great replies here.
Here are some. Listen up.
Whom would you like Dog Slayer to kill?
He should kill the people
who sit around on park benches,
eating nuts
and scattering trash everywhere.
Here's another one.
Wouldn't it be great if he killed
the ones who refuse to stop honking?
It would be.
Here's another one.
You know how
when you're waiting in line
and the person behind you
is standing too close to you?
He should kill them
so we can finally breathe.
Let me see.
"Dear Dog Slayer..."
My mom forbade me
from going on the internet
"because I'm doing bad at school.
Could you please kill my mom?"
- So it says.
- He wants him to kill his mom?
It seems so. Look at his nickname.
Vengeful generation.
So this Mehmet Yurtgil went to the doctor.
He threatened the doctor
and shut him up by scaring him.
And then, he forces him
to write this report about Ufuk.
- Is that so?
- Yes, sir.
And the first victim
is this Mehmet Yurtgil.
You remember when I told you that
I'd picked you from among 50 women?
Thank you for not letting me down.
I have another thing to thank you on.
The other day,
when we were talking in my room
and I told you that what's happening
might have nothing to do with Kambura...
You know how you asked me for the file?
How you didn't give up on it?
Thank you for that, as well.
Good job. We're getting closer.
What did the good sir write this time?
They all had
the same word written on them.
"Personal."
"Personal." So he killed them
for his own reasons, huh?
- Seems so.
- Then...
Whom did he kill all these people for?
Who are they?
Chief, these men had 80 priors.
Accessory. Forgery.
Their rap sheet is something to behold.
But they're not connected to Kambura.
No fingerprints, either.
But the crime was caught on CCTV.
Let me guess. Cat costume.
Yes.
We were able to follow him a long while
through neighborhood shops' cameras.
He went in and out of a few streets.
He acted like he wasn't sure
which way he was supposed to be headed.
He went into a construction site, because
that whole area is a construction site
and there are no cameras looking inside,
we lost the suspect.
We lost him because of
the urban transformation project.
He had his escape planned.
Those construction sites are like
black holes in the middle of our cities.
This is bad. This is really bad.
This is really bad.
Everyone's getting on the ride.
Whoever has a bone to pick
will shoot, kill, and blame him!
So we have the Kambura connection.
What do you think?
Tayyar Kaymak,
who died in the house that night,
has a brother, Hamza Kaymak.
We think he might know something.
Maybe he's the killer.
Maybe he wants to avenge his brother.
No, sir.
He was in prison for mugging someone
while the murders were being committed.
He's in prison, huh? Fine. Alright.
But he has to know something.
He's Tayyar's brother after all, right?
We need to find out what he knows.
Go to his prison and talk to him.
He escaped.
He fled the night when we were trying
to get Ufuk out of Kambura.
There's a manhunt for him right now.
No way...
See, Sefa? Another escape.
Come on, Chief.
It was a lapse of judgement.
He handed himself in.
How could I've known he'd try that?
Anyway. Fine.
Here's what we're going to do.
Nevra, you go after Tayyar's brother.
Get print-outs of his mugshot.
Spread them around.
If he's out there,
someone will have seen him.
Sefa, you gather more information
on the house that burned down.
Anyone who remembers
or knows something about that night...
Get the whole Kambura
in here for interrogation.
- Let's go.
- Right away, Chief.
This is not going to work out.
What if I get really sick
before I do all these people in?
Then...
First...
Hello.
Do you have a last wish?
No?
You do?
Forgive me, but I don't give a toss.
Hello?
Yes?
Who?
Who, did you say?
- Hamza Kaymak, right?
- Yes, Ates, it's really urgent.
Don't worry. His photos
will be everywhere in half an hour.
Thank you.
When will I see you?
I don't know when
I'll be able to get out of here.
Do you go home at all?
- Sometimes, yes.
- Can I come?
Come.
Alright.
- Firuz...
- Yeah?
What do you have?
Firuz, this won't get me
in trouble, right?
Come on, Fiko!
You've known me for years.
Relax. You'll be fine.
What is this? What did you find?
I found some blood on the crime scene
that doesn't belong to the victims.
Probably belongs to the suspect.
- Is this the DNA report on it?
- Yes.
Good.
Here.
Don't spend it all in one place.
This isn't in the file
you provided the others, right?
- You threw it out, right?
- Yes. I did.
- I'll see you around.
- Firuz. How's your boy doing?
The same. No change.
What's this?
Deva, take a look at this. Come here.
Isn't that the corpse
that was found in the jungle?
Salim or something?
But what are they doing there?
Who are they?
I don't know.
Respond to them and let's get acquainted.
One second. One second, miss.
Calm down for one second.
You saw the man from the photos, right?
Alright.
Where did you see him?
In a dream?
You saw him in a dream.
Sweet dreams, miss.
- This is impossible.
- Be patient. Something might turn up.
What are you doing?
I'm making a list of the Kamburan gentry.
Tomorrow is the Kambura Day
at the station.
I might tell them I'm their new leader.
Hello? Connect them.
Nevra, I'm calling
your mom's husband in, as well.
I'm listening, sir.
Where did you see him?
When?
Please stop wasting my time.
Ayhan?
- Ayhan, good luck with all this.
- Thanks, Agah.
We're doing our best to tidy up.
I'm sorry about last night.
You join us once in a blue moon,
I wish it hadn't been so unpleasant.
It wasn't unpleasant.
It was a proper disaster.
What was that?
I'm so glad we up and left.
I wouldn't want to get beat up.
I had a lady friend with me, too.
We were so scared.
What business do you have with such men?
Don't worry, Agah.
There's nothing left to be scared of.
What do you mean?
What if they come back?
They were shot that night.
All three are dead.
No way!
Really. Not everyone's like us, after all.
They must've gone after the wrong types.
Tried to extort him, and got shot.
Istanbul has become unrecognizable.
It shouldn't be this easy to kill people.
Look how relaxed you are,
talking about it.
I don't recognize Istanbul anymore.
Especially not Beyoglu.
Oh, that old Beyoglu...
That dear old Beyoglu...
What can I say?
When you're right, you're right.
Sadly, we've been getting reports
of mistreatment of residents
from nursing homes more and more lately.
However, we're at
a stellar nursing home right now.
We have a resident with us.
Let's ask her some questions.
Are you happy here?
Would you like to say anything?
I turned 65.
You look great.
I hope you see many more years yet.
On my last birthday, I made another wish.
- Like a child.
- That's great.
It was another impossible wish, of course.
It might not be. I hope it comes true.
You know what I wished for?
To become a good person.
- Great. We should all aspire to that.
- She remembers everything.
What is it, Agah?
You're awfully interested in her.
No. I'm more interested in the TV.
Mine's getting old.
I might get one of these.
Do you like it here?
How long have you been here?
It's crystal clear.
Whenever I come here,
something's on the TV.
- Anyway... Good luck to you.
- Thanks. Take care of yourself.
Come on. Tidy it up.
We're about to open back up.
Come on. We need to tidy the place up.
Customers are on the way.
So with Alzheimer's,
let's say it's at an advanced stage.
It's all over.
The patient remembers nothing.
Completely disconnected from the world.
- Yes?
- Might they suddenly remember?
Might they get their memory back?
Is that possible? Is that a possibility?
Does that happen?
Why are you asking me this?
You're not at that stage yet.
It's too early to be
worrying about stuff like this.
I'm pondering every eventuality.
It's worth hoping for.
Is it possible at all?
I realize that
I'll forget everything some day.
But I'm asking you
if this is a possibility.
Agah!
Alzheimer's...
Is still shrouded in mystery.
Each person is an exception.
Each case progresses differently.
But in general,
that's outside the realm of possibility.
Possibilities, exceptions.
You're not saying anything!
I'm asking you if it's possible or not!
Remember when I told you
about sudden bursts of anger?
I don't want to talk about my bursts!
Answer me!
You're having
one of those bursts right now.
Because you don't answer!
Because your question
doesn't have an answer!
Forgive me.
I mean...
Even if there are no known cases...
It's possible.
How about you relax now?
Take a few deep breaths
through the nose. Relax...
I can relax later! I can't relax now!
I have work to do!
- I'm leaving, with your permission.
- Agah...
Yes?
- Are you up to something?
- I don't... What do you mean?
Have you stopped taking your medication?
Of course not. I'm taking my meds.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Alright. For your next appointment,
please bring Zuhal along.
Excuse me? Why?
Is Zuhal the patient or am I?
Why does she need to be here?
Alright, fine.
Fine. I'll bring my daughter along.
How will I get in?
Where will I get in?
You poor Agah.
How will you...
Of course you can't.
Serves you right for coming so unprepared.
You're not about to sprout wings
and jump over the fence, are you?
Hello again.
You told me to come see you
if I needed anything.
No matter what, you said.
I need something.
Could you please die for me?
What are these?
The best picnics...
Are those had at home, Nevra.
I'll take that. Come in.
- Any news on Tayyar's brother?
- No.
There are, actually. Some woman called.
Told me she saw him in her dreams.
- How does that sound?
- Sounds great.
It's better than nothing.
When did you move in here?
As you can see, I never really did.
It's been like this for like six months.
I think it looks nice.
Maybe I should decorate
my place after yours.
I think that's a great idea.
Everything's all tidied up, you see?
Plus, when you want to move out,
you don't have to do any packing up.
Why? Are you planning to go somewhere?
I always go somewhere, Ates.
You can't tell from the outside,
but I very often leave my body.
- It's your turn.
- What turn?
I've told you everything about me.
Told you I've been rotting for years.
That all I want is
to become that old Ates again.
That Ates who
just got out of college.
That Ates who still believes
in journalism.
I've shown you all my scars.
Let you see all my pain.
It's your turn to tell me.
First, tell me why
you knocked on my door that night.
You know how you say...
That all you want is
to become that old Ates again...
I'm the exact opposite.
What I fear most
is becoming the old Nevra.
Why?
I think...
I don't know how to co-exist with people.
How to talk to people.
What to do with friends.
How to spend time with a boyfriend.
How to manage the space
between you and someone else.
I don't know how to do any of that.
But I've always pretended to know.
And I was always wrong.
I've had relationships
I really didn't want at all.
I've had friends that I never liked.
I couldn't say no to anyone.
I don't know why,
but I always cared so much
about what people thought about me.
As thought I had to make everyone happy.
Because...
You're...
Good.
No.
Because I'm weak.
I'm so weak, in fact,
that I'm scared of opening those boxes
and running into the old Nevra in them.
I knocked on your door that night,
because I felt really lonely that night.
The old Nevra, the one
I never want to become again,
used to fling herself
into some guy's arms
whenever she felt lonely.
Ce... Ce...
Cemil!
Whom was I with on that night?
You, or...
The old Nevra?
The old Nevra...
The old Nevra
would probably be
with someone else right now.
That's what I ran away from, Ates.
Cemil, he has a gun, Cemil.
Cemil...
Cemil!
- You stay inside.
- OK, be careful.
I ran away from myself.
That's why I wanted a new life.
A life where no one knew me.
To be more accurate...
A life without people
who think they know me.
That's why I resigned and started over.
Cemil!
Cemil...
There's no one here.
There was.
It was him.
- Who?
- The serial killer.
He's on everywhere.
He wears a cat costume.
He was there.
He had a gun in his hand.
- But there's no one around.
- He must've run away.
Maybe you scared him.
Funny.
Do you realize, Zuhal,
that you saved my life?
If I'd answered the door,
I doubt he'd have been scared of me.
- Let's go inside.
- Sure. Let's.
Cemil!
This is the first time
I'm telling someone all this.
Strange, right?
You chasing yourself,
and me running away from myself.
That's exactly why, I think...
We'll be a perfect couple.
- You know our first order of business?
- What?
You didn't eat anything.
Why aren't you eating?
Have you spoken to your mom?
She texted last night.
Staying over at a friend's or something.
- She should be back today.
- Who is this friend?
- I don't know.
- Aren't you curious?
She's an adult. Why would I be?
What do you mean, why? Is this a hotel?
Check in or out whenever you'd like.
You do it all the time.
We don't mind
you staying at your girlfriend's.
Stop running your mouth.
You're being ridiculous.
- Are you mad about something?
- Why would I be mad!
She should've let us know.
"I'll be here. I'll be back by this time."
Are you talking to me,
or are you staring at that screen?
I can do both.
No you can't listen
and do that at the same time. Drop it.
Fine. I've dropped it.
- What's that?
- What's what?
- That. Let me see that.
- Here...
- What's this?
- You're completely oblivious then, huh?
You don't watch the news?
He's a serial killer.
The first real Turkish serial killer.
How do you know it's a he?
It might be a woman.
That's possible, of course.
Why did you stick that on there?
Because he's doing incredible stuff.
What's incredible about killing people?
Depends on who you're killing.
Good morning.
They received another tip.
It seems legit this time.
There's nothing to eat around the house
except for our picnic's leftovers.
I'll be fine. Go save the world
so I can write about it later.
I'm going.
Came all the way to my front door.
To the house.
To my house.
I knew this was going to happen.
I knew it.
If you're killing Kamburans, you're going
to end up at my door sooner or later.
What am I supposed to do now? Tell me.
Whom do I bury and where?
Give me something.
We have the DNA report.
I have a connection in the lab.
He gave me the file
without the others knowing.
Run it against the DNA
of 80 million people.
What's this guy's beef with Kambura?
What's your people doing there?
There's this burnt-down house in Kambura.
They're looking for the brother
of the man who died in the fire.
Yeah. Hamza.
- Mister Hamza Kaymak.
- Yes, that's his name.
- He's a fugitive. Escaped from prison.
- I know. Because I arranged it.
Hamza doesn't know about that part,
of course. He wouldn't even know me.
What is it, Firuz? Why are you surprised?
You thought I didn't have other friends
working in other places?
Is that what you thought?
Do you know where Hamza is now?
Gratitude is a dying concept these days.
I don't know where he is, sadly.
That ingrate called Hamza ran away
from the people who broke him out.
Why did you get him out of prison, then?
Because I knew you'd fail with Ufuk,
I decided to take matters
into my own hands.
Fine, but what does Ufuk
have to do with Hamza?
Firuz, the less you know,
the easier you'll sleep.
That way, you won't come to me
asking me to let you go.
Got that?
We have lots of people
coming in from Kambura today.
Looking into the burnt-down house.
You know what
we were just talking about, Zuhal?
Why do you think he lowered his gun
when he saw you?
He didn't want to kill you.
He was here for me.
Why didn't he come inside?
I mean...
I don't know.
- Don't you find it strange?
- Very strange.
Maybe he changed his mind.
I don't know.
Isn't it possible that he regretted it?
It's not that easy, taking a life.
Well, Zuhal,
that depends on whom you're killing.
Yes, Sungur.
Why did that house burn down?
Who burned it down?
I don't know who burned it down,
but we all thought Tayyar was a thief.
I mean...
Word was going around.
Thieves drive me up the walls.
If he came to us, telling us needed help,
we would've given him everything.
But stealing? Come on.
We saw a crowd gathering around the house.
So I went over with the kids.
Suddenly, a fire started.
We wanted to put it out...
- But couldn't.
- You couldn't.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
I'm looking for Kamuran G枚zc眉.
They told me he worked here.
Brother Kamuran? Over there.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Good day. Murder Bureau.
Nevra Y谋lmaz.
I'm looking for Kamuran G枚zc眉.
Come on in. I'm Kamuran.
Take a seat.
You said you knew Hamza Kaymak.
I know him, of course.
He sat right there just yesterday.
Helped us clean the mussels.
Then he got word of something
and started panicking.
He apparently talked to someone
last night. He was gone in the morning.
- Where might he have gone?
- I wouldn't know.
Bulgaria, Greece...
The guy he talked to smuggles people.
One of the boys overheard them.
And Hamza...
Probably to pay that smuggler,
he took all the money we kept here.
Look... I implore you.
If you find that man,
ask him about our money.
It was for their honest work.
I don't remember anything, son.
I wouldn't know anything at all.
Selim... Uncle Selim.
You must've overheard something.
You weren't there that night. I know.
But didn't people talk about it
around Kambura? They must have.
Well...
Our people don't like foreigners.
Not me, of course. But...
I don't discriminate at all.
But... I mean...
- That might be why.
- Because he was a foreigner.
Sure.
Foreigners are different to us.
Different to us. Yes.
Ates...
You ran a story on human smugglers.
It had interviews and stuff in it.
I need to get a hold of one of them.
I don't care who.
Alright. I'll see you there.
Nobody put chains on anything.
Who told you they put chains
on the windows and doors?
It was all ablaze when we arrived.
Ufuk was crying out, trying to get inside.
We did our best, but it was impossible.
We were torn between holding Ufuk back
and trying to put out the fire.
That's when something fell on
Ufuk's head. A beam or something.
He was already a half-wit.
After that, he became really strange.
What were you doing there?
Ufuk had been talking about it a while.
Saying he'd burn that place down,
saying he'd kill Tayyar.
When we saw Ufuk
running to the house, we followed him.
To stop him from doing something stupid.
But we couldn't.
Why did Ufuk want to kill Tayyar?
Because he was a thief,
or because he was Romani? Why?
He's mad, I'm telling you.
You can't ask a madman why he did what.
Tayyar might've given him
dirty looks, for all I know.
It's a small place.
There's nothing to do but bicker.
You think being involved with
my daughter makes you immortal?
Alright.
If you're not going to bleed for now,
whom would you like to take your place?
How about your blood brother?
That works, right? That works beautifully.
I think that would be so poetic.
Hello.
Who are you looking for.
- We're looking for Anchor R眉艧t眉.
- I don't know him.
They told us everyone in Kumkap谋
would know him.
Especially you.
There must've been a mistake.
I don't know anything.
I don't know any R眉艧t眉.
We aren't after you.
Just tell me where Anchor R眉艧t眉 is.
- There's this street.
- Where is it?
You have a deal.
Anchor R眉艧t眉?
Yes? What do you want?
I want this man.
His name is Hamza Kaymak.
What does it have to do with me?
He paid a smuggler
to take him across the border.
Why would I know about smugglers?
- Aren't you a smuggler?
- What are you talking about? No.
I'm actually really calm by nature.
I don't like getting mad.
But I'm in a real hurry. Would you like to
see me get mad in a hurry?
What if you did?
What would I do...
I might start with
making you eat the shells, for a start.
Do you have
the license plate down? Alright.
Announce it over the radio.
The white minivan
will be leaving Tophane in two hours.
It's carrying illegal aliens
and the fugitive Hamza Kaymak.
I'm sending you all the info.
I'm on my way.
Nevra...
Did you just point a gun at a man
for throwing nuts on the ground?
I can do you one better.
I saw a bull in my dream the other day.
I pointed my gun at that poor creature.
Um...
I should head to the paper.
I'll clean up my office a bit.
Thank you.
I hope you find what you're looking for.
I already have.
- What happened next?
- Next, nothing...
He pointed his gun at me.
He took a good look at me,
and lowered his gun.
I shut the door, of course.
When we went looking for him,
he was gone.
- You didn't call the cops?
- Of course we did. Of course!
You must've been so scared.
It was really scary in the moment.
But thinking about it now...
There was this moment
when he took a good look at me...
It went on for a few seconds.
I felt something...
- I felt something really strange.
- What did you feel?
I mean... It was almost like...
Like I was sure he'd never hurt me.
It was so strange.
Yes. It really is.
I mean, my whole life,
I've never been so sure
that someone wasn't going to hurt me.
Do you get what I'm saying? Never!
No matter whom! Except for you, of course.
But look...
Look, this is burned onto my mind.
I'm really little.
Eight years old. Maybe nine.
We're going on vacation.
My dad told me he'd teach me
how to jump from the pier.
I'm on the pier.
My dad's in the water.
He's gesturing me, telling me to jump.
"Come on, jump."
But I can't jump. I couldn't do it.
I felt my father
wouldn't be able to protect me.
Do you get what I'm saying?
It felt as though...
As though he could hurt me,
albeit unintentionally.
As though if I were to drown,
he wouldn't be able to rescue me.
If something were to happen
to me, he wouldn't...
I couldn't trust my father!
I couldn't trust my father on that day!
But whatever it was
that was inside that cat...
I trusted that thing, Deva!
Could he be someone you know, mom?
- Or might he know you?
- Don't be silly.
- I wish you did.
- Where's your grandfather?
- Huh?
- I asked you where your grandfather is.
He might be with his girlfriend.
I don't know.
Oh, Deva...
Hello!
- Is there anybody there?
- I'll be right there.
Hello. How can I help you?
I was looking for...
I don't know, a small houseplant.
Agah?
- Agah Beyoglu?
- Yes?
Forgive me, I'm not sure I remember you.
It's Tayfun, Cemil's friend!
From Kambura!
Tay...
Tayfun! Is that you? No way!
- What a coincidence!
- You haven't changed one bit.
- You're still as handsome as ever.
- Stop it. I'm an old man now.
How are you doing?
What are you doing here?
Not much. I own this whole area.
I cultivate all kinds of plants.
How nice. How...
I was passing by and I needed
some plants for the house.
When I saw this place,
I decided to stop by.
- What a coincidence.
- Don't worry, I've got you.
You used to take such good care of us.
Do you remember all those meals
you bought for Cemil and I?
We were dirt-poor students back then.
Come on. Take a seat.
Make yourself at home.
You must be busy.
I wouldn't want to impose.
Don't be ridiculous.
I've sent the guys home.
It's almost closing time.
Come on. Let's catch up.
- Come on.
- OK, then.
What a coincidence.
It's a small world, I'm telling you.
We have the vehicle in our sights.
It's headed right to here.
Alright. Finish the paperwork first.
Don't let them suspect anything.
He might be armed.
Of course.
Follow the vehicle,
but keep your distance.
- Thank you. You're so kind.
- Of course.
So? Do you and Cemil
still see each other?
Cemil's too busy.
He's become an important man.
He stops by now and again.
- Would you mind if I had some raki?
- Of course.
- It goes down well at this time of day.
- Helps me clear my head.
- Enjoy yourself.
- You prefer coffee, right?
- Yes. Thank you.
You could join me, though.
Would you like a glass?
No. I shouldn't.
The other day, I was visiting a friend...
He set a beautiful table
and brought out a bottle of raki.
We were having so much fun, but after
a while, I started feeling really bad.
- Why? Was it your stomach?
- No. Memory loss.
I forgot what I came there to do.
I don't have the constitution anymore.
You enjoy yourself, I'm fine.
Thank you.
Pull over.
Good evening. Papers, please.
Good evening, officer.
Here.
All my papers are there.
Everything should be in order.
- I have somewhere to be.
- Hold up. I haven't checked yet.
Get out! Out! Out!
Get out! Get out of the car!
Get out! Out! Out, I said!
Get out!
Put your hands up!
Let me see your hands.
Get up! Get up!
Listen up.
They have Hamza.
- So? What am I supposed to say?
- What are you supposed to say?
Hamza will tell them everything he knows.
They've forced our hand.
You're going to tell them
everything you know, as well, Vural.
Keeping Ufuk in mind, of course.
Is that clear?
Of course.
- How many left?
- This is the last one.
- Name?
- Vural Yasl谋.
Go on.
Take a seat, Vural.
Vural Yasl谋... Yes.
Go on. Tell me what happened in Kambura.
How did you escape from prison?
Who helped you?
Storks.
Storks flew me away.
Then flew me back.
Who would help a poor man such as I?
I escaped on my own, of course.
Got myself hospitalized,
and escaped from there.
Your brother Tayyar and his family
died in a fire in Kambura.
What do you know about that?
I don't know much about it.
My brother liked to drink.
He was a drunk.
He drank like a sponge.
But you can't really help it.
You need workers to till the fields.
He came to Kambura every year.
Found a job to do one way or another.
They worked, him and his whole family.
A fire broke out at their house.
His family died in that fire,
including all his children.
That drove me up the walls.
I headed to Kambura.
I asked them what happened.
They told me there was a fire,
started from a cigarette butt.
I asked the fire brigade and the police.
They all told me the same story.
There was this guy, Halis. He used to
run the fire brigade. He's dead now.
He told us it was a cigarette butt
that started the fire.
That's what we all knew.
It didn't sit right with me...
It was a tiny house.
I didn't get why they couldn't escape.
Then two young men came to talk to me.
They were brothers. Twins, apparently.
- One was named Seyfi or something.
- And the other's name, Umut?
That might've been it. It's been a while.
- They're Ufuk's brothers.
- Ufuk?
They're actually triplets.
Go on with your story.
They told me
to drop the subject and go home.
I asked them why.
They told me my brother, Tayyar,
had raped a young girl from Kambura.
And not once, at that. Again and again.
His time must've come, they said.
If you keep hanging around,
they might decide
to take her revenge on you, they said.
They weren't talking about someone else.
They were threatening me.
"Since you're Tayyar's brother,
you might die before your time."
"They'll plug you full of holes."
That's exactly what they said.
Nevra came to Kambura.
We spoke in front of the house, in fact.
That's where we ran into
each other after all those years.
It can't have been more than a week.
Ufuk found out about it.
Came to me, told me a cop from Istanbul
was there to take him away.
I asked him what he'd done.
Asked him why...
"I burned that house down," he said.
"I killed those people."
But he'd been singing
the same refrain for years,
so I didn't take him very seriously.
He told me about a girl then.
There was apparently someone
Ufuk had been pining after.
That bastard named Tayyar raped her.
Ufuk decided to kill him in a fire.
That was the night.
He went to the house
and put chains around the exits.
Then he started the fire.
I was stunned, of course.
Who is this girl?
Whom did Tayyar rape?
Why didn't we ever find out about it?
He didn't answer any of it.
Just up and left.
I thought he was hallucinating again.
He'd never been all there, you know.
But it all turned out to be true.
He really did burn that house down.
Why else would he hang himself?
Tayyar's family had been inside.
His children, his wife.
All dead.
Who could live with that knowledge?
We saw the flames and ran over.
We gathered around the house...
But there was nothing we could do.
Remember that fireman
who told us it was a cigarette butt?
The late Halis?
He had been protecting Ufuk.
He must've known what really happened.
His brothers must've known also.
Seyfi and Umut were their names.
May God forgive their sins.
Do you think your brother
might've really done it?
- Could he really have raped that girl?
- I don't know.
He would never do something like that
when sober. That, I'm certain of.
But drink? Drink turns people inside out.
You never know who people really are.
Not even your own brother.
That's why I left Kambura.
Did they tell you who the girl was?
- No, they didn't.
- Are you sure?
I don't know!
No. I don't know who she was.
She must've been really scared.
She didn't make herself known.
Let me tell you something.
If we'd known about what he did,
we would've been the ones
to burn that house down.
We would've fucked his whole family.
I mean, when I say fuck...
As a figure of speech, you understand.
We would never touch
his wife and his kids.
- There's a proper way of doing things.
- A proper way...
You'd fuck him properly.
Back then, of course,
villages didn't look like they do today.
They were properly rural.
I was in some county in Anatolia,
working as a court clerk.
I come across this murder file.
I open it up
and look at the suspect's statement.
He's a young man. 18 or so.
His father takes him aside,
tells him
about the blood feud his family's in.
They looked into it after the fact.
It had been going for 60-70 years.
Two families,
killing each other one by one.
Anyway, the father says to his son,
"It's our turn to take a life."
"You're going to do it. You're young,
you won't do much time."
The boy's father brings out the gun.
It's a family heirloom.
They've been using that same gun
to kill their enemies for 70 years.
Right there,
the father teaches him how to use it.
"Here's how you load the chamber.
Here's how you cock the gun."
"You got it?" his father asks the boy.
"I got it," the boy says.
He takes the gun in his hand,
and shoots his father. Just like that.
Doesn't even hesitate.
The gendarme asks him,
"Why did you do it?"
"Why else?" says the boy.
"I wanted to end the feud."
They ask the boy again in court.
"We get it, you wanted the feud to end.
But how could you shoot your father?"
"Well," the boy says,
"I've always hated my father."
"I would've killed him a long time ago,
but I didn't have a gun."
- That's some story.
- It is.
What about the blood feud?
Did it end?
It did. The other family was baffled.
The feud ended,
but it was the boy that suffered for it.
He was sentenced to life.
Isn't that how it always goes?
The young are always the ones
who end up suffering.
- It's all over the TV.
- Why do you say that?
Why hasn't there ever been
an elderly suicide bomber, for example?
It's always the young
who blow themselves up.
It's always the young ones.
Never the elderly.
The young ones die so quick,
so easily... It's a real pity.
Their lives have no value.
How can there be a meaning to life
if there is no value to it, right?
How have we gotten onto this subject?
I don't know. I must be getting drunk.
Anyway. I've kept you too long.
Give me some flowers and I'll go.
Of course.
I want something for the windowsill.
- What would work?
- Here. This one. Here.
- I'll give you this one.
- A rubber plant?
- Yeah. You need to water it twice a week.
- Alright.
- It likes sunlight, but not too much.
- Of course. Of course.
Mebrure used to love these.
What do I owe you?
- Don't even mention it.
- No way. I want to pay for it.
- I can't take your money.
- Of course you can.
I know we're friends,
but this is business.
- But...
- It's your first sale to me.
I hope it brings you luck.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- You're too kind.
- Don't be silly.
- Thank you so much. Say hi to Cemil.
- Of course. Take care.
- Take care.
- Come back soon.
Goodbye. Of course.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Oh...
The bag...
Of course...
Oh...
That was some explosion.
I must've went overboard with the bomb.
I almost went back for the bag.
I'm starting to really lose it.
SAVE ME NEVRA