Can I be part of your start-up?
Why?
Why. as in?
You all are engineers
You need an MBA
Naveen had called
Yogi and Naveen have quit their jobs and...
are planning a start up.
I feel you should join them
Anyhow, you have to speak to dad regarding this
I really want to be part of this
Unless you don't solve one of their problems
they don't need you
I know a coder, he is in 3rd year
Let's get him onboard. Trust me. He'll rock!
I looked into your idea
It's quite interesting actually
But, I haven't mailed you anything yet
Privacy on mail is a myth, my friend.
I think we need Jeetu
You think we need jeetu?
We need Jeetu.
I'll not be able to join. Sorry!
Why are you so scared of your Dad?
I can solve your problem
I can give you something which you need.
I can give you Jeetu.
Untill you find an investment
I'll pay for Jeetu's salary
Cheers!
and then "There were Four".
Ok. Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Your idea is very good.
I am going to U.S
As soon as I am back from U.S
We will start the investment process
Great!...
ok
That's..
wow..
So, zeeshan!
When do you return?
I am back in november 2016
November 2016..?
Yeah.. got some work
But you guys don't worry
A soon as I am back, we'll complete the funding and start the work
and mark my words
By quarter 3, 2030!
You will be number 1 in your verticle
2030?
Yes.. 2030!
You have to understand and get into the mind of the VC
they are all very rich guys
you have to suit up a little bit
You have to look a little professional
Boss! I think all that is bullshit!
Next time wear a t-shirt and slippers to meeting
Keep your feet on the table and tell him
write a cheque, or else I am leaving moth*rf**ker
Confidence is the key!
So, once we acquire enough users, we plan to raise a second round
We might even go mobile only. Just like Flat-Chat!
So, What do you think?
Gaurav!
Haan!
yes. One sec
Guys, you all are from 2011 batch. Right?
yes!
Do you guys know Shaina Oberoi?
Shaina Oberoi?
Do you guys have her number?
No?
How much funding do you need?
You have set it up well in two and a half years.
Investors were very excited about the idea of delivering Indian food to homes
and its very affordable
The meal that you are eating now costs Rs. 435
Cool. Rs.435 for 3 plates.
Its Rs.435!
I have Rs.400
Be confident, place your foot on the table
I'll give you the funding.
like Now!
Be professional
Show me some Confidence!
What are you thinking?
Yes!
That's more like it. Boss!
What are you doing?
You will not get my money and
I will make sure no body funds you in Hiranandaani.
You don't keep your foot up.
He will. How will he not?
I lived in the silicon valley for 17 years
I have invested in like 5 companies there
But India
The fragrance of soil has dragged me to this country.
You know, I want do something Indian
we will make India's Uber
We call it "Induber".
You getting what Iam saying!
you see..
Why don't you have any females in your team?
You think woman are not on par with men
I started Zorpolo from scratch
and today, it's worth 50 f**king million
Why don't you have any female co-founders?
Come on join me.. come on.. what's wrong?
come on.. come on..
Getting a funding is equal to fighting the battle of Mahabharatha
Pandavas were 5 of them, though.
Now to win this war, what do you guys need?
Passion
Commitment
and Dedication
It was retorical
Ask what is needed?
What is needed Sir?
We need Shree Krishna!
Tell me, who is Arjun among you guys?
Arjun?
should be Jeetu? I can be Yudistir.
No Iam Yudistir, I never lie
You are Bheem? No.. Dibs on Bheem.
You are Sehdev
You are Bheem?
Naveen.. ya Naveen
Ya..I think it's me. Iam Arjun.
Hello Arjun
Ah..
In 1972
my gradfather started a small bhujiya shop on the streets of Bikaner
a small shop
and today
Weather its breakfast with tea or snacks with beer
it's only our brand, that people use
It's been 25 years, we are leading the market
also we were on the cover page of last month's Fortune magazine.
Despite of all this
Do you know what people call us behind our back?
What do they say?
Bhujiyawaala!
So that's why you want to expand to different sectors?
You are catching on..
I am putting my money on new ventures
Your product is very exciting
Perfect for our diversification.
I want to invest in you guys
That's great Gary
we actually wanted to dilute 15 to 20% of our equity
for around 1.2 to 1.6
You guys decide the number
I' ll decide the equity
I want atleast 51%
But sir 51% practically makes you the owner of the company
Company?
You mean.. four of you?
haan?
If one falls sick, you won't be having a proper teams to play carrom
Company!
Amount that you're asking for in the market
multiplied by 4
plus my brand
My contacts
Plus new office space
Its not a bad deal at all
Sir can we negotiate somewhere around 30-35%
I am not selling vegetables, you As*h*le
Ah! Gary, but this is a very difficult decision
we will think over it and let you know
like 51% is a lot
Shree Kriskna had asked Arjun, the blood of his own family members
I am just asking for a little more stake
nothing much.
Will talk about it on Sunday
Parth.
Parth?
Naveen.
Parth!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry... Sorry.
No no.. Please.
Go on..
I don't want to hold you back.
No.. I was thinking about Gary's proposal..
Naveen!
Do you realise we, meet like once a week now.
You'll be busy when I come to your place
Can't you talk to me for 5 minutes properly?
I'm sorry. sorry!
Don't you think you have been saying sorry too often these days?
Iam sor....
Yeah maybe I am screwing up a lot these days
I am really sorry
Naveen, Its not gonna work like this.
We need to talk..
I am sorry.. I am sorry..
Aww Baby.. You got scared?
Arey. It's not funny.
Yogi was saying
Ashish brokeup the same way
He got busy with the startup
he couldn't give time to his girlfriend
What nonsense!
such a cliche.
But cliches exists for a reason
Let us do some clihe?
Let's go to Goa.
What about your Bangalore trip?
I'll skip it
and moreover we dont even know when we get time after this weekend.
Don't be foolish and
ignore the job.
Your job stays with you for the next 30 years, even if I don't
just go to Bangalore
Lets go to Goa!
It's just a small project, anyway
Arey, its your work ya
Don't cheat your work!
Will go to Goa someother time.
Ok. What defines you better?
Business Consultant at Mckenzie or Naveen Bansal's girlfirend?
Tell me.
Ok fine.
I will go to Bangalore
Happy?
Very unromantic as*hole
What un-romantic as*hole
We can have fun here as well.
wanna drink something?
Ya.. One hazelnut cappucino and one Chicken tikka sandwich
One tea and two idlis please.
and dessert?
and what cigerrates do you have?
Goldflake. Sir
I have drawn the second FD too on wednesday.
Yogi is looking for loan
and don't know how much to depend on Mandal!
and about Gary's proposal
at times feel it's a necessity
and some times I feel its greed!
But you don't have to necessarily settle for Gary
Tomorrow, you have an event
won't there be potential investors?
there will be.. But..
may be for one last time.
We are running out of time, Shreya
If none of the investors show any interest in our tommorow's presentation
we might have to go with Gary
Did you try your Jury room approach?
No.. not yet.
What do your 3 stooges say?
Nothing as yet
They are banking on me to take the right decision.
That's getting me more scared
I could hug you right now
and say that you will be great
you will make the right decision
or
I could be less dramatic and tell you
I believe in you Naveen Bansal
Just like the 3 boys waiting for you at home.
Oh Shit!
What happened?
wait.. wait.. can I get a parcel..? 6 idli's, 2 chai...
Sir. Food got over.
Where is he still?
He said he will return in 15 minutes, its been 2 hours now.
asked me to wait just for a tea.
I need to go home and sleep
Yogi, call him now.
He left his phone here
we would have made tea here itself
If this as*hole wouldn't have used all the milk to set the curd
Tomorrow is an important day
How do we get lucky if we don't eat curd and sugar?
Shut up! You piece of crap
As*hole
For the last 6 hours you are only changing the font of Thank You.
Aey.. Aey.. Its very important to make a lasting impression. Ok!
Atleast I am not roaming around the city since morning
I had been to print visiting cards, you motherf*ckr
What do you do when you meet investors and they ask for contacts?
Guys, what's happening here?
Naveen, this is harrasement at work place
I can't work like this.
I can't tolerate this.
What you can't tolerate?
You 'll take my laptop to the room and jerk off watching Wolf of Wallstreet
No, I was preparing for the pitch.
I''ll kill you ba*t**d
You know what I saw on touchpad?
Yogi, what are you saying man?
We had to use sanitizer, Jeetu tell him.
Stop it.. Stop it Yogi.
Yogi, Behave your age.
You are bullying us since 10th standard.
Stop it now.
Madal, he's right. there's was something on the touchpad that day!
Jeetu! You are doubting me?
I swear, it was just curd.
Jeetu relax
we have an event tomorrow, don't be stressed.
You be quiet.
Do you even know what stress is?
Soumya is asking for watermelon from past 3 days
and I am not able to do it because
from past 2 days I am getting a compilation error
I am lying here since 2 days and I am exhausted doing this
I thought of having a good sleep today to be ready for tomorrow's event
But now you ruined it by coming two hours late
Now, the market at Borivali opens at 6am
I have to buy it from there.
Soumya will also ask me to get fresh fish also
So I need to carry watermelon in one hand and fish in the other
and travel in local train from Borivilli
because my bike is punctured and
no time to repair it because I am lying here since the last two days
Stress it seems.
Hold this!
Is breakfast ready?
Set it up quickly, please!
Did you read my message?
I don't have time now
I am already runing late by half an hour
I have to get fresh and leave.
Where are you going on Sunday morning, son?
Dad!
Arey No.. my nephew was saying
Vishwanathan Anand doesn't like fried idli at all
What?
Ya seriously
Too much crowd..
These 24-25 years kids try to start the company as soon as they get out of college.
Half of them might not even know the spelling of entreprenuer
All virgin as*es!
That qeue looks smaller.
Is this the line for Registration?
No!
We are standing to pick up the ration
hahaha
As*hole
Do you know him?
whom?
That guy. Wanna be Zukerburg, Amit Awasti.
completed his B-Tech from NIT Hamirpur
but wears Harward T-shit to show-off
He is the founder of Litigator
Litigator?
Its the social network for Lawyers.
They had issues with co-founder regarding equity last March
They used his own app to file a lawsuit against him
Do you recognise him?
who? John Snow?
who Snow?
That guy in black suit?
Oh..the guy in black suit?
Ya.
haan.
No.
He is the founder of milkman.com, Ritwik mukherjee.
Okay.
Milkman. I've heard about it. Its like the Uber of dairy products
Dairy products my ass !
Its just an online stable.
In 2012, it started of with the name dudhwala.com...
but then government banned it thinking it's a porn website.
Now they have relaunched it with a new name.
By the way, I'm Saurabh Mandal.
This is Naveen Bansal
And yogi.
Hello sir.
Do you have a VC ?
Visiting card ?
Yes, I do. Freshly baked .
Then give it.
Actually you meet a lot of frauds in such events.
Last time some asshole clicked a selfie saying "I am Rahul Yadav".
Later I got to know that asshole was just a B.com student from Mithibhai.
Give it using two hands... With one hand is cnsidered unluncky!
You should be knowing all of this, we are of same age.
Take it.
ya.. like that
Ravi Ram Rastogi.
Hmm..
CEO, CTO, CMO
Founder, Superentreprenuer.com
This is my 8th company
and about those seven before this?
They were shut down.
Oh!
But this one will take me to the list of Fortune 500
Wait and Watch!
Thing is.. Hello..
So the thing is
The soul of entreprenuer is always restless.
It will roaming around untill you come up with a masterpiece.
So only 3 of you guys?
No sir..
No.. no. Its good.
The lesser number of co-founders, higher will be the equity value.
No sir, we are four of us. Jeetu is on his way
Yogi, call him and ask where did he reach?
Oho.. that's like 8% loss.
No problem, carry on!
Leave it Dad.
It's in the warranty
company guy will come and fix it for free.
haan. You studied computer science instead of mechanical
you might get tired to do all these stuffs
give me a bigger screw driver?
are you looking for app for it?
No.. no. Its about work
Watchen was saying..
You didn't come home for 2 days.
Actually Dad.
the company guys are making him work a lot
beacuse of the project
they call him daily, even on sundays
You get fresh
get ready
Dad, would you want to eat watermelon?
What kind of project do you have on Sunday's?
Call your boss and tell
your dad has come from Bikaner, so can't come today.
give the phone, let me speak to him
Dad, It doesn't work that way.
have just come for a day
If not for Pandyaji's daughter wedding
I wouldn't have come.
Can't you have lunch with your dad for a day
your company won't shut down without you.
Yu have grown up now right!
nothing like that Dad.
I will just be back.
Hey! I am talking to you!
Send TTYL to your boss
Dad
Watermelon
Hello Yogi.
Yogi i can't come
All of a sudden dad showed up!
What nonsense?!
yes! He is not allowing me to leave.
Not allowing to leave?
Are you a 4th grader?
Arey Yogi.
Jeetu?
Yes dad i am coming.
I am talking something important, and you are peeing?!
Just wait Yogi.
Jeetu?
The seminar is about end, post lunch is our main event.
Leave quickly!
Yogi I will talk to you later
Jeetu?
yes dad!
What is this?
looks like a boxer
it was stuck behind the tank
You don't even have time to keep your clothes in check.
and what were you doimg in the bathroom?
nothing.. phone...
I was peeing.
you will wash your hands after that or
anyone from the company will come to do it.
I'm really really sorry sir, but this is the fourth time i'm telling you
that i can not give you the passes until the entire team registered
But madam you have to let us startup
This is our VC card
I am sorry sir. We have to follow certain guidelines.
See, listen...
Apoorva..
Apoorva, our friend is on his way.
Isn't it possible to first give us our three passes.
Like, you can hold on to our friend's pass.
He will collect it from you, when he is here.
Let me check.
Naveen.
Naveen..
Actually I
just found out that...
this is not a movie theatre...
and we cannot hold on to your passes.
But we have paid the registration fee....
1,857 Rupees per head.
Sir, you're holding the que, could you please step aside.
You can't do this to us...
I want to speak to the management.
How can she talk to us like this ?
I'll get you fired.
Mark my words.
The battle has just begun.
The battle of 1,857 rupees.
Mangal and Pandey wont let her be.
Stop it.
What rubbish !
How can she talk to us like this.
Relax.
Let's figure out something.
Figure out what?
She has everyone's profiles.
We won't get entry without jitu
I told you, let's have sugar and curd before leaving.
Mandal, Please don't start again.
Dont' answer.
Answer.
Hi Gary..
Gary, I am little busy, can I call you after sometime ?
There's still time for the presentation to start, Parth..
You're already busy ?
No Gary.
We just came here to see a friend.
One doesn't meet friends in such events...
You either meet your competition or investors!
Don't think of me as an idiot.
And Listen..
Put your phone on loudspeaker
Then you won't have to play Dumb charades.
Ya.
I'm not upset...
If I was in your place I would have done the same.
You should get a good value for a good product..
and there is no better place then such events to realize your product's value.
Gary, It is a good event but we're.....
In a hurry ? I know..
You have to meet a lot of investors...
have to discuss you're future plans
I know..
But before that, you dont want to listen to my new offer ?
New offer ?
I thought a lot..
Then I realised that this deal is little unfair for you..
So the amount which you guys had proposed?
Suffix a zero to the number.
Gary..
That's a lot of money!
No.
You wanted a lot of money...
and I am giving you a lot of money X 10
But ofcourse...
Equity will be the same... 51%.
That is non-negotiable.
I'm on my way to my lonavala farmhouse...
For a meeting.
Give me your answer before I get there...
Or the offer stands cancelled.
And ya...
If you get an investor before that then..
All the best.
But Gary how will I reply so fast
Naveen you're beer
And I am snakcs!
If we both get together, we'll have a party!
I'll be waiting for your call...
Parth.
Did he just offer us...
Jitu always goes missing in such crucial times.
Mandal just text him once. -okay.
What are you thinking ?
I need a jury room.
Smells nice!
Have you added ajwaine?
Yes papa.
Salt water fish have a very unique taste..
They're very soft soft.
ya.
We don't get it over at our place!
I'll be back in two minutes.
Where are you going at lunch time ?
Just closeby to get some milk... Rgiht below the building!
The milkman has already come in the morning!
Dad. I though I'll prepare some 'Rabdi' for you in the evening!
There was less milk so I asked him to.
Ya she asked me to.
But why do you need to go in this heat???
I will have it next time.
No Dad. It's no trouble. I insist.
Saumya makes nice 'rabdi'. I'll go get it in 2.
Wait a minute Jitu.
Sit over here.
Beta (daughter) listen.
Make me this concoction.
Papa, can I make it after lunch ?
No, the doctor has asked me to have it with lunch.
And listen.
Take your time and boil it for long!
There's no hurry.
Yes, Papa.
Tell me honestly.
Where were you going.
Papa, to buy milk, whatelse.
You were going to smoke a ciggarette.
Papa, I quit smoking in college.
Don't lie.
I've found a few in your office bag!
Papa..
How much should I lie for you ?
Before marriage...
Before marriage I had to lie to Parimal that you dont drink or smoke..
They married their daughter into our family because they had trust in us.
And you had promised your mom
That you would quit smoking!
Did you quit?
Okay, Sorry papa.
If you get desperate to smoke than have a chewing gum .
Hardiyal quit it the same way.
Okay Papa then I will go, get some mint from downstairs!
Here.
Have it.
If you make one more sound
I will put castrol in your mouth and make you gargle it.
What are we waiting for ?
We are getting soo much money now!
If we take more time then even this plan will get ruined.
Naveen has the first right to take a decision.
Let him come out of the jury room.
Then we will decide.
What is this jury room ?
I've been sseing it since our college time.
Whenever Naveen faces a dilema
He locks himself in a room for 15 minutes.
And he comes out with the right decision.
And thats why we call it a jury room.
But in such a busy event, how did he find a empty room ?
This is the height of sexism.
What, were they not expecting female entreprenuers at all ?
Gents washroom is open but the female washroom is locked!
You will get a lot of mcps in such events.
You know what..
Even in my visiting card I have given my brothers number.
And how did you ?
If one Gandhiji can convice lacks of britishers ...
Why wouldn't a housekeeper get convinced with two!
You guys are still here ?
Ya.
Didn't go home?
Where is that CEO of your's ?
Actually that's who we are waiting for!
If you're wasting time...
Then follow me on twitter!
Ya ya..
I have 198 followers.
If you both follow me, then it'll become a double century.
Shit !
I have only 116...
But I have 312 followers on linkedIn.
312 ?
Shit !
Just wait for my app to get launched..
Then watch how I overtake you.
Why can't you go there and do your networking ?
Actually I am waiting for my roommate..
I forgot my keys.
Even the other 7 are out.
So he is coming to give me the keys.
You'll are 9 people staying together?
4 BHK ?
No No..
It's a 2 BHK
But spacious enough.
800 sqft.
Actually
Since I got a divorced in 2008...
I've to live in a shared apartment!
It helps you build..
Teamspirit.
You had a divorce ?
Yes.
Sorry.
Why you're saying sorry ?
When she is not saying sorry..
It's okay.
Everyone is not that lucky to have a Sudhamurthi in their life.
Once my company gets funded...
Just wait and watch how 'Manglik' girls line up for me!
But in so many years you didn't get funded even once ?
I did..
In 2003 I did..
There was an investor who was ready to invest..
But was asking for 50% equity.
And our founder and CEO
Was sort of a buddha type..
Said no to it .
Since then till today... I swear to god
The only time I have slept peacefully is while travelling in a train's sleeper class.
Ya karunesh..
Yes.
Come inside.
What !
They aren't letting you?
Why do you always come in boxers???
Dumbfuck!
What happened ?
Tell me what happened ?
Yogi ?
Okay, I have decided.
What ?
I want to tell you'll with Jeetu. Let's go to his place .
What are you doing ?
Yogi'd texted me. I am going down.
They are waiting for me in the parking lot.
What will I answer dad if he gets up ?
Please handle it for 2mins..
Please..
Please.
Okay, you go...
I will handle it.
Third floor or fourth floor ?
Terrace !
Don't stand... -Hey jitu, hie..
Don't stand over here, the watchman out here is my dad's spy.
Hmm, so what did you decide? Mandal, lower the volume.
So what did you decide, we are taking money from Gary, right ?
This one's not telling us anything at all!
No, we aren't taking money from Gary.
Infact I already texted him saying "No".
Naveen, what is the logic behind this ?
What logic, It's our idea our hardwork
We are working on it from such a long time
Now randomly we would give away half the stakes to somebody, why ?
He is giving us money, that's why, don't you get it..
How it helps our compnay's valuation!
I guarantee you, in one year we will create more value than this .
Naveen..
Are you serious !
We couldn't even go for today's event
Forget about raising funds...
Investors aren't calling us for even a second meeting.
You think Sikoya and Nexus will join hands...
and beg you to take their investments ? !
We'lll have to compromise a little, Naveen .
Aren't you all realising that thios guy is a 'Bhujiyawaala'.
He doesn't even have a technical background..
How will he understand our product ?
That's the advantage.
If he doesn't have any technical knowledge
he won't interfere . -what if he interferes ?
Then we're fucked.
We'll think about it later..
And how can you take such an important decision by yourself?
Just because you've C.E.O. on your visiting card...
... doesn't mean you are the boss.
Naveen
We are a team..
And there is no I in team.
Guys it isn't that..
You know, whenever I've taken a decision in the jury room, it's always been right
yes？
And what exactly do you do in the jury room ?
What ?
I am asking you!
How do you take your decision in the jury room?
It's simple..
He must be listing down the pros and cons..
Does a SWAT analysis of it and determines the probablity.
Even I have done that in the third semester of my high school
SWAT analysis ?..
Probablity ?..
He fucking tosses a coin and decides.
What !
Tosses and decides ?
Naveen look here..
I had decided to marry saumya after asking you!
I didn't need to toss a coin for that.
But you needed it today?
You fucking decided four peoples carrer,ambition
and their future on the basis of tossing a coin !
And what if it was the other side of the coin ?
Then right now we would have been in Gary's farmhouse licking his ass ? !
Naveen I can follow you till hell but I can't follow a 1 Rupee coin.
Naveen, everyone has left their job...
This startup was your idea, right ?
We are working 16 hrs continously at your home.
And this CEO tosses a coin and decides.
Atleast you could have asked us once ?
Was that asking for too much from you?
What was it Naveen? Head or tail ? - Guys I don't know what it was!
Decision was taken on the basis of tossing the coin, not on the result of it.
What do you mean ?
Like this coin even life gives us 2 choices...
No matter how many lists of pros and cons you make both sides would always be equal
And you won't be able to pick any side.
That time all you can do is listen to your heart.
That's why if you toss the coin once, you will come to know which side won.
But you didn't even see if it was a head or a tail ?
I didnt see it but I heard it.
When the coin stays in the air for half a second..
A voice answers from the bottom of your heart...
Which says..
Please let it be heads, please heads!
That's when you realize no matter what the result is...
Your heart wants it to be heads.
And I have realised that our first investment can't be set on the basis of greed.
Where gary is in greed of equity and we of money
Our first investment should be only on the basis of our...
Idea and skill.
Just for more funding I can't let anyone control my ambitions.
I am really sorry I could'nt do it.
Now you guys decide what to do.
Where are we going ?
Back to the event.
But what if they don't let us in!
The same thing what we always do ..
Try.
Let's go.